<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FAQ on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FAQ on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Piper Bly .</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Piper. I&amp;rsquo;m an underground cartoonist, professional illustrator, and wandering ne&amp;rsquo;er-do-well. I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling stories and creating work for what is basically my entire adult life, and this is where I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to place my thoughts on doing so, as well as ramblings about life in general.
This blog is mainly where I write about things that hold my interest, and is also where I put notes on books, records, and other such things that I&amp;rsquo;m working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/post/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/faq/</guid>
      <description>Note: This FAQ page is a constant work in progress, as is most of the site. As I get new questions, think of things I might want to make sure my readers know, and invent new answers and/or questions for those answers, I&amp;rsquo;ll be adding them here. If you can&amp;rsquo;t find an answer to whatever it is that you&amp;rsquo;re curious about, send me an email and I might just add it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/post/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/links/</guid>
      <description>The following are links to websites of folks I think are cool.
Note that I said websites, not accounts. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to use this page to promote social media networks, and the vast majority of folks (specifically, other cartoonists/DJs) who I know all have social media accounts in place of a website, so this list shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be considered an exhaustive compendium of folks I think are neat.
f you&amp;rsquo;re not on this list but think you should be, I probably can&amp;rsquo;t find your website or I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten around to adding you yet because I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with other obligations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellany</title>
      <link>/post/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc/</guid>
      <description>The following is a series of links to random accoutrements that I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out a way to shoehorn into a post, but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to build a whole new website for. So, I&amp;rsquo;m putting them all under a lil&#39; umbrella here for those of you who would be interested in these types of things.
Note: This list is VERY incomplete at the moment&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;m in the middle of a bunch of things and need time to code a bunch of the things I plan on including here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
