<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>photo roll on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/photo-roll/</link>
    <description>Recent content in photo roll on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Sarah Allen Reed.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/photo-roll/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 03 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll03/</guid>
      <description>Part one of two sets of progress photos of me working my way through the concept art for The Garden.
 
 The initial pencils for the concept art image. I hid [Gnome Chompski](https://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Garden_Gnome) in there somewhere--see if you can find &#39;im!  
 Starting in on inks, going section by section.  
 Layer layer layer  
 Most of the sections are filled in now; only a few more adjustments then it&#39;s digitization time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 02 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll02/</guid>
      <description>Some in-progress photos of me working my way through Our Lady Maven Issue 1.
 
 Inking panels from the comic.  
 Full art for Page 8.  
 Close up inks. You can see the ink smudges from the typewriter real well here.  
 Probably my favorite panel. 
 
 Sneaking in an overt homage to one of my favorite adventure game detectives</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 01 - Polyhymnia, Emotional Support Dumbass</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll01/</guid>
      <description>Polyhymnia was supposed to be a service dog for my autism and PTSD, but the training she was supposed to get never actually happened. So now she&amp;rsquo;s just my favorite dumbass who tries her best. Here&amp;rsquo;s some cute photos of her over the years.
 
 Baby Poly  
 Not-quite-baby Poly, sunnin&#39; on my old sofa.   
 OH LAWD SHE TONGUE
 
 &amp;quot;Look mom, I can DJ too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 00 - Selfies, Self-Portraits, And Portraits Of The Soul</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll00/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll00/</guid>
      <description>For whatever reason, a lot of folks seem to be fascinated with knowing what folks who create things look like. I&amp;rsquo;ve never understood it&amp;ndash;partially because I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly the type of artist known for going out of her way to look remotely presentable&amp;ndash;but for those of you curious, here&amp;rsquo;s a tiny little selection of self-portraits and press photos I&amp;rsquo;ve had taken over the years.
 
 Self-portrait from the pages of Tabula Rosetta.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>