<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Piper Bly .</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#022: Studio News: Fall And Winter, 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0022/</guid>
      <description>Hey ya&amp;rsquo;ll! Sorry for the delay, again, but I&amp;rsquo;ve got a whole bunch of studio news, life updates, and the like for ya. This one&amp;rsquo;s a bit long, so settle in and get comfortable.
Also, some things on this list include some heavier topics; I&amp;rsquo;ve went ahead and put a content warning both on those posts and on the titles of the sections in the table of contents, so if you&amp;rsquo;re not in the headspace for some heavier topics you can go ahead and skip past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#017: Studio News: Summer 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0017/</guid>
      <description>Hey ya&amp;rsquo;ll! As you know, it&amp;rsquo;s been a good minute since I&amp;rsquo;ve had the time to sit down and write a full-on Studio Update. We&amp;rsquo;re finally settled in&amp;ndash;mostly&amp;ndash;in the new studio1, and I wanted to check in and let y&amp;rsquo;all know what&amp;rsquo;s coming down the pike, what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to, and where I&amp;rsquo;m planning on heading next.
 WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WORKING ON OUR LADY MAVEN 
Issue 2 on the drawing board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#011: The Finer Things, April &amp; May 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0011/</guid>
      <description>HahaahaAHAAHAA fuck this is late
I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy. As much as I&amp;rsquo;d like to, I&amp;rsquo;ve not had much time to pen a long column about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to in my spare time, much less had much spare time to spend. Snakes, Barren, and a couple other upcoming projects have kind of monopolized most of my attention, and I&amp;rsquo;m a bit late on having a second to sit down and write about fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#009: Stone Jaw: Trans Healthcare And Other Cognitohazards</title>
      <link>/post/0009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0009/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve honestly hesitated to write about this topic; it&amp;rsquo;s a personal one that&amp;rsquo;s heavy even by my standards, and on top of that it&amp;rsquo;s not an easy thing to talk about. With that stated, it has kind of colored my output (when it hasn&amp;rsquo;t outright prevented me from creating work at all) for the past few years, and to be quite frank I&amp;rsquo;m going to end up covering it (or aspects of it) in one of my upcoming books anyways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#008: Studio News: March &amp; April 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0008/</guid>
      <description>Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bit of a longer segment this month, so I&amp;rsquo;m breaking my &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo; into two segments; &amp;ldquo;Studio News&amp;rdquo;, where I talk about the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to and what I&amp;rsquo;ve got in the pipeline, and &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo;, where I talk a bit about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to, watching, reading, playing, and smoking.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also got a bit of a long, introspective topic to talk about, but that&amp;rsquo;s getting lopped into its own post as well; it&amp;rsquo;s heavy enough for one of my books, which means that I&amp;rsquo;d rather put it in its own little column instead of putting it in with the lighter things I usually talk about on this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#005: Apparently I&#39;ve Been Banned From Instagram</title>
      <link>/post/0005/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0005/</guid>
      <description>Quick note - as of me editing this post on March 15, my Instagram account has been reinstated. I&amp;rsquo;m still going to actively avoid using it unless necessary, as I stated in this post, and I&amp;rsquo;ve also added &amp;ldquo;Share To&amp;rdquo; buttons to these blog pages and to the galleries if you wish to show off my work to some folks or talk about what I have to say on this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#003: Studio Notes/The Finer Things, January &amp; February 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0003/</guid>
      <description>The corkracks, sometime in the middle of production of Our Lady Maven.  Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I’ve just finished up the final touches on Issue 1 of Our Lady Maven at long last, and I’ve finally got time for a bit of a breather to write a bit about what I’ve been working on, what I’ve been reading when I have a second to sit down and read, what I’ve been listening to in the studio, what I’ve been playing in my wee small hours of the morning before I pass out for the day, and (for those few of you who are curious for reasons other than wondering “what the fuck is wrong with her”) what I’ve been smoking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#001: A Fresh Start, Old Computers, and a New Coat Of Paint</title>
      <link>/post/0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0001/</guid>
      <description>Intro Hey, y&amp;rsquo;all. As you&amp;rsquo;ve most likely noticed, 2022 was&amp;hellip;.well, not a good year for social media. Twitter&amp;rsquo;s on fire, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s been under federal scrutiny for years now, and seeing as I don&amp;rsquo;t have a face for anything but radio, I&amp;rsquo;ve never bothered with Tiktok.
So, now that I&amp;rsquo;ve finally updated my website again, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to just go back to basics and start a little blog here instead. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been more long-winded than most social media sites want me to be as it is, and this kind of format gives me more of an opportunity to write a bit about things I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t normally get the chance to talk about otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Piper. I&amp;rsquo;m an underground cartoonist, professional illustrator, and wandering ne&amp;rsquo;er-do-well. I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling stories and creating work for what is basically my entire adult life, and this is where I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to place my thoughts on doing so, as well as ramblings about life in general.
This blog is mainly where I write about things that hold my interest, and is also where I put notes on books, records, and other such things that I&amp;rsquo;m working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/post/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/faq/</guid>
      <description>Note: This FAQ page is a constant work in progress, as is most of the site. As I get new questions, think of things I might want to make sure my readers know, and invent new answers and/or questions for those answers, I&amp;rsquo;ll be adding them here. If you can&amp;rsquo;t find an answer to whatever it is that you&amp;rsquo;re curious about, send me an email and I might just add it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/post/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/links/</guid>
      <description>The following are links to websites of folks I think are cool.
Note that I said websites, not accounts. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to use this page to promote social media networks, and the vast majority of folks (specifically, other cartoonists/DJs) who I know all have social media accounts in place of a website, so this list shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be considered an exhaustive compendium of folks I think are neat.
f you&amp;rsquo;re not on this list but think you should be, I probably can&amp;rsquo;t find your website or I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten around to adding you yet because I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with other obligations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellany</title>
      <link>/post/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc/</guid>
      <description>The following is a series of links to random accoutrements that I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out a way to shoehorn into a post, but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to build a whole new website for. So, I&amp;rsquo;m putting them all under a lil&amp;rsquo; umbrella here for those of you who would be interested in these types of things.
Note: This list is VERY incomplete at the moment&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;m in the middle of a bunch of things and need time to code a bunch of the things I plan on including here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>