<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>the garden on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/the-garden/</link>
    <description>Recent content in the garden on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Sarah Allen Reed.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/the-garden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#020: Studio News: Fall 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0023/</guid>
      <description>Hey ya&amp;rsquo;ll! As you know, it&amp;rsquo;s been a good minute since I&amp;rsquo;ve had the time to sit down and write a full-on Studio Update. We&amp;rsquo;re finally settled in&amp;ndash;mostly&amp;ndash;in the new studio1, and I wanted to check in and let y&amp;rsquo;all know what&amp;rsquo;s coming down the pike, what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to, and where I&amp;rsquo;m planning on heading next.
 WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WORKING ON OUR LADY MAVEN THE GARDEN WHAT HAPPENED TO SNAKES?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#017: Studio News: Summer 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0017/</guid>
      <description>Hey ya&amp;rsquo;ll! As you know, it&amp;rsquo;s been a good minute since I&amp;rsquo;ve had the time to sit down and write a full-on Studio Update. We&amp;rsquo;re finally settled in&amp;ndash;mostly&amp;ndash;in the new studio1, and I wanted to check in and let y&amp;rsquo;all know what&amp;rsquo;s coming down the pike, what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to, and where I&amp;rsquo;m planning on heading next.
 WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WORKING ON OUR LADY MAVEN 
Issue 2 on the drawing board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 05 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 2, Part 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll05/</guid>
      <description>Part one of a series of progress photo galleries of me working through Our Lady Maven, Issue 2.
 
 Hand-lettering, as usual. It&#39;s how we do it here.  
 Pencilling in a facsimile of the Chicago skyline.   
 Roughing in the other two panels.  
 Blocking in the kids with some more rough pencils. I&#39;m using a General&#39;s carpenter&#39;s pencil here to scratch in some shading to mark where I&#39;m going to put some thick swatches of black ink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 04 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 2</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll04/</guid>
      <description>Part two of two sets of progress photos of me working my way through the concept art for The Garden.
 
 Initial pencils for the concept art for Kaia here.  
 Pencilling in the adults....  
 ...and the other kiddos.  
 Adding in some inks on the concept art of the adults. 
 
 Inked kiddos. Karina, Penny, and Bobbie on the top, and a full sheet of Kaia on the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 03 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll03/</guid>
      <description>Part one of two sets of progress photos of me working my way through the concept art for The Garden.
 
 The initial pencils for the concept art image. I hid [Gnome Chompski](https://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Garden_Gnome) in there somewhere--see if you can find &#39;im!  
 Starting in on inks, going section by section.  
 Layer layer layer  
 Most of the sections are filled in now; only a few more adjustments then it&#39;s digitization time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ongoing Project Update Threads</title>
      <link>/post/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/updates/</guid>
      <description>The following is a series of progress threads for pieces that are announced, that I have permission to share the creation process of, and that I want to share with you. These all used to be up solely on social media, but in the interest of both wanting to have everything in one place and insisting upon utilizing Indieweb principles to make sure my work isn&amp;rsquo;t lost to the ages for the umpteenth time thanks to the whim of some techno-jackanape, I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting them here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Update Thread: The Garden</title>
      <link>/post/update_garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/update_garden/</guid>
      <description>Here, you can find a chronological &amp;ldquo;thread&amp;rdquo; of sorts of posts about Our Lady Maven. You can also click on over to the [&amp;quot;The Garden&amp;quot;] tag](/tags/the_garden/) to see all these posts individually, as well as a good amount of other things I&amp;rsquo;ve written that mention the series.
This page gets updated all the time, so check back frequently!
 Photo Roll 04 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 2 September 8, 2023 Original post here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>