<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>the jazz program on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/the-jazz-program/</link>
    <description>Recent content in the jazz program on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Sarah Allen Reed.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/the-jazz-program/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#010: : Much Ado About Cassette Tapes: May 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0010/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm&#34;&gt;datafruits.fm&lt;/a&gt; for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records. This one will be our programming calendar for the month of May of 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to tune in, &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;head on over to datafruits.fm/chat&lt;/a&gt; on Tuesday evenings from 10 PM EST/7 PM PST to 1 AM EST/10 PM PST. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to learn more about the show and read about the fantastic artists and old-time radio shows we&amp;rsquo;re broadcasting this week&amp;hellip;well, read on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, a bit of an interlude&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;if-i-knew-what-i-was-doing-it-wouldnt-be-called-research----sourcing-the-history-of-old-time-radio&#34;&gt;IF I KNEW WHAT I WAS DOING, IT WOULDN&amp;rsquo;T BE CALLED RESEARCH &amp;ndash; SOURCING THE HISTORY OF OLD TIME RADIO&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0010/01.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Some of the many physical tapes in my collection. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week, we talked about my history with collecting old-time radio, the Dead, and other fun things on cassettes, as well as a bit of my history with manipulating cassettes in my work as a musician and DJ. Collecting these little guys is fun and all, but when it comes to researching them for these write-ups and for the show, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more than just spinning .mp3s that goes into it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a long time, the old time radio hobby was kind of open season. Much like found footage groups, folks would trade cassettes at swap meets, often with very little in the way of labeling, consistency in naming conventions, or much else. The transition to .mp3s and filesharing in the late &amp;rsquo;90s, and early &amp;rsquo;00s didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly help much. It was pretty common to find shows with woefully incorrect metadata, or literally no metadata at all. Thankfully, these days we have a lot of groups that have gone out of their way to research, catalogue, and document as much as possible about these pieces of radio history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://audionoir.com&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Audio Noir&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Another fantastic station worth tuning into, Audio Noir plays nothing but the great detectives 24/7. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://otrr.org&#34;&gt;The OTRR&lt;/a&gt; is often my first port of call when doing research on a new program to play on the air. Between their encylcopedic main website &lt;a href=&#34;https://archive.org/search?query=creator%3A%22Old+Time+Radio+Researchers+Group%22&#34;&gt;and their archive work on archive.org&lt;/a&gt;, if a radio show exists these folks probably have it in their registry. They even have a program on offer called &lt;a href=&#34;https://otrr.org/?c=otter&#34;&gt;OTTER&lt;/a&gt;, which fixes metadata and helps track down missing info in case you find a show file that&amp;rsquo;s incomplete, and the &lt;a href=&#34;ttps://www.otrr.org/OTRRPedia/pedia.html&#34;&gt;OTTRPedia&lt;/a&gt; is another great resource for finding that kind of info manually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For tracking down exact show air dates, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oldtimeradiodownloads.com&#34;&gt;Old Time Radio Downloads&lt;/a&gt; usually has pretty close to what I&amp;rsquo;d be looking for. I try and list the exact date of air for each show when I can, but sometimes the dates conflict. Ninety nine percent of the time, OTRD has the exact date of air I&amp;rsquo;m looking for. OTTRPedia also often has that info, but I like the way OTRD has it displayed; a simple CTRL+F and a quick type of the episode name gets me the info I need, quick as you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, as much as I&amp;rsquo;d like to keep you locked on &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;datafruits.fm&lt;/a&gt; during my show hours, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of other Internet radio stations&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; I use to discover new-to-me shows to share with all of you. &lt;a href=&#34;https://oldtime.radio/&#34;&gt;Oldtime.radio&lt;/a&gt; is a great web player with different &amp;ldquo;stations&amp;rdquo; that are sorted by genre, &lt;a href=&#34;http://audionoir.com/&#34;&gt;Audio Noir&lt;/a&gt; is a former pirate radio station (and current Internet radio station) out of Chicago that focuses on the best of noir radio plays, and if you want a break from the radio plays and want some call-in cranks and spoops, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.u7radio.org/&#34;&gt;U7&lt;/a&gt; plays the best of Art Bell twenty four hours a day, seven days a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of radio&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;may-2023-talkie-time--jazz-program-schedule&#34;&gt;MAY 2023 TALKIE TIME / JAZZ PROGRAM SCHEDULE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;may-2-2023&#34;&gt;May 2, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--lives-of-harry-lime---works-of-art--clay-pidgeon&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : Lives Of Harry Lime - Works Of Art / Clay Pidgeon&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0010/02.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/02.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; No, not &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; Harry Lyme. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0099785/characters/nm0000582&#34;&gt;Different movie.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;The Third Man&amp;rsquo;, released in 1949, directed by Carol Reed, and starring Joseph Cotten in the lead role of Holly Martins and the great Orson Welles himself as Harry Lime, is an undisputed classic of film noir. Hell, the British Film Institute once declared it the greatest British film of all time. At the risk of spoiling an over seventy year old movie, the film follows Martins attempting to find out who killed his friend Lime, only to find out that Lime faked his own death. Lime eventually finds himself actually killed by Martins, and that&amp;rsquo;s where the story ends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This film isn&amp;rsquo;t where the story of Harry Lime &lt;em&gt;begins&lt;/em&gt;, however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starring Welles reprising his role from the 1949 cult movie, &amp;lsquo;Lives Of Harry Lime&amp;rsquo; forms a series of prequels of sorts, telling the many tales of Lime&amp;rsquo;s work (and many lives) as a con artist. As Welles himself puts it, &amp;ldquo;Harry Lime had many lives&amp;hellip; and I can recount all of them. How do I know? Very simple. Because my name is Harry Lime.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll be listening to &amp;ldquo;Works Of Art&amp;rdquo;, originally aired on September 28, 1951, and &amp;ldquo;Clay Pidgeon&amp;rdquo;, which aired on August 17, 1951.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-presents-_first-of-the-month-listener-request-night_--chick-corea-for-the-boss-man&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program Presents &lt;em&gt;First Of The Month: Listener Request Night&lt;/em&gt; : Chick Corea for The Boss Man&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s Listener Request night again, and we&amp;rsquo;ve got a top-priority request here. Datafruits&amp;rsquo; own big cheese, MC Firedrill&amp;ndash;or &amp;ldquo;Ton&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo; as I often refer to him&amp;ndash; wants to hear some Chick Corea. And who am I to refuse the Big Cheese?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, we&amp;rsquo;ll be playing three records from Chick Corea&amp;rsquo;s Elektric Band, namely 1986&amp;rsquo;s self-titled, 1987&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Light Years&amp;rsquo; and 1991&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Beneath The Mask.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;may-9-2023&#34;&gt;May 9, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0010/03.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/03.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &#34;shut up and bring daddy the FUCKIN REMOTE or im GOIN OUT FOR CIGARETTES&#34; -- Randy Stone, probably&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--night-beat---number-13--i-wish-you-were-dead&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : Night Beat - Number 13 / I Wish You Were Dead&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There have been many legends of radio and TV with some notable sponsors. Orson Welles&amp;rsquo; radio theatre troupe was notably sponsored by Campbell Soup. Jim Henson got his start &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LmhIizQQol0&#34;&gt;blowing up proto-Muppets in the name of Wilkin&amp;rsquo;s Coffee.&lt;/a&gt; But very few can say that they were sponsored by your alcoholic stepdad&amp;rsquo;s breakfast of choice&amp;ndash;namely, the winning combination of Pabst Blue Ribbon Beer and Wheaties.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Night Beat has that honor. Starring Frank Lovejoy himself as reporter Randy Stone, each episode has Stone on the titular night beat for the Chicago Star, and each episode ends with him screaming for the copy boy to take his story in to the editor&amp;rsquo;s office because he was just too lazy to do it himself, just like your alcoholic stepdad used to do about the TV remote. Sponsored by the breakfast of champions, indeed. We&amp;rsquo;ll be hearing &amp;lsquo;Number 13&amp;rsquo;, which originally aired on March 6, 1950, as well as &amp;lsquo;I Wish You Were Dead&amp;rsquo;, which originally aired on May 22, 1950.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-smoke-if-ya-got-em---joe-hendersons-relaxin-at-camarillo-1979-antonio-carlos-jobims-stoneflower-1970-and-jeremy-manasias-witchery-2007&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program: Smoke If Ya Got &amp;lsquo;Em - Joe Henderson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Relaxin&amp;rsquo; at Camarillo&amp;rsquo; (1979), Antonio Carlos Jobim&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Stoneflower&amp;rsquo; (1970), and Jeremy Manasia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Witchery&amp;rsquo; (2007)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0010/04.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/04.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Witchery cover art&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; I genuinely don&#39;t know why, but I can&#39;t look at this cover art and &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; hear a reggae cover of &#39;Ocean Man&#39;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look, we gotta have at least &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; dumbass theme night on the schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea of &amp;ldquo;records with dudes smoking on the cover&amp;rdquo; honestly comes directly from my recent listens of Jeremy Manasia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Witchery&amp;rdquo;, a record I put on because the cover amused the hell out of me. The idea of a relatively energetic piano jazz record with a cover art featuring the lead pianist ripping a hit off a blunt with &amp;lsquo;Murica sunglasses and a giant doofy grin on his face is just a fantastic one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It then occurred to me that there&amp;rsquo;s an absurd amount of jazz records that just have &amp;ldquo;band leader hitting a cigar/cigarette/blunt&amp;rdquo; for cover art. So, I put together a list. You find recurring themes in the strangest places, man. We&amp;rsquo;ll be listening to Joe Henderson&amp;rsquo;s seminal &amp;lsquo;Relaxin&amp;rsquo; At Camarillo&amp;rsquo;, Jobim&amp;rsquo;s masterpiece of bossa nova &amp;lsquo;Stone Flower&amp;rsquo;, and the aforementioned New York jazz scene staple&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Witchery&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;may-16-2023&#34;&gt;May 16, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--dick-lawrence-review---lost-pilot-of-a-lost-age&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : Dick Lawrence Review - Lost Pilot Of A Lost Age&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0010/05.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/05.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Witchery cover art&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; RIP to yet another fantastic classical music station. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadcast from the legendary (and now &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bruceduffie.com/awnibwiki.html&#34;&gt;overtaken by a soft rock station and apparently wiped from the face of Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;) classical station WNIB in Chicago in the &amp;rsquo;80s and &amp;rsquo;90s, The Dick Lawrence Review is an interesting case in the history of narrative radio. A writer &amp;amp; vintage music historian who got his start in the early 1970s at WXFM with a &amp;ldquo;Roaring 20s&amp;rdquo; show, Dick&amp;rsquo;s radio programs combined vintage music, pulp magazine stories, and what he called &amp;ldquo;audio archeology, a restoration of antiq sounds&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t managed to find many recordings of his show (or even a photo of the man), and the ones I could track down have very little in terms of metadata and broadcast dates, but the ones I have found are fantastic. We&amp;rsquo;ll be listening to &amp;ldquo;Lost Pilot Of A Lost Age&amp;rdquo; tonight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-ben-webster---see-you-at-the-fair-1964--ben-webster-plays-duke-ellington-1989--soulville-1957&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program: Ben Webster - See You At The Fair (1964) / Ben Webster Plays Duke Ellington (1989) / Soulville (1957)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love me some Ben Webster. Old-time fans of the show know that, before we went to an &amp;ldquo;artist spotlight&amp;rdquo;-type format, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BkiFKnIio7I&#34;&gt;title track from his record &amp;ldquo;Soulville&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt; was our unofficial theme song. Slow, jazzy, and the perfect theme to &amp;ldquo;light up a smoke, light a cigar, and light your local police precinct on fire&amp;rdquo; (as the old opening to the show used to go), Ben and the gang know how to set a mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll be setting plenty of moods this evening, with 1964&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;See You At The Fair&amp;rdquo;, 1989&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Ben Webster Plays Duke Ellington&amp;rsquo;, and the aforementioned &amp;lsquo;Soulville&amp;rsquo;, released in 1957.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;may-23-2023&#34;&gt;May 23, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time-fear-on-four---green-and-pleasant--survival&#34;&gt;Talkie Time: Fear On Four - Green And Pleasant / Survival&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aired originally between 1988 and 1997 on BBC4, &amp;ldquo;Fear On Four&amp;rdquo; features host Edward de Souza as &amp;ldquo;The Man In Black&amp;rdquo; in a fantastic horror anthology series. If there was ever a BBC Radio production that saw the sound staff earning their paycheck, this is it. The foley is impeccable, and with stories by authors like Bram Stoker, Mary Shelley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight we&amp;rsquo;ll be listening to &amp;lsquo;Green And Pleasant&amp;rsquo;, written by Bert Coules and originally airing on January 3, 1991, and &amp;lsquo;Survival&amp;rsquo;, adapted from a story by John Wyndham and originally airing on March 19, 1989.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program--ingfried-hoffman-memphis-black---soul-cowboy-1969--soul-club-1969--hammond-bond-2007&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program : Ingfried Hoffman (Memphis Black) - Soul Cowboy (1969) / Soul Club (1969) / Hammond Bond (2007)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0010/06.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/06.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Soul Cowboy cover art&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; It may shock you to hear, but this is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; a photograph of a German organist. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pop jazz scene in the 60s and 70s was a weird one, as exemplified by last month&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://truckstop.coffee/post/0006/#the-jazz-program-tom-jones-pretends-to-be-an-american-for-two-hours-to-varied-but-amusing-results-tom-1970-darlin1981the-body-and-soul-of-tom-jones-1973&#34;&gt;Tom Jones Pretends To Be An American For Two Hours, To Varied But Amusing Results&lt;/a&gt;. Carrying on with that theme, we have legendary German jazz organist and composer Ingfried Hoffman, who&amp;hellip;well, for some reason, donned the visage of a black-as-fuck soul band from the deep South for two entire records.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m going to be honest, I tried as hard as I could to figure out a way to frame this episode without a &amp;ldquo;yeah no, this is not okay&amp;rdquo;-type disclaimer. Unfortunately for me, we&amp;rsquo;re pulling pseudonymous European jazz records from the time period which had both the golden age of blaxsploitation cinema and a European jazz scene that saw a lot of composers for television getting into producing their own records and finding out real quick that putting a random well-to-do TV-sound-booth white guy in a suit on the cover was not going to move discs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0010/07.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/07.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Soul Cowboy cover art&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; The actual &#34;Memphis Black&#34;. No, I don&#39;t know what to do with that information either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ingfried spent a lot of his earlier career played with Rolf Kühn and many others during this time period &lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, so there is a distinct possibility this was meant as an explicit tribute to the Memphis scene that just so happened to wear the face of American blaxploitation cinema because that&amp;rsquo;s the inspiration he was pulling from. Or, more likely, they just wanted to move records, and figured putting a young black chick on the cover would be more effective than an old German dude.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless of intent, there&amp;rsquo;s an absurd amount of musical blackface from this period in music history, and there&amp;rsquo;s no getting around that. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna ignore this time period on a show dedicated to deep dives in and around jazz, but I&amp;rsquo;m also not just slap a &amp;ldquo;this music was a product of its time&amp;rdquo; label on this episode and play the records without pointing this all out, or ignore the problematic elements of this time period entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, tonight&amp;rsquo;s show features two of his records under the pseudonym of &amp;ldquo;Memphis Black&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Memphis Soul Band&amp;rdquo;&amp;ndash;depending on where you were in the world when buying this record, as the releases differ in the US and EU releases&amp;ndash;as well as his eponymous release &amp;ldquo;From Twen With Love&amp;rdquo;. Disclaimer aside, these three releases are some of the finest examples of chill-out organ work from this time period, and are fairly essential and rare grooves from a time period that would eventually lay the foundation for electronic genres like trip-hop, downtempo, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;may-30-2023&#34;&gt;May 30, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time-_cloak-and-dagger-night_---the-brenner-pass-story--the-people-in-the-forest&#34;&gt;Talkie Time: &lt;em&gt;Cloak And Dagger Night&lt;/em&gt; - The Brenner Pass Story / The People In The Forest&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re continuing our end-of-the-month listenthrough of &amp;ldquo;Cloak And Dagger&amp;rdquo;, the radio drama adaptation of Corey Ford and Alastair MacBain&amp;rsquo;s 1946 book &amp;ldquo;Cloak and Dagger: The Secret Story of the OSS&amp;rdquo;, Cloak and Dagger has proved a frequent listen while I&amp;rsquo;ve inked away at Our Lady Maven, and it&amp;rsquo;s absolutely worth a listen even for those of you who aren&amp;rsquo;t currently drowning yourself in WWII spy history for work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0010/08.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0010/08.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Soul Cowboy cover art&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; CRIME JAZZ CRIME JAZZ CRIME JAZZ &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is our third night in our listen-through of the full series, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be listening to the two episodes which sequentially followed last month&amp;rsquo;s edition&amp;ndash;namely, &amp;lsquo;The Kachin Story&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Direct Lines To Bombers&amp;rsquo;, which aired on June 18, 1950 and June 25, 1950 respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-presents-_crime-jazz-night_--crime-jazz-volume-1-discs-1-3&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program Presents &lt;em&gt;CRIME JAZZ NIGHT!&lt;/em&gt; : Crime Jazz Volume 1, Discs 1-3&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like we say every month &amp;ndash; those in the know, know about Crime Jazz. And if you don&amp;rsquo;t know, we&amp;rsquo;ll be getting you in the know tonight for yet another end-of-the-month installment of Crime Jazz Night. We&amp;rsquo;ll be taking our first steps into the original first volume of the pirate site master compilation, with discs 1-3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s the show lineup for this month! I&amp;rsquo;ll be back in a few days with a few other posts&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot to write about that I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to put up here, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with a bunch of life stuff, including getting ready to finally leave Colorado and head off to greener pastures. I&amp;rsquo;ll see you next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a good one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SARAH &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;Footnotes...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re talking more about talkies than jazz here, but if you&amp;rsquo;d like other Internet radio stations to tune into that have similar jazzy sounds to my own, I&amp;rsquo;d be remiss if I didn&amp;rsquo;t include &lt;a href=&#34;https://somafm.com/secretagent/&#34;&gt;Illinois Street Lounge&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://somafm.com/secretagent/&#34;&gt;Secret Agent&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://soma.fm&#34;&gt;soma.fm&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If that sounds like a strange thing for me to fixate on, I want to point out that this strange sponsorship pairing &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Night_Beat_(radio_program)&#34;&gt;is literally in the first three lines of the Wikipedia article.&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna guess that I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one who finds that combo unintentionally hilarious. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To underscore the point of &amp;ldquo;yeah no, literally half the records from this time period and in this genre were just Not Okay by today&amp;rsquo;s standards&amp;rdquo;, it&amp;rsquo;s also worth noting that Ingfried&amp;rsquo;s first LP credit with Rolf Kühn&amp;ndash;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/master/486693-Rolf-K%C3%BChn-feat-Klaus-Doldinger-Rolf-K%C3%BChn-Feat-Klaus-Doldinger&#34;&gt;namely, &amp;lsquo;Rolf Kuhn feat. Klaus Doldinger&amp;rsquo;, released in 1962&lt;/a&gt;&amp;ndash;was only three years after &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/master/206156-Martin-Denny-Afro-Desia&#34;&gt;Martin Denny&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Afro-Desia&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;, another record (and composer) who we&amp;rsquo;ll eventually get to on another episode with its own disclaimer. Popular jazz in the &amp;rsquo;50s, &amp;rsquo;60s and early &amp;rsquo;70s was just kinda appropriational at best and outright &amp;lsquo;of its time&amp;rsquo; type racist at worst. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#006: Adventures In Thrift Store Tape Hunting: April 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0006/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0006/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm&#34;&gt;datafruits.fm&lt;/a&gt; for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records. This one will be our programming calendar for the month of April, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to tune in, &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;head on over to datafruits.fm/chat&lt;/a&gt; on Tuesday evenings from 10 PM EST/7 PM PST to 1 AM EST/10 PM PST. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to learn more about the show and read about the fantastic artists and old-time radio shows we&amp;rsquo;re broadcasting this week&amp;hellip;well, read on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, a bit of an interlude&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;home-recording-is-killing-the-music-industry-we-micd-your-tape-deck-so-you-can-help&#34;&gt;HOME RECORDING IS KILLING THE MUSIC INDUSTRY, WE MIC&amp;rsquo;D YOUR TAPE DECK SO YOU CAN HELP&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0006/01.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0006/01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Me performing live&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Yours truly, in my natural habitat: staring at a Thinkpad while fucking about with DJ decks and making a tape player make funny noises. Still image taken from a video of a live set recorded in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last month, I talked a bit about the early days of the tape trading traditions in the old time radio scene. This month, I&amp;rsquo;m going to take that and run in a slightly different direction (as I tend to do) and talk a bit about how how tape decks, pirate recordings, and both my works as a musician and my love of radio came about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been futzing about with tape decks for about as long as I&amp;rsquo;ve been recording sounds. My first release as Coma Roulette has me mucking about with an old radio and a tape deck on various tracks (something that&amp;rsquo;s been a recurring theme throughout my sonic output, as you can see from this photo of me performing life as Shibito in 2021, sampling an old tape of Gregorian chant via an old karaoke box) and I&amp;rsquo;ve had a reputation for using sampled sounds in my work since the beginning. You might think a lot of this would come from my time in and around the Internet&amp;ndash;plunderphonics and pirate radio go hand in hand with warez and IRC channels, after all&amp;ndash;but most of my love affair with tape comes from something a bit more personal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something I always try to do when I&amp;rsquo;m in a new place is explore, and one of my first ports of call always seems to be either the local flea markets or the local thrift shops. You can tell quite a bit about a city and its inhabitants by what they&amp;rsquo;re willing to hawk you on consignment, and in multiple occasions I&amp;rsquo;ve had the distinct luxury of finding dubbed tapes. Whether they&amp;rsquo;re joints from local bands sold at the local music shop for a few dolars, old Dead tapes from local heads who have transcribed them by hand and are selling them for two bucks a pop, or old time radio recordings being left outside because no one wanted them,&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; tapes have always seemed to find me in my travels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s definitely a lot of memories attached to my very meager tape collection. Between the few albums I&amp;rsquo;ve released through labels I still have copies of, the small shelf of tapes I&amp;rsquo;ve done art for, and my racks of old-time radio recordings, and the random copies of tapes I found at thrift stores by musicians whose discographies I now own (some of whom I play on the radio for you every Tuesday!) those lil&amp;rsquo; plastic squares have always kind of accompanied me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And speaking of the radio, let&amp;rsquo;s get into the schedule for this month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;march-2023-talkie-timejazz-program-schedule&#34;&gt;March 2023 Talkie Time/Jazz Program Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0006/02.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0006/02.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tom Adams&#39; cover art for Endless Night by Agatha Christie.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; This has nothing to do with the BBC4 version, I just love this cover art on this particular edition of the novel by the legendary Tom Adams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;april-4-2023&#34;&gt;April 4, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--agatha-christies-endless-night&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : Agatha Christie&amp;rsquo;s Endless Night&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look, property ownership&amp;rsquo;s expensive these days. Murdering your wife with cyanide capsules to get her inheritance isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly out of the question. I mean, have you &lt;em&gt;seen&lt;/em&gt; how high the rent is? Too damn high, if you ask me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll be listening to Joy Wilkinson&amp;rsquo;s 2008 BBC4 adaptation of this absolute classic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-presents-_first-of-the-month-listener-request-night_--lisafreak-takes-the-decks&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program Presents &lt;em&gt;First Of The Month: Listener Request Night&lt;/em&gt; : Lisafreak Takes The Decks&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s Listener Request night again, and we&amp;rsquo;re doing something special. Last week was chat member Lisafreak&amp;rsquo;s birthday, and I joked in the chat that I wish she&amp;rsquo;d have told me so I could have had something ready. Thankfully, I said, next week was Listener Request night, and so if we wanted to do a birthday show then I&amp;rsquo;d be more than happy to play whatever she&amp;rsquo;d like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out, &lt;a href=&#34;/lisa.txt&#34;&gt;she had an entire playlist ready to go,&lt;/a&gt; and it&amp;rsquo;s jam-packed with some fantastic stuff. We&amp;rsquo;ll be blasting it in its entirety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;april-11-2023&#34;&gt;April 11, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0006/03.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0006/03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Alan Ladd as Dan Holiday&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Alan Ladd in a promotional poster for Box 13, looking like a stone cold badass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--box-13---triple-cross--three-to-die&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : Box 13 - Triple Cross / Three To Die&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three&amp;rsquo;s usually a lucky number, but there&amp;rsquo;s nothing lucky about anything if it involves Dan Holiday. It&amp;rsquo;s time for more episodes of Box 13 on Talkie Time, the show about a mystery novelist with a need for ideas and adventure, a penchant for getting himself into trouble and a PO box that just seems to keep getting filled with exactly that kind of trouble.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll be listening to Triple Cross (originally aired November 7, 1948) and Three To Die (originally aired June 2, 1948)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-bob-berg---new-birth-1978--another-standard-1997--short-stories-1987&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program: Bob Berg - New Birth (1978) / Another Standard (1997) / Short Stories (1987)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Horace Silver, Miles Davis, Chick Corea. If you&amp;rsquo;ve heard those names, congrats&amp;ndash;you&amp;rsquo;re not too far from Bob Berg. The Brooklyn-born tenor sax wielder recorded with a laundry list of post-bop and modern jazz household names in his long career, and helmed his fair share of records under his own group as well. We&amp;rsquo;ll be checking out two of his post-bop recordings in two separate decades in &amp;lsquo;78&amp;rsquo;s New Birth and &amp;lsquo;97&amp;rsquo;s Another Standard, as well as a smoother side of his stellar oeuvre that lands somewhere in the middle of both with 1987&amp;rsquo;s Short Stories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;april-18-2023&#34;&gt;April 18, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--the-adventures-of-sam-spade---string-of-death-caper--soap-opera-caper&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : The Adventures Of Sam Spade - String Of Death Caper / Soap Opera Caper&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It should come as no surprise that the jump from the pages of Dashiell Hammett&amp;rsquo;s crime novels to ABC&amp;rsquo;s radio crime lineup was as smooth and easy as a strong glass of bourbon on a PI&amp;rsquo;s desk. &lt;em&gt;The Maltese Falcon&lt;/em&gt;&amp;lsquo;s Sam Spade has some of the most interesting stories in all of crime radio, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be airing two of them tonight&amp;ndash;specifically, &amp;ldquo;The String Of Death Caper&amp;rdquo; (originally airing February 2, 1951) and &amp;ldquo;The Soap Opera Caper&amp;rdquo; (originally airing February 16, 1951). Steve Dunne stars in the titular role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-tom-jones-pretends-to-be-an-american-for-two-hours-to-varied-but-amusing-results-tom-1970-darlin1981the-body-and-soul-of-tom-jones-1973&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program: Tom Jones Pretends To Be An American For Two Hours, To Varied But Amusing Results-Tom (1970)/ Darlin&amp;rsquo;(1981)/The Body And Soul Of Tom Jones (1973)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0006/04.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0006/04.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tom Jones&#39; bad-fitting shirt.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Someone get this legend a tailor. And probably some new buttons for that shirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me get a few things out of the way first, One, I unironically love Tom Jones. Whether you classify him into vocal jazz/crooner territory or not, you can&amp;rsquo;t argue exactly how fantastic and jazzy a lot of the compositions he appears on are (I&amp;rsquo;d like to submit his record &amp;ldquo;A-Tom-Ic Jones&amp;rdquo; as evidence here), and you also simply can&amp;rsquo;t argue with that vocal range. I&amp;rsquo;m playing him on The Jazz Program for the same reasons that we&amp;rsquo;ve featured both Astrud Gilberto and Portishead&amp;ndash;the former because, in my mind, crooner pop/exotica functions very well as a &amp;ldquo;gateway drug&amp;rdquo; to the more complex stuff,&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and the latter because this is my show, dammit, I play what I want, and my standards for what counts as jazz are looser than Tom Jones&amp;rsquo;s shirt on half his album covers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two, Tom Jones is not American. He is not from down south, he&amp;rsquo;s not country, and despite what his multiple album covers with him sporting a full afro would have you believe, he&amp;rsquo;s not any kind of soul save plastic. Man&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Welsh&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which makes the three records we&amp;rsquo;re playing tonight, in which he, in order&amp;ndash;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;covers Elvis&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Polk Salad Annie&amp;rdquo;, a track which starts with him claiming that &amp;ldquo;some y&amp;rsquo;all never been down south&amp;rdquo;, and then proceeds with him telling you all &amp;lsquo;bout where &lt;em&gt;he&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/em&gt; from, which clearly is Louisiana&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;puts on a cowboy hat in the cover art and does his best impression of cowboy trucker&amp;rsquo;s music,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;and, finally, dons an afro that he thought work for much of the 70s and into the 90s and has cover artist Shel Starkman paint him like he&amp;rsquo;s about to drop the best soul-funk record you&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard in your life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;simultaneously infinitely amusing and incredible listens. Somehow, Atomic Jones unironically nails all three notes. Don&amp;rsquo;t believe me? Tune in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;april-25-2023&#34;&gt;April 25, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time-_cloak-and-dagger-night_---the-brenner-pass-story--the-people-in-the-forest&#34;&gt;Talkie Time: &lt;em&gt;Cloak And Dagger Night&lt;/em&gt; - The Brenner Pass Story / The People In The Forest&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on Corey Ford and Alastair MacBain&amp;rsquo;s 1946 book &amp;ldquo;Cloak and Dagger: The Secret Story of the OSS&amp;rdquo;, Cloak and Dagger has proved a frequent listen while I&amp;rsquo;ve inked away at Our Lady Maven, and it&amp;rsquo;s absolutely worth a listen even for those of you who aren&amp;rsquo;t currently drowning yourself in WWII spy history for work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While claming to be based on fully authenticated case histories of OSS espionage, the series is about as wild as your average pulp from the era. Some language and themes haven&amp;rsquo;t exactly aged well (as with a lot of its ilk and similarly-themed shows from its era up until the 80s&amp;ndash;see also half of James Bond&amp;rsquo;s catalogue) but if you can look past its flaws, it&amp;rsquo;s still an entertaining romp for those of us who love a good spy romp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is our second night in our listen-through of the full series, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be listening to the two episodes which sequentially followed last month&amp;rsquo;s edition&amp;ndash;namely, The Breener Pass Story and The People In The Forest, which aired on June 4, 1950 and June 11, 1950 respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0006/05.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0006/05.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Crime Jazz.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; CRIME JAZZ CRIME JAZZ CRIME JAZZ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-presents-_crime-jazz-night_--crime-jazz-volume-2-discs-7-9&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program Presents &lt;em&gt;CRIME JAZZ NIGHT!&lt;/em&gt; : Crime Jazz Volume 2, Discs 7-9&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those in the know, know about Crime Jazz. And if you don&amp;rsquo;t know, we&amp;rsquo;ll be getting you in the know tonight for yet another end-of-the-month installment of Crime Jazz Night. We&amp;rsquo;ll be playing Discs 7-9 of Volume 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s the show lineup for this month! I&amp;rsquo;ll be back in a few days with a few other posts&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot to write about that I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to put up here, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with a bunch of life stuff, including getting ready to finally leave Colorado and head off to greener pastures. I&amp;rsquo;ll see you next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a good one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;SARAH &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly, finding a bunch of old recordings of old time radio that I saved from the garbage because the local consignment place didn&amp;rsquo;t feel they&amp;rsquo;d be worth selling should have been one of the first canaries in my ear screaming that I was not going to have a good time in Colorado. The first two examples are from Portland, Maine, a city which I still miss living in. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The textual reason as to &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; trouble keeps following him is literally that Holiday ran a classified ad in the newspaper he used to work for saying, and I quote, &amp;ldquo;Adventure wanted, will go anywhere, do anything – write Box 13, Star-Times&amp;rdquo;. I feel like that&amp;rsquo;s a great way to get a pipe bomb in your mailbox, but he seemed to spend much of the series getting people who just wanted to knife him instead. Not the brightest idea a noir protagonist&amp;rsquo;s ever had, which is impressive given the genre he&amp;rsquo;s a protag in&amp;hellip; &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Case in point: look me in the eyes and tell me that Fallout 3, 4, and New Vegas didn&amp;rsquo;t do more to get folks into jazz, lounge, crooner music, and even golden-age country than literally anything else in the past 10 years. You can&amp;rsquo;t. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#004: What Is A Talkie, And What Does It Do?: March 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0004/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0004/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0002/05.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; You might not like it, but this is what peak UI design looks like. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm&#34;&gt;datafruits.fm&lt;/a&gt; for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records. This one will be our programming calendar for the month of March, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to tune in, &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;head on over to datafruits.fm/chat&lt;/a&gt; on Tuesday evenings from 10 PM EST/7 PM PST to 1 AM EST/10 PM PST. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to learn more about the show and read about the fantastic artists and old-time radio shows we&amp;rsquo;re broadcasting this week&amp;hellip;well, read on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, a bit of an interlude&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-talkie-and-what-does-it-do&#34;&gt;WHAT IS A TALKIE, AND WHAT DOES IT DO?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Talkies&amp;rdquo;, as I call them, are basically exactly what it says on the tin&amp;ndash;radio dramas, usually older ones from the 30s, 40s, and 50s. You know how your gramma complains about how people are interrupting her TV stories? Well, take away the TV and add the radio and you&amp;rsquo;ve basically got the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(And yes, I am basically a 75 year old woman trapped in a weird transfemme&amp;rsquo;s body. Now be a good kiddo and fetch me my pipe, Gramgram Sarah&amp;rsquo;s got some stories to tell you.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://otrr.org&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0004/00.png&#34; alt=&#34;OTRR logo&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; These are your FRIENDS, they fight for RADIO. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been in love with radio talk shows for years now. As most of you know (seeing as you&amp;rsquo;re on the website that hosts my studio blog and professional portfolio) I work in professional illustration, specializing in sequential art and storytelling. What that means is that I spend a lot of my time staring at a drawing table making tiny lines on paper, with not a lot of time to watch TV or take my attention elsewhere. I&amp;rsquo;m also a noted advocate for open-source software, and not only have I never had a Spotify account but I&amp;rsquo;ve also never been arsed to check out any &amp;ldquo;podcasts&amp;rdquo; that required me to have a proprietary app or anything of the sort. Hell, for most of my life I&amp;rsquo;ve not even had a smartphone if I can avoid it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This brings us to the magical work of the Old Time Radio Researcher&amp;rsquo;s group. These fine folks find their roots in the old days of tape trading. Back in the day, a lot of the only records of talk shows and those sorts of programs were thanks to home taping and bootleg audio recordings, ripped straight from the air. Eventually, as the years went on, these tape rips gave way to CD rips, then .mp3 files. Thing is, very few of these types of programs had any real classification system&amp;ndash;most folks wrote down the details of the show on the tape box or in a notebook, and everyone recorded them differently. There was also an issue of access&amp;ndash;not a lot of resources were available for the younger generation to enjoy these programs, or even have much of an idea as to what they were listening to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.otrr.org/&#34;&gt;Old Time Radio Researchers, or OTRR for short&lt;/a&gt;, fixed this by doing two things&amp;ndash;compiling their old tapes and uploading them to the Internet Archive for anyone to enjoy, and creating a catalogue of said tapes to make sure everyone had a record of what they were listening to, who it starred, and when it originally aired. I stumbled upon the radio drama collecting hobby through these fine folks a good few years ago, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been collecting recordings and doing my best to spread the word of old-time radio ever since.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll have a few more words next month on the subject, but for now, here&amp;rsquo;s our schedule&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;march-2023-talkie-timejazz-program-schedule&#34;&gt;March 2023 Talkie Time/Jazz Program Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0004/01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Frank Sinatra as Rocky Fortune&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Can you picture this fine gentleman as a professional layabout? ...Yeah, neither can I. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;march-6-2023&#34;&gt;March 6, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--rocky-fortune---the-prize-fight-fix--honor-among-thieves&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : Rocky Fortune - The Prize Fight Fix / Honor Among Thieves&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Francis Albert Sinatra was no stranger to either acting or radio&amp;ndash;the crooner had multiple incarnations of fifteen- to thirty-minute variety programs throughout his career and a good many fantastic films&amp;ndash;but the most interesting of his radio appearances (at least to me) is his role as Rocky Fortune, a frequently unemployed problem solver who shows up and solves crimes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If that seems like a bit of an underwhelming elevator pitch, it is&amp;ndash;to be frank, the most fascinating part of the whole thing is that it stars The Chairman Of The Board as a murder-busting layabout. Slot literally anyone else in that role and you&amp;rsquo;d have had a recipe for middling reviews at best and a stinker at worst. Thankfully for all of us, you can&amp;rsquo;t keep Ol&amp;rsquo; Blue Eyes down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-presents-_first-of-the-month-listener-request-night_--slim-galliard---laughing-in-rhythm-box-set-discs-1-2&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program Presents &lt;em&gt;First Of The Month: Listener Request Night&lt;/em&gt; : Slim Galliard - Laughing in Rhythm (Box Set), Discs 1-2&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve had a decent amount of requests for features since starting this show years ago. In its early days before the single-artist-feature format we do now, I&amp;rsquo;d simply slot in tracks as requested if I could fit them in, but with this new format I&amp;rsquo;ve had to do something a bit different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting this month, the first Tuesday will see the First Of The Month Listener Request Night, where I run a feature on an artist suggested by listeners in the Datafruits chat. This month&amp;rsquo;s inaugural request comes from Datafruits chat member river, with two hours of Slim Galliard&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Laughing In Rhythm&amp;rdquo; multi-disc career-spanning set from Proper Box UK. We&amp;rsquo;ll start with the first two disks and&amp;ndash;who knows?&amp;ndash;maybe play a bit more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;march-13-2023&#34;&gt;March 13, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--mercury-theatres-the-campbell-playhouse---the-murder-of-roger-ackroyd&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : Mercury Theatre&amp;rsquo;s The Campbell Playhouse - The Murder Of Roger Ackroyd&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0004/02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Cover art to Le temps passe&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; One of the most unsettling cover art pieces in all of trip-hop. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On October 30, 1938, Orson Welles and his troupe at the Mercury Theater repertory company broadcast one of the most infamous radio plays ever aired. Their interpretation of H.G. Welle&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The War Of The Worlds&amp;rdquo;, interpreted live on-air as a faux real-world emergency broadcast, was so realistic that the cops got called, multiple small towns went into states of panic, the FCC nearly barred them from the air&amp;ndash;and earned them a sponsorship from the Campbell Soup Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First airing on December 9, 1938, The Campbell Playhouse aired the same kind of programming that made The Mercury Theater On The Air famous, but now with cash flow. A masterclass in foley, radio drama, and narrative adaptation alike, the entire series is absolutely worth a listen. We&amp;rsquo;ll be airing their interpretation of Agatha Christie&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;The Murder of Roger Ackroyd&amp;rsquo; tonight, which originally aired on November 12, 1939.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-zofka---bikini--chocolat--2000-2015-le-temps-passe&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program: Zofka - Bikini / Chocolat / 2000-2015 Le temps passe&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll admit it, I&amp;rsquo;m a sucker for making my audiences listen to whatever I&amp;rsquo;ve been fascinated by at any given moment. I don&amp;rsquo;t mean that as a deterrent, mind&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;d like to think I have decent taste, and part of why I got into radio in the first place is to share what I&amp;rsquo;ve found with all of you. This is very much one of those episodes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of online radio pioneers soma.fm, and often have one of their &amp;ldquo;stations&amp;rdquo; (read: curated playlists by a selection of fantastic DJs) playing while I work. Zofka has at least one track on their &amp;ldquo;Illinois Street Lounge&amp;rdquo; station, and it&amp;rsquo;s that track that sent me down a rabbit hole of trip-hop and nu-jazz. We&amp;rsquo;ll be playing three of their records tonight, including the retrospective &amp;ldquo;2000-2015 Le temps passe&amp;rdquo; which has the dubious honor of having one of the most unsettling pieces of cover art that I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen on a trip-hop record.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;march-20-2023&#34;&gt;March 20, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time--yours-truly-johnny-dollar---the-rat-pack-matter--the-wayward-fireman-matter&#34;&gt;Talkie Time : Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar - The Rat Pack Matter / The Wayward Fireman Matter&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Johnny Dollar is one of the more interesting of the leading men in the radio noir genre for a couple reasons. Not only is he not a PI&amp;ndash;he&amp;rsquo;s an investigator for an insurance company, often going out to investigate &amp;ldquo;accidental deaths&amp;rdquo; and finding them more often than not to be murders&amp;ndash;but he&amp;rsquo;s had more people voice him than nearly any other character in the history of radio noir dramas. You&amp;rsquo;d think that a downside at first glance, but every single actor who takes up the mantle plays the character very well in their own unique way. Tonight, we&amp;rsquo;ll be taking a listen to Bob Readick&amp;rsquo;s version of the wielder of the action-packed expense account, with two cases to die for&amp;ndash;The Rat Pack Matter and The Wayward Fireman Matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-the-grateful-dead-and-ornette-coleman---live-at-oakland-alameda-county-coliseum-22393&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program: The Grateful Dead And Ornette Coleman - Live at Oakland-Alameda County Coliseum, 2/23/93&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Grateful Dead might not be known for their proximity to jazz, but they toured with more than a few jazz legends in their time. Jerry and the crew have shared the stage with the likes of Branford Marsalis (fantastic sax player, brother of Wynton Marsalis, the world-famous trumpeteer, and son of Ellis Marsalis Jr., pianist extrordinare), David Murray (New York based legendary saxophonist), and Charles Lloyd (west-coast based flautist and tenor saxophonist), as well as tonight&amp;rsquo;s feature&amp;ndash;the legendary Ornette Coleman. We&amp;rsquo;ll be playing a live tape from the Oakland-Alameda County Coliseum, a night that featured Ornette opening the show with Jerry joining him onstage later on and Ornette returning the favor near the end of the Dead&amp;rsquo;s set. This set is an absolute must listen for jazz cats and deadheads alike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0004/03.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0004/03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Crime Jazz Season 2 Volume 5 cover art&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; CRIME JAZZ CRIME JAZZ CRIME JAZZ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;march-27-2023&#34;&gt;March 27, 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;talkie-time-cloak-and-dagger---file-2218--the-trojan-horse&#34;&gt;Talkie Time: Cloak And Dagger - File 2218 / The Trojan Horse&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on Corey Ford and Alastair MacBain&amp;rsquo;s 1946 book &amp;ldquo;Cloak and Dagger: The Secret Story of the OSS&amp;rdquo;, Cloak and Dagger has proved a frequent listen while I&amp;rsquo;ve inked away at Our Lady Maven, and it&amp;rsquo;s absolutely worth a listen even for those of you who aren&amp;rsquo;t currently drowning yourself in WWII spy history for work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While claming to be based on fully authenticated case histories of OSS espionage, the series is about as wild as your average pulp from the era. Some language and themes haven&amp;rsquo;t exactly aged well (as with a lot of its ilk and similarly-themed shows from its era up until the 80s&amp;ndash;see also half of James Bond&amp;rsquo;s catalogue) but if you can look past its flaws, it&amp;rsquo;s still an entertaining romp for those of us who love a good spy romp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-jazz-program-presents-_crime-jazz-night_--crime-jazz-volume-2-discs-4-6&#34;&gt;The Jazz Program Presents &lt;em&gt;CRIME JAZZ NIGHT!&lt;/em&gt; : Crime Jazz Volume 2, Discs 4-6&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those in the know, know about Crime Jazz&amp;ndash;both the moniker denoting the weird hodge-podge of genres from lounge to exotica that acompanied the numerous neo-noir and police drama epics that haunted cinemas in the &amp;rsquo;60s and &amp;rsquo;70s, and the now-defunct &lt;a href=&#34;https://thecrimelounge2.blogspot.com/&#34;&gt;series of compilation records hosted on Blogspot and lost due to the demise of Rapidshare.&lt;/a&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re talking about the latter in this case. And if you don&amp;rsquo;t know, we&amp;rsquo;ll be getting you in the know tonight for yet another end-of-the-month installment of Crime Jazz Night. We&amp;rsquo;ll be playing Discs 4-6 of Volume 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s our schedule for this month. Thanks in advance for tuning in; hope you enjoy the show. I&amp;rsquo;ll be back soon with a bit of information about Talkie Time, as well as our schedule for the month of February.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Thanks as always for reading; you&amp;rsquo;re amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not. Talk soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;SARAH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;Footnotes...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and we&amp;rsquo;re playing &amp;ldquo;Blackmail Is Murder&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Death Is No Joke&amp;rdquo; from the 1947 series &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://archive.org/details/OTRR_Box_13_Singles&#34;&gt;Box 13&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; on January 31st. See you then! &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#002: Why Love Jazz? About The Jazz Program and Our February 2023 Programming</title>
      <link>/post/0002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0002/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0002/05.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; You might not like it, but this is what peak UI design looks like. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm&#34;&gt;datafruits.fm&lt;/a&gt; for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. Since finally deleting &lt;a href=&#34;https://i.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/newsfeed/002/245/165/433.gif&#34;&gt;my Twitter account&lt;/a&gt;, however, I&amp;rsquo;ve had a bit of an issue. Usually, I&amp;rsquo;d use Twitter to let listeners know what we&amp;rsquo;d be playing that week, as well as make some dumb jokes and encourage folks to tune in. Since I took the thing out back and shot it, however, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to tune in, &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;head on over to datafruits.fm/chat&lt;/a&gt; on Tuesday evenings from 10 PM EST/7 PM PST to 1 AM EST/10 PM PST. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to learn more about the show and read about the fantastic artists and old-time radio shows we&amp;rsquo;re broadcasting this week&amp;hellip;well, read on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-jazz-program-and-what-does-it-do&#34;&gt;What Is A Jazz Program, And What Does It Do?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obligatory &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/rG6ZgXSMDX4?t=79&#34;&gt;Homestar Runner references aside&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;ldquo;Sarah Allen Reed And The Jazz Program&amp;rdquo; is exactly what it says on the tin&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s an excuse for me (Sarah Allen Reed) to share my love of jazz with all of you fine folks for two hours every Tuesday night. I&amp;rsquo;ve had a love affair with jazz for the majority of my life, and unlike most of my long-term relationships this one has yet to end in a gigantic ball of flame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like most folks with raging, life-altering addictions, I started young. I was raised in various places outside of Saint Louis, MO (a town so attached to jazz that our hockey team is called the Saint Louis Blues) and when I was growing up, I had a choice between two radio stations I was allowed to listen to in the very Christian household I was raised in. One was Joy FM, an absolute garbage fire of a contemporary Christian radio station that eventually &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.timesnewspapers.com/webster-kirkwoodtimes/features/joy-fm-ready-to-make-transition-to-kfuo-fm-classic-99-airwaves/article_c9776bb8-516d-506e-9d0f-9adc3357b32f.html&#34;&gt;bought out and unceremoniously destroyed one of the only independent classical music stations in the contiguous United States&lt;/a&gt;. (I&amp;rsquo;m still mad about that, for the record.) The other was that exact classical music station, which (thanks to some fantastic individuals and an outpouring of community support) &lt;a href=&#34;https://classic1073.org/&#34;&gt;currently exists on the top of the dial in the form of Classic 107.3&lt;/a&gt;. Given the fact that contemporary Christian music is one of exactly two genres of &amp;ldquo;music&amp;rdquo; I consider to be unlistenable (the other being modern country, and both for roughly the same reasons)&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. you can take a guess as to which of the two options I picked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://news.stlpublicradio.org/arts/2015-11-22/obituary-don-wolff-prominent-defense-attorney-known-for-sharing-his-love-of-jazz&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0002/01.png&#34; alt=&#34;The man himself.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; The man himself. RIP. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Granted, if my very religious foster parents were so insistent upon keeping me on the straight and narrow, they prooobably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have let me listen to that one either&amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;Broadway Spotlight&amp;rdquo; was also a weekly fixture on Classic 99, and given the fact that I ate that up every Saturday evening I&amp;rsquo;m honestly shocked that anyone was surprised when I finally came out of the closet.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bring this up for exactly one program&amp;ndash;&lt;a href=&#34;https://news.stlpublicradio.org/arts/2012-10-02/im-don-wolff-and-i-love-jazz&#34;&gt;I Love Jazz by the late and incomparable Don Wolff.&lt;/a&gt; was aired every Friday night, and I tuned in religiously. If there is one reason why I fell in love with the power of radio, it is Classic 99, and Don is 95% of that for me. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have many highlights in my god-awful childhood, but hearing the sentence “I’m Don Wolff, and I love jazz!” and drowning myself in one of the most majestic forms of music known to man was one of the few. To this day, if there&amp;rsquo;s one form of sonic expression that I hold near and dear to my heart more than any, it&amp;rsquo;s jazz, and The Jazz Program is my tribute to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to know more about Talkie Time? Check this blog week when I write a bit about it, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm/shows/the-jazz-program-with-sarah-allen-reed-780922f3-7de0-445e-83bb-6a5188316668&#34;&gt;just tune in!&lt;/a&gt; Until then, let me talk about what we&amp;rsquo;re playing this month and who we&amp;rsquo;re spotlighting:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;february-2023-jazz-program-schedule&#34;&gt;February 2023 Jazz Program Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://www.discogs.com/artist/257623-Houston-Person&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0002/02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Houston Person&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Houston Person. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;january-31-2023---houston-person&#34;&gt;January 31, 2023 - Houston Person&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;in-a-sentimental-mood-the-nearness-of-you-and-my-romance&#34;&gt;In A Sentimental Mood, The Nearness Of You, and My Romance&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day yet? No, because if it was we&amp;rsquo;d be playing J. Dilla. (See below.) No, tonight we&amp;rsquo;re playing three classic albums from soul saxophonist Houston Person, all three of which are guaranteed to get you in a romantic state of mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve got two selections from his time at High Note Records-1998&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/master/721084-Houston-Person-My-Romance&#34;&gt;My Romance&lt;/a&gt; and 2000&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/release/5607748-Houston-Person-In-A-Sentimental-Mood&#34;&gt;In A Sentimental Mood&lt;/a&gt;, and we&amp;rsquo;re closing the evening out with a much funkier record from 1978, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/master/805191-Houston-Person-The-Nearness-Of-You&#34;&gt;The Nearness Of You&lt;/a&gt;, released on Muse Records.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;february-7-2023---django-reinhardt--stéphane-grappelli&#34;&gt;February 7: 2023 - Django Reinhardt &amp;amp; Stéphane Grappelli&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;rome-1949&#34;&gt;Rome, 1949&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve never been privy to the absolute magic that is Django Reinhardt, here&amp;rsquo;s a great place to start. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/release/14329170-Django-Reinhardt-St%C3%A9phane-Grappelli-Rome-1949&#34;&gt;Rome, 1949&lt;/a&gt; is a three-disk set featuring violinist Stéphane Grappelli paired up with the master guitarist over the span of three disks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reinhardt&amp;rsquo;s time in Italy after returning from his time in the States in the late 1940s has a lot of fascinating details that paint a wonderful picture of the man himself&amp;ndash;according to his &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.abebooks.com/book-search/title/django-reinhardt/author/delaunay-charles/&#34;&gt;biography by Charles Delaunay&lt;/a&gt; the guitar master would sometimes show up for scheduled concerts without a guitar or amplifier, or even refuse to show at all, skipping the shows to &amp;ldquo;walk to the beach&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;smell the dew&amp;rdquo;. While you can definitely hear that free spirit in these recordings, we thankfully did in fact get them at all, and they&amp;rsquo;ve been compiled here in this fantastic three-disk set from Label Ouest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;february-14-2023---_valentines-day-booty-bumpin-special_---j-dilla&#34;&gt;February 14, 2023 - &lt;em&gt;Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day Booty Bumpin&amp;rsquo; Special!&lt;/em&gt; - J. Dilla&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;donuts-beats-2002-12-and-ruff-draft-beats&#34;&gt;Donuts, Beats 2002 1&amp;amp;2, and Ruff Draft Beats&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can see some of you thinking J. Dilla is a weird choice for a Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day Special. If you&amp;rsquo;re on that list, remind me to check on your boyfriend and/or girlfriend, as they&amp;rsquo;ve clearly never gotten to experience a decent ending to a Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day date in their life. I feel like someone owes it to them to fix that, and if it ain&amp;rsquo;t gonna be you &lt;em&gt;somebody&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/em&gt; gotta step up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/release/8534979-Katsumi-Horii-Project-Ocean-Drive&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0002/03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Houston Person&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Cover art for &#34;Ocean Drive&#34;, by &lt;a href=&#34;http://gallery.eizin.co.jp/&#34;&gt;Eizin Suzuki.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;J. Dilla is &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; face of the Detroit sound of instrumental production as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned, and you can&amp;rsquo;t get better instrumentals to dance, romance, and take off your pants to. We&amp;rsquo;ll be playing Donuts, Beats 1&amp;amp;2, and Ruff Draft Beats in their entirety, and we&amp;rsquo;re gonna go long into the night. Light some candles, put down the good blanket, and pour some good liquor. We aren&amp;rsquo;t playing love songs this Valentine&amp;rsquo;s day. We&amp;rsquo;re playing &lt;em&gt;lovemaking music, baby.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;february-21-2023---horii-katsumi-project&#34;&gt;February 21, 2023 - Horii Katsumi Project&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hot-is-cool-sky-cruisin-and-ocean-drive&#34;&gt;Hot Is Cool, Sky Cruisin&amp;rsquo;, and Ocean Drive&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it getting warm yet? No? Well, fuck. We&amp;rsquo;ve all been waiting for warm beach weather for the past five months, and while it&amp;rsquo;s not gonna get here any sooner, we can at least play some classic Japanese jazz fusion while we wait for the landlord to fix the hot water heater. &lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll be playing the quintessential 1987 release &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/master/1393045-Katsumi-Horii-Project-%E5%A0%80%E4%BA%95%E5%8B%9D%E7%BE%8EProject-Hot-Is-Cool&#34;&gt;Hot Is Cool&lt;/a&gt;, as well as 1997&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/master/2109667-Horii-Katsumi-Project-Sky-Cruisin&#34;&gt;Sky Cruisin&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt; and 1988&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/master/1266264-Katsumi-Horii-Project-Ocean-Drive&#34;&gt;Ocean Drive&lt;/a&gt;, the latter of which features immaculate cover art by master Japanese illustrator &lt;a href=&#34;http://gallery.eizin.co.jp/&#34;&gt;Eizin Suzuki&lt;/a&gt;. Look at that painting and tell me you don&amp;rsquo;t wish it was summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;february-28-2023---crime-jazz-night&#34;&gt;February 28, 2023 - CRIME JAZZ NIGHT!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;crime-jazz-season-2-vols-1-3&#34;&gt;Crime Jazz Season 2, Vols. 1-3&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0002/04.png&#34; alt=&#34;CRIME JAZZ&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; CRIME JAZZ CRIME JAZZ CRIME JAZZ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those in the know, know about Crime Jazz&amp;ndash;both the moniker denoting the weird hodge-podge of genres from lounge to exotica that acompanied the numerous neo-noir and police drama epics that haunted cinemas in the &amp;rsquo;60s and &amp;rsquo;70s, and the now-defunct &lt;a href=&#34;http://thecrimelounge2.blogspot.com/&#34;&gt;series of compilation records hosted on Blogspot and lost due to the demise of Rapidshare.&lt;/a&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re talking about the latter in this case. Being a relentless archivist, I have been hunting for far, far too long for copies of this series, and at long last I have nearly the entire second &amp;ldquo;season&amp;rdquo; (as they called it) of releases in my posession. Until I run out, we&amp;rsquo;ll be playing these fantastic records in their entirety on the last Tuesday of every month. So far, I&amp;rsquo;ve only tracked down the second season&amp;ndash;if you have the first, email me at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sarah@sarahallenreed.com&#34;&gt;sarah@sarahallenreed.com&lt;/a&gt; and send me some download links and I will personally buy you a beer (or coffee).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s our schedule for this month. Thanks in advance for tuning in; hope you enjoy the show. I&amp;rsquo;ll be back soon with a bit of information about Talkie Time, as well as our schedule for the month of February.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Thanks as always for reading; you&amp;rsquo;re amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not. Talk soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;SARAH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;Footnotes...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have class, dammit. If I wanted to listen to thinly veiled propaganda, I&amp;rsquo;d just listen to the 1812 Overture like a functioning individual. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4C-YSq5flow&#34;&gt;Besides, at least Tchaikovsky knows how to put together a melody.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seriously, if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, please send maintenance in here and fix the thing. It&amp;rsquo;s been out for like two weeks now and I can only take so many cold showers before I turn into a raisin. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and we&amp;rsquo;re playing &amp;ldquo;Blackmail Is Murder&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Death Is No Joke&amp;rdquo; from the 1947 series &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://archive.org/details/OTRR_Box_13_Singles&#34;&gt;Box 13&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; on January 31st. See you then! &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

