<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>open source on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/open-source/</link>
    <description>Recent content in open source on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Sarah Allen Reed.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#005: Apparently I&#39;ve Been Banned From Instagram</title>
      <link>/post/0005/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0005/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Quick note - as of me editing this post on March 15, my Instagram account has been reinstated. I&amp;rsquo;m still going to actively avoid using it unless necessary, as I stated in this post, and I&amp;rsquo;ve also added &amp;ldquo;Share To&amp;rdquo; buttons to these blog pages and to the galleries if you wish to show off my work to some folks or talk about what I have to say on this blog. Either way, I appreciate you all reading, as usual. You&amp;rsquo;re amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not, as always. On with the post&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0005/01.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0005/01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Instagram&#39;s ban notice.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; weeeeeeee &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, uh. yeah. Sup, y&amp;rsquo;all. Title says it all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m no stranger to getting in trouble. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent half my life getting in trouble. Hell, to a lot of people I &lt;em&gt;am&lt;/em&gt; trouble. That&amp;rsquo;s kind of half the reason I ended up in this field to begin with&amp;ndash;as I&amp;rsquo;ve stated in interviews before, there was a point in time where being a minor menace to society was a prerequisite to this profession and no one notified me when that switched to needing to be an advertiser-friendly influencer.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, usually I know what I did and I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly shy about owning up to it if I feel particularly bad about it or telling you to get bent if I don&amp;rsquo;t. And in this case, I&amp;rsquo;ve got nothing. I just hit the &amp;ldquo;post&amp;rdquo; button to put some new art up I was working on, and I got hit with a fun little message telling me my account was &amp;ldquo;disabled&amp;rdquo; and was pending a &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo; to even get reinstated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I ain&amp;rsquo;t gonna lie here, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have no idea why I got hit with this.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My best guess&amp;ndash;if I could even approach a guess&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;ndash;is one of two options. One, I have not had what anyone could consider a functional smartphone in months. I always post from their meagerly-featured web client when I have to post, and I don&amp;rsquo;t have &lt;em&gt;The App&lt;/em&gt; anywhere. I keep a &lt;a href=&#34;https://lineageos.org/&#34;&gt;LineageOS&lt;/a&gt; device around that I often forget to pay the bill on for two-factor authentication, taking photos of my work, and other such nonsense, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t leave the house. I also have a flip phone so the few people who would actually be worried if I disappeared into the woods can know vaguely where I am. That&amp;rsquo;s it. I don&amp;rsquo;t have the Google Play store on a device that isn&amp;rsquo;t kept either off or in a Faraday cage, which is why the fun last request at the end of multiple 2FA verifications to let Instagram determine whether I&amp;rsquo;m human enough for their standards kind of unsettled the fuck out of me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0005/02.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0005/02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Instagram&#39;s ban notice.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; We&#39;re in the bad web now, kids &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be honest, there was like 30 minutes where I just kind of considered letting it die and not bothering. I don&amp;rsquo;t exactly think I&amp;rsquo;m off center for not particularly wanting to participate in what some police offices consider standard booking procedure to prove to Mr. Metaverse that I&amp;rsquo;m not a fuckin&amp;rsquo; robot, especially since I&amp;rsquo;m fairly certain that it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly off-key to assume they just want more pictures of human faces for their own AI bots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Which brings me to the second and only other reason I can think of that I might have gotten banned: I have a habit of telling the numerous spambots that accost my feed to blow it out their ass, and there&amp;rsquo;s a distinct possibility that one of the scammers-with-a-thousand-faces decided to mass report me for either profanity or impersonation.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did hold the Metaverse&amp;rsquo;s version of a mug shot booking card with my middle and index finger so that I could flip the camera off in the selfie, so while I probably am not getting the account back I am at least getting the last jab in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be frank, I probably won&amp;rsquo;t return to mainstream social media even if my Instagram account gets reinstated. I know that fucks me as far as my work and livelihood goes, but I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s worth the cost on my psyche. I cold-turkeyed Twitter after Musk took over, even though half the industry seems to only put open calls for work on that website despite the site&amp;rsquo;s open hostility to nearly every single marginalized group, including and especially trans folk.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; My time on Twitter was mostly spent watching other creators constantly cannibalize each other and undermine each other in the fight for eyeballs, and it got to a point where that was not how I wanted to do this anymore. Musk letting the alt-right kids back on in droves kind of gave me the excuse to cut the cord. The plan was to eventually yeet Instagram as well once I had a decent foothold on getting this blog loaded up with things to read, but it looks like that decision has been made for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And yes, I do know that my account is &amp;ldquo;pending review&amp;rdquo;, but given the fact that the bit of research I&amp;rsquo;ve done seems to have given an answer of &amp;ldquo;a week to never&amp;rdquo; as to when I&amp;rsquo;ll have access to it, I&amp;rsquo;m going to behave as if it is permanently 86&amp;rsquo;d. If it &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; get re-instated, I&amp;rsquo;ll use it to let folks know when I have a new blog post up, but the pandemic was the last &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.catb.org/jargon/html/S/September-that-never-ended.html&#34;&gt;variation upon a theme of the Eternal September&lt;/a&gt; that I have the patience to deal with in my lifetime, at least directly. I have joined a couple smaller social networks that specifically cater to illustrators, and when I have my account set up there I&amp;rsquo;ll probably share them here and add a &amp;ldquo;social&amp;rdquo; section to the navbar to hold them all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0005/03.gif&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0005/03.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Email Me gif from the golden age of Geocities.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Take it back to the good old days of the good web, baby. (Gif sourced from &lt;a href=&#34;https://gifcities.org&#34;&gt;Gifcities.&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m also most likely going to add some &amp;ldquo;Share to $OPEN_SOURCE_FORUM&amp;rdquo;-type button to the blog posts in the future when I can be bothered to work them into the code, and if I can find a way to do so that won&amp;rsquo;t end up with me getting bombarded with either spam or transphobic slurs I might add a comment section. I do want my work to be shared with those who want to read it, but to be honest I don&amp;rsquo;t want to hear from folks who want to use the comment section to willfully misinterpret what I have to say at best or insult me or try and sell me something at worst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, you can find me on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pillowfort.social/sarahallenreed&#34;&gt;Pillowfort&lt;/a&gt;, a comfy old-school Tumblr clone with no NSFW ban, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://cohost.org/sarahallenreed&#34;&gt;Cohost&lt;/a&gt;, a microblogging platform with about the same vibe. As of the time of pushing this article to the server, I don&amp;rsquo;t have any content on either yet, but I will soon. &lt;del&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not particularly sure about whether or not I&amp;rsquo;m going to join Mastodon, but I will be adding a &amp;ldquo;Share on Mastodon&amp;rdquo; button to the blog soon enough.&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minor editor&amp;rsquo;s note&amp;ndash;I found out that Rusty Hodge, the guy who founded Soma.FM and a large part of why I got into DJing on internet radio in the first place, hangs out on DEF CON&amp;rsquo;S Mastodon server. I also found out that DEF CON has a server, which in and of itself is tight as hell. So yeah, I kind of caved in and joined Mastodon. &lt;a href=&#34;https://defcon.social/@sarahallenreed&#34;&gt;You can find me on defcon.social here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, I&amp;rsquo;m kind of leaning towards the model I have already kind of put forth here&amp;ndash;if you enjoy my work and want to interact with me about it, &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sarah@sarahallenreed.com&#34;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/bio/&#34;&gt;send something to the PO box&lt;/a&gt;, or simply find me at a convention or when I&amp;rsquo;m having a book signing or something. I love hearing from all of you and listening to your reactions to my work, but to be quite frank I would rather talk &lt;em&gt;with&lt;/em&gt; you all about it than have what we&amp;rsquo;re talking about get muddied in the shallowness of a walled garden&amp;rsquo;s comment section. If I get emails with particularly interesting questions which I want to make sure to respond to, I&amp;rsquo;ll definitely toss them into a &amp;ldquo;letterbag&amp;rdquo; section on this blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My work is how I communicate and interact with the world around me. It seems a fool&amp;rsquo;s game to limit your ability to communicate back to two hundred and fourty characters, especially with algorithms that monetize constantly pitting us all against each other. Time will tell how badly this fucks my career up, but for now, I suppose my move is not to play. Let&amp;rsquo;s hope it&amp;rsquo;s at least a somewhat winning one in the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Either way, I appreciate having all of you along for the ride. You&amp;rsquo;re all amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not. Talk soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash; SARAH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have multiple rants on why and how that entire switch was an awful move for both the medium and the majority of interesting creators, but that&amp;rsquo;s another rant for another time. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure I &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; approach a guess, to be honest. These algorithms don&amp;rsquo;t seem to have a thought process that falls in the realm of any kind of reasoning I&amp;rsquo;d consider human. And no, I don&amp;rsquo;t consider capitalist &amp;ldquo;growth mindset&amp;rdquo; nonsense or the walled-prison-type designs commonplace in the modern Web a part of any kind of reasoning I&amp;rsquo;d consider human. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire concept of &lt;a href=&#34;https://pitchwars.org/pitmad/&#34;&gt;Pitmad&lt;/a&gt; and half the links on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.creatoradvisor.com/category/job-postings/&#34;&gt;Comic Book Resources&lt;/a&gt; are some fairly decent examples of my point here. I&amp;rsquo;m not linking them here because I don&amp;rsquo;t like the job they&amp;rsquo;re doing&amp;ndash;all of the people running these are fantastic individuals, to the best of my knowledge/interactions with them&amp;ndash;but rather to illustrate this point. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#001: A Fresh Start, Old Computers, and a New Coat Of Paint</title>
      <link>/post/0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0001/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey, y&amp;rsquo;all. As you&amp;rsquo;ve most likely noticed, 2022 was&amp;hellip;.well, not a good year for social media. Twitter&amp;rsquo;s on fire, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s been under federal scrutiny for years now, and seeing as I don&amp;rsquo;t have a face for anything but radio, I&amp;rsquo;ve never bothered with Tiktok.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, now that I&amp;rsquo;ve finally updated my website again, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to just go back to basics and start a little blog here instead. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been more long-winded than most social media sites want me to be as it is, and this kind of format gives me more of an opportunity to write a bit about things I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t normally get the chance to talk about otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been putting off updating my website for over a year and some change now. 2022 wasn&amp;rsquo;t exactly my year, and even if I had the energy to do it then, I&amp;rsquo;ve been so unreasonably busy that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have had the time. But now I&amp;rsquo;ve got more than enough time, and so in the interest of ensuring that I&amp;rsquo;m not constrained to the character limit of Twitter or the weird &amp;ldquo;photo not posted!&amp;rdquo; behavior that Instagram gets every single time I write a caption that contains phrases like &amp;ldquo;trans rights&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;nazis have no place in modern society&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;fuck&amp;rdquo;, I&amp;rsquo;m going to do what a lot of other artists are doing and go back to longer-form writing here &lt;em&gt;ye olde web 1.0 style&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It didn&amp;rsquo;t take long for me to think of an opening salvo, either. Seeing as I&amp;rsquo;ve been happily plunking away on this computer terminal working on this codebase for half a month, I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a better (or more stereotypically trans) topic to start with than my perpetual aesthetic obsession with my Linux desktop and open-source software, especially in an industry that isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly known for going open source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-hardware&#34;&gt;The Hardware&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0001/setup1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0001/setup1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Eiffel tower&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Screenshot of the website in progress. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a good portion of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve used Linux for the vast majority of my creative career. Given the fact that I do professional illustration, audio work, and creative work in general for a living, that&amp;rsquo;s not what you&amp;rsquo;d call a &amp;ldquo;typical&amp;rdquo; choice. Linux has a bad rap for being what most creative professionals would refer to as &amp;ldquo;functionally unusable&amp;rdquo; (and for good reason, especially in the professional audio space). I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved in free and open source software since I was a teenager, however, and at this point I can&amp;rsquo;t really imagine using anything else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s quite a few reasons I use free, libre, and open-source software (or FLOSS, for short) in nearly every applicable scenario I can (and tend towards using abandonware and old software when I can&amp;rsquo;t)&amp;ndash;it aligns with a good percentage of my principles and way of being in the world, I appreciate the freedom to cusomize and tinker, I can&amp;rsquo;t stand rent-seeking behavior in corporations that like to clamp down monopolies on certain industries (especially creative fields), etc., etc., ad infinitum. With that stated, there is a fairly importing contributing factor as for why I got into Linux in the first place: I&amp;rsquo;m poor as all get out, and always have been. Linux is a lot of things to a lot of people, but for me it has one thing that has always set it above the rest&amp;ndash;free as in freedom. I got into Linux back in the days when I couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford a computer that can run anything else. The vast majority of my early career saw me too poor to afford anything even remotely close to cutting edge, and so I just grabbed whatever computer I could find, slapped Linux on it, and made the little bastard do what I needed it to do. And to this day, I&amp;rsquo;ve been happily doing the same thing with all my computers ever since.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
      &lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0001/setup3.png&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0001/setup3.png&#34; alt=&#34;Eiffel tower&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; My current IDE, vscodium (a telemetry-free, open source fork of Visual Studio Code). Also shown is the equivalent of my &#34;start menu&#34;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/davatorium/rofi&#34;&gt;rofi&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point in history, it&amp;rsquo;s fairly easy to get your hands on a relatively usable thin-client (like the Lenovo Thinkcentre M93p I&amp;rsquo;m using here) and it&amp;rsquo;s also easier than ever to customize whichever distro you&amp;rsquo;re using to get it to behave exactly how you want, or just to pick and download a free and open-source distribution of Linux tailor-made to audio production or graphics and bonk it over the head to function however you want. With companies like Adobe having a reputation for needlessly screwing over their customers at any given opportunity and other companies that were, at one point, &amp;ldquo;better about that&amp;rdquo; going much the same way, there&amp;rsquo;ll probably be fewer better times to switch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t use a stock distribution. Never really have. What you&amp;rsquo;re seeing here is a borderline &lt;a href=&#34;https://old.reddit.com/r/unixporn&#34;&gt;/r/unixporn&lt;/a&gt;-ready power user workstation, beaten into the ground and painted in a nice patina of trans- and femboy-pride colors. (Just like this website, &lt;a href=&#34;https://variant-archive.tumblr.com/post/179097473122/femboy-pride-flag&#34;&gt;if you didn&amp;rsquo;t catch the intentional color scheme choices&lt;/a&gt;.) That&amp;rsquo;s not a purely stylistic choice (although I do have a fondness for the artistic merit of a finely tuned-workstation) as much as it is force of habit. For the longest time, all I had to work with and create work with were 10-15 year old laptops, and if you&amp;rsquo;ve ever had to get a crotchety old crank like a IBM T60 humming again, you&amp;rsquo;ll know that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing that can do the job quite like a minimalistic desktop environment and using nothing but command-line apps for every task you can squeeze into a &lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/rxvt-unicode&#34;&gt;urxvt&lt;/a&gt; window.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to do much of that sort of thing anymore (although I do keep my old Thinkpads very close to my heart, &lt;a href=&#34;/resume/bio&#34;&gt;as you can see in my author photo in the &amp;ldquo;about me&amp;rdquo; page on this website&lt;/a&gt;&amp;ndash;that lil&amp;rsquo; guy there is my beloved Thinkpad X60, Conseil.) and can use the full range of what modern open-source software has to offer to my advantage. I currently run two different computers for 90% of my production; a Lenovo Thinkpad P90 (named after my beloved Piranese mix, Polyhymnia) that sits just above my drawing board that I use for listening to radio shows, podcasts, and Let&amp;rsquo;s Plays while I work on inks (and which hooks directly down into my oversized scanner and an ancient screenless Wacom tablet in case I need to do digital touch-up or color work on whichever piece I&amp;rsquo;m working on) and this little old guy here, Herotodus (named after the ancient Greek historian).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
      &lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0001/setup4.png&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0001/setup4.png&#34; alt=&#34;Eiffel tower&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; The ol&#39; battlestation. Herotodus (the computer) sitting on Goliath (the secretary desk), ready for action. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it involves me having to do some writing in any form, be it research for a new book, bullet journalling, hacking away on the website or other development projects, working with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zettelkasten&#34;&gt;index card catalogue that I use in lieu of a functioning memory&lt;/a&gt;, or even reading a bit, Herodotus and Goliath (the secretary desk she sits on) is the dynamic duo I turn to. I&amp;rsquo;ve also managed to do quite a bit with Winetricks to get some of my favorite classic games running, so you can often catch me in the mornings in the studio playing a hand of Cribbage or Spades or running through some old text adventure games as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The nice thing about a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thin_client&#34;&gt;thin client&lt;/a&gt; is that you can fit the little guys damn near anywhere&amp;ndash;in a drawer, wedged between some books, mounted underneath the desk, or really anywhere you can think of that you can pipe some cords out of. I can&amp;rsquo;t look you in the eye and tell you that I&amp;rsquo;m a strict observer of the teachings of the Church of Cable Management, but I am someone who believes in doing the equivalent of &amp;ldquo;going on Christmas and Easter to see Grampa and take a family photo in the name of keeping up appearances&amp;rdquo;. Some rubber bands, a bit of &amp;ldquo;shove the cables in back of stuff&amp;rdquo; and the old &amp;ldquo;wrap the cords around the monitor&amp;rdquo; trick are more than enough for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Herotodus is hooked into an old-school 4:5 aspect ratio monitor I snagged from an old job I worked at. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s neurodiverse impulse, writer&amp;rsquo;s habit &lt;em&gt;a la&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jeremyutley.design/blog/the-daily-discipline&#34;&gt;Jerry Seinfeld&amp;rsquo;s old &amp;ldquo;yellow legal pads&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;, or just plain old aesthetics, but I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to function with anything involving getting words or code down if I&amp;rsquo;m not typing it out on a clicky keyboard and seeing it displayed on a 4:3 or similar aspect ratio monitor. 16:9 doesn&amp;rsquo;t do it for me, for some reason. I&amp;rsquo;ve had my fair share of CRTs as well over the years&amp;ndash;they&amp;rsquo;re just easier on the eyes, at least for me&amp;ndash;but not only will one not fit on top of Goliath at any viewable angle but the only one I have currently seems to have burnt out. (Quite frankly, I&amp;rsquo;d use my ancient Brother WP-3550 as a daily driver if I could&amp;ndash;but that&amp;rsquo;s a topic for when I inevitably get around to spending a post opining about my typewriter and word processor collection.) This ancient HP 1755 does its job though, and I do love its side-mounted USB ports for transferring files and what-not, as well as its sturdiness. The old girl&amp;rsquo;s built like a tank. I&amp;rsquo;ve always admired that in a lady.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-desktop&#34;&gt;The Desktop&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
      &lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0001/setup5.png&#34;&gt;
      &lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0001/setup5.png&#34; alt=&#34;Eiffel tower&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
  My favorite Monday morning pasttime, Sierra Online&#39;s &#34;Hoyle Card Games 2005&#34;, running through &lt;a href=&#34;https://winehq.org&#34;&gt;Wine.&lt;/a&gt; Yes, you can have your table partner be a giant grizzly bear. Yes, he talks. His name is Harley. No, I&#39;m not happy about this hand either.
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As far as software goes, I use a plethora of open-source software in my daily workflow. The entire system itself is a weird frankenstein monster of piping &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Airblader/i3&#34;&gt;i3gaps&lt;/a&gt; through &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.xfce.org/&#34;&gt;XFCE&lt;/a&gt;&amp;ndash;you can check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://feeblenerd.blogspot.com/2015/11/pretty-i3-with-xfce.html&#34;&gt;The Feeble Nerd&amp;rsquo;s post on the subject&lt;/a&gt; if you want to know how to set that up&amp;ndash;with a good amount of UI/UX customizations as well. Me being the absolute fruit I am (and also prone to headaches when confronted with any color emanating from a screen writ large that isn&amp;rsquo;t a variation upon a theme of black or grey), I&amp;rsquo;ve customized almost the entire thing in the pinkest and purplest colors I can find and installed a bunch of plugins and custom themes to ensure I never have to deal with &amp;ldquo;light-mode&amp;rdquo; anything if I can avoid it. At some point, I&amp;rsquo;ll probably clean up and upload my config files to my &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sarahallenreed&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; so anyone who&amp;rsquo;s interested can clone them and customize them to their liking; if that happens, I&amp;rsquo;ll link it here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For practical software, I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://gimp.org&#34;&gt;GIMP&lt;/a&gt; for graphics editing and tinkering with larger UI elements, &lt;a href=&#34;https://vscodium.com/&#34;&gt;VS Codium&lt;/a&gt; with a Vim emulation plugin for programming and other code manangement work (although &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.blog/2022-06-08-sunsetting-atom/&#34;&gt;I used Atom until the crooks bought out Github and sunsetted the poor thing&lt;/a&gt;; RIP to the best IDE I&amp;rsquo;ve ever used), &lt;a href=&#34;https://novelwriter.io/&#34;&gt;novelwriter&lt;/a&gt; for long-form document editing and planning (i.e. graphic novels, games, and other things that require keeping track of characters, settings, and concepts) &lt;a href=&#34;https://ghostwriter.kde.org/&#34;&gt;ghostwriter&lt;/a&gt; for shorter-form Markdown pieces (like this blog here!) and a few other odds and ends here and there for other workflow-related things. I also use &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.winehq.org/&#34;&gt;Wine&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dosbox.com/&#34;&gt;DosBox&lt;/a&gt; to emulate old PC games, &lt;a href=&#34;https://mednafen.github.io/&#34;&gt;Mednafen&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.carpeludum.com/kega-fusion/&#34;&gt;Kega-Fusion&lt;/a&gt;, and a couple other emulators for console games, and I do play a fair amount of Linux games as well. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pysolfc.sourceforge.io/&#34;&gt;PySolFC&lt;/a&gt; is a perennial favorite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re moving studios (and states!) in a few months here, and while I&amp;rsquo;m not looking forward to carting an entire secretary desk and an army of computers, typewriters, and sundry halfway across the country for the umpteenth time, I can&amp;rsquo;t honestly imagine studio life without them. (Plus, I need the typewriters to give you folks half the lettering that shows up in &lt;a href=&#34;https://ourladymaven.com/&#34;&gt;Our Lady Maven!&lt;/a&gt; It just wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the same if I used a font&amp;hellip;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how often I&amp;rsquo;ll be updating this blog, but seeing as I don&amp;rsquo;t have Twitter anymore (which means I don&amp;rsquo;t have many other outlets to talk about games, books, and records I&amp;rsquo;ve been fascinated by in the studio), I can&amp;rsquo;t look you in the eye and tell you I&amp;rsquo;m completely invested in keeping Instagram around, and after years of having to use social media as a professional in this industry I&amp;rsquo;ve been burnt out to all hell on the entire concept, this is more or less going to be what I use to keep y&amp;rsquo;all updated.
A large part of my struggle over the past couple years has been balancing the need for a &amp;ldquo;professional freelance illustrator branding&amp;rdquo; with the part of me that genuinely loves and wants to talk about creative pursuits, weird inspirations, and the troubles, tribulations, and triumphs of life that inspire a lot of my work in an honest and genuine manner. I&amp;rsquo;ve gone through a lot of different thoughts on how to tackle that problem, but this is probably gonna be how I do that, and I&amp;rsquo;ll try and update it at least a couple times a month to let y&amp;rsquo;all know what I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on, what I&amp;rsquo;ve been enraptured in, and what I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You definitely don&amp;rsquo;t have to read every single post on here if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to, but hopefully this will be a nice little window into the life and thought process of the giant dork who pens and voices what (I&amp;rsquo;d hope) are some of your favorite comics, books, and radio shows. If you want to get ahold of me to ask some questions about whatever it is I wrote about, request a topic for me to write a bit about (ask me about bits of my artistic process, for instance) or just send me a letter, you can check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/bio&#34;&gt;my current mailing and email address over on the About Me page on my portfolio site.&lt;/a&gt;. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll do a lil&amp;rsquo; letter column if I get enough mail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re all amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not. Talk soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;SARAH&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

