<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Sarah Allen Reed.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 14 - Went Out Shootin&#39;, December 24, 2023</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll14/</guid>
      <description>Autumn █████████ and I went out on Christmas Eve to get both of us out of our heads a bit and for me to go shooting. Here&#39;s a little sample of what Imogen and I shot today. All of these were edited with Darktable on Linux Mint.
 
 Some pretty goosies.   
 the gooses are on the looses!  
 Keeping watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#020: Now I Have A Jazz Program, Ho-Ho-Ho - December 2023 Radio Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0020/</guid>
      <description>pictured: your face when you realize exactly how incredible the programming is on tuesday nights on datafruits dot eff emm
 Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 13 - Scenes From The Studio - November 2023</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll13/</guid>
      <description>November 2 
 November 2nd is [Prey Day](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deadly_Prey), of course, so that narrows down today&#39;s background noise material.  
 The task was to do as much as I could to update the blog. I didn&#39;t get as much done as I&#39;d like, but progress is progress.   
 The drawing board covered in last month&#39;s completed pages.  
 Also, today I tried to take a photo of Polly with Imogen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 12 - Mister Pliskin Presents New Rekkids Day, December 2023</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll12/</guid>
      <description>Mister Pliskin sez it&#39;s new rekkids day.  
 What&#39;s in the baggie? Who can say!   
 Let&#39;s take a gander, shall we?  
 First up: my third favorite Yes record, 90125.  I used to have this one (and Fragile, my second favorite Yes record) on cassette years back when i owned a shitty Toyota Corolla with a tape deck. I&#39;ve been looking for a replacement copy ever since, and while this isn&#39;t exactly a cassette I&#39;m glad to finally have it in the collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#019: Stuffy Turkeys And Jive Tofurkeys - November 2023 Radio Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0019/</guid>
      <description>IN A NOT TOO DISTANT HOLIDAY, NEXT THURSDAY AD!
 Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 11 - Jazzy Fuckin&#39; Holidays 2023 Poster Process</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll11/</guid>
      <description>Drafting, Pencilling, and Inking 
 Starting in on pencils. The lettering and all that was done (as always) on graph paper and glued up as I went; for a more in-depth look at how I do that, check out this process thread.  
 Here&#39;s the rest of the lettering, glued up and into place.  
 Starting in on inks.  
 Two passes later. I was originally going to black the entire poster&#39;s background out, but I decided to sketch in some variations in tone for the sky and trees as opposed to simply a blacked-out sky covered in snow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 10 - Meet Navi!</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll10/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s the baby! Shown here with Vim and Nerdtree, with a tin of Bengal Slices and one of my many pipes.  
 Here&#39;s some screenshots of my original setup, starting with Vim with Startify.   
 Dosbox with Frederick Pohl&#39;s Gateway.  
 Liferea. Due to the Pinephone&#39;s smaller screen, this isn&#39;t the *best* solution for RSS feeds, but I&#39;ve yet to find a CLI one I like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 09 - Scenes From The Studio - Datafruits World Expo Poster</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll09/</guid>
      <description>Initial pencils and lettering.  
 Starting in on inking.   
 First and second pass of inks down. I wanna point out here that the lil&#39; guy there in the witch&#39;s hand was designed by Datafruits&#39; own Zaxy. His name is Beamsprout, if you were curious.  
 As with nearly everything else, I&#39;m doing the lettering by hand.
 
 Inking the lettering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 08 - Polyhymnia Bein&#39; Cute, Part 2</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll08/</guid>
      <description>Polyhymnia was supposed to be a service dog for my autism and PTSD, but the training she was supposed to get never actually happened. So now she&amp;rsquo;s just my favorite dumbass who tries her best. Here&amp;rsquo;s yet another gallery worth of cute photos of her over the years.
 
 hey, how ya doin&#39;  
 lik lik lik. One of the last photos of her in our old apartment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 07 - Meet Imogen!</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll07/</guid>
      <description>Falling down a rabbit hole. Most of these suggestions came from my good buddy Miranda Thomas, who thankfully and helpfully suggested KEH as a reputable used reseller. Which is good, because I sure don&#39;t have new-camera money.
 
 Mama (me) and the baby! Imogen is named after Imogen Cunningham, if anyone was wondering.  
 A glamour shot, taken with my old Oneplus 7 Pro that I&#39;ve used for the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 06 - Scenes From The Studio - October 2023</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll06/</guid>
      <description>September 30, 2023 
 Whole bunch of lettering bubbles and a lit, bubbling hookah. Not the worst way to start a work session.
 
 Watching Kiko roll through Stonekeep and reading through the Our Lady Maven script.   
 Pencils down on the first panel on page 4.  
 Some early drafts for potential cover art for an upcoming project.
 October 15, 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#018: It&#39;s Spooky Jazz Season, Bitches: The October 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0018/</guid>
      <description>Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#017: Studio News: Summer 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0017/</guid>
      <description>Hey ya&amp;rsquo;ll! As you know, it&amp;rsquo;s been a good minute since I&amp;rsquo;ve had the time to sit down and write a full-on Studio Update. We&amp;rsquo;re finally settled in&amp;ndash;mostly&amp;ndash;in the new studio1, and I wanted to check in and let y&amp;rsquo;all know what&amp;rsquo;s coming down the pike, what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to, and where I&amp;rsquo;m planning on heading next.
 WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WORKING ON OUR LADY MAVEN 
Issue 2 on the drawing board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 05 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 2, Part 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll05/</guid>
      <description>Part one of a series of progress photo galleries of me working through Our Lady Maven, Issue 2.
 
 Hand-lettering, as usual. It&#39;s how we do it here.  
 Pencilling in a facsimile of the Chicago skyline.   
 Roughing in the other two panels.  
 Blocking in the kids with some more rough pencils. I&#39;m using a General&#39;s carpenter&#39;s pencil here to scratch in some shading to mark where I&#39;m going to put some thick swatches of black ink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 04 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 2</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll04/</guid>
      <description>Part two of two sets of progress photos of me working my way through the concept art for The Garden.
 
 Initial pencils for the concept art for Kaia here.  
 Pencilling in the adults....  
 ...and the other kiddos.  
 Adding in some inks on the concept art of the adults. 
 
 Inked kiddos. Karina, Penny, and Bobbie on the top, and a full sheet of Kaia on the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#016 : The Jazz Program Drifts By The Window: The September 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0016/</guid>
      <description>Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#015: Leave A Message After The Jazz: (A Posthumous) August 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0015/</guid>
      <description>Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#014: We Couldn&#39;t Jazz Up A Title: July 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0014/</guid>
      <description>Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#013: : Mama Sarah Shows You How To Cook Shit: Hick Ass Vegan Saag Paneer</title>
      <link>/post/0013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0013/</guid>
      <description>this better not be another cock, mervin  Welcome to How To Cook Shit, a new segment here on the blog where I, for some reason, insist upon sharing some of my favorite recipes with you all. This is my website, though, so you&amp;rsquo;re all going to have to make do.
I spent way too much time in professional kitchens in my twenties when I couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite pay the bills with my work, and I&amp;rsquo;ve joked constantly about quitting comics forever and opening up a little diner if one of my books ever makes it anywhere near profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 03 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll03/</guid>
      <description>Part one of two sets of progress photos of me working my way through the concept art for The Garden.
 
 The initial pencils for the concept art image. I hid [Gnome Chompski](https://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Garden_Gnome) in there somewhere--see if you can find &#39;im!  
 Starting in on inks, going section by section.  
 Layer layer layer  
 Most of the sections are filled in now; only a few more adjustments then it&#39;s digitization time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#012: : Jazz Is A Many-Splendoured Thing: June 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0012/</guid>
      <description>Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#011: The Finer Things, April &amp; May 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0011/</guid>
      <description>HahaahaAHAAHAA fuck this is late
I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy. As much as I&amp;rsquo;d like to, I&amp;rsquo;ve not had much time to pen a long column about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to in my spare time, much less had much spare time to spend. Snakes, Barren, and a couple other upcoming projects have kind of monopolized most of my attention, and I&amp;rsquo;m a bit late on having a second to sit down and write about fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#010: : Much Ado About Cassette Tapes: May 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0010/</guid>
      <description>Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#009: Stone Jaw: Trans Healthcare And Other Cognitohazards</title>
      <link>/post/0009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0009/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve honestly hesitated to write about this topic; it&amp;rsquo;s a personal one that&amp;rsquo;s heavy even by my standards, and on top of that it&amp;rsquo;s not an easy thing to talk about. With that stated, it has kind of colored my output (when it hasn&amp;rsquo;t outright prevented me from creating work at all) for the past few years, and to be quite frank I&amp;rsquo;m going to end up covering it (or aspects of it) in one of my upcoming books anyways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 02 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll02/</guid>
      <description>Some in-progress photos of me working my way through Our Lady Maven Issue 1.
 
 Inking panels from the comic.  
 Full art for Page 8.  
 Close up inks. You can see the ink smudges from the typewriter real well here.  
 Probably my favorite panel. 
 
 Sneaking in an overt homage to one of my favorite adventure game detectives</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#008: Studio News: March &amp; April 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0008/</guid>
      <description>Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bit of a longer segment this month, so I&amp;rsquo;m breaking my &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo; into two segments; &amp;ldquo;Studio News&amp;rdquo;, where I talk about the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to and what I&amp;rsquo;ve got in the pipeline, and &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo;, where I talk a bit about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to, watching, reading, playing, and smoking.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also got a bit of a long, introspective topic to talk about, but that&amp;rsquo;s getting lopped into its own post as well; it&amp;rsquo;s heavy enough for one of my books, which means that I&amp;rsquo;d rather put it in its own little column instead of putting it in with the lighter things I usually talk about on this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#007: An Old Interview (or, A Time Capsule To 2019 Sarah)</title>
      <link>/post/0007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0007/</guid>
      <description>What is this, exactly? While going through some old files on an old shared network drive trying to track down an old script I&amp;rsquo;m working on re-writing, I found this series of interview answers that I gave for a blog that wanted to interview me.
If that seems a strange way of doing things, it kind of is. It&amp;rsquo;s also more or less the norm on a lot of journalistic outlets nowadays, especially those that cater to small press books and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 01 - Polyhymnia, Emotional Support Dumbass</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll01/</guid>
      <description>Polyhymnia was supposed to be a service dog for my autism and PTSD, but the training she was supposed to get never actually happened. So now she&amp;rsquo;s just my favorite dumbass who tries her best. Here&amp;rsquo;s some cute photos of her over the years.
 
 Baby Poly  
 Not-quite-baby Poly, sunnin&#39; on my old sofa.   
 OH LAWD SHE TONGUE
 
 &amp;quot;Look mom, I can DJ too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#006: Adventures In Thrift Store Tape Hunting: April 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0006/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0006/</guid>
      <description>Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#005: Apparently I&#39;ve Been Banned From Instagram</title>
      <link>/post/0005/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0005/</guid>
      <description>Quick note - as of me editing this post on March 15, my Instagram account has been reinstated. I&amp;rsquo;m still going to actively avoid using it unless necessary, as I stated in this post, and I&amp;rsquo;ve also added &amp;ldquo;Share To&amp;rdquo; buttons to these blog pages and to the galleries if you wish to show off my work to some folks or talk about what I have to say on this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#004: What Is A Talkie, And What Does It Do?: March 2023 Radio Programming Calendar</title>
      <link>/post/0004/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0004/</guid>
      <description>You might not like it, but this is what peak UI design looks like.  Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make a monthly post here to let you fine folks know which records we&amp;rsquo;re going to be playing each episode, as well as take a bit to talk about some of my favorite jazz and jazz-related artists and records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#003: Studio Notes/The Finer Things, January &amp; February 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0003/</guid>
      <description>The corkracks, sometime in the middle of production of Our Lady Maven.  Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I’ve just finished up the final touches on Issue 1 of Our Lady Maven at long last, and I’ve finally got time for a bit of a breather to write a bit about what I’ve been working on, what I’ve been reading when I have a second to sit down and read, what I’ve been listening to in the studio, what I’ve been playing in my wee small hours of the morning before I pass out for the day, and (for those few of you who are curious for reasons other than wondering “what the fuck is wrong with her”) what I’ve been smoking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#002: Why Love Jazz? About The Jazz Program and Our February 2023 Programming</title>
      <link>/post/0002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0002/</guid>
      <description>You might not like it, but this is what peak UI design looks like.  Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! As the vast majority of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been the host of The Jazz Program on datafruits.fm for a good couple years now, and the host of a small show called Talkie Time on the timeslot before it. Since finally deleting my Twitter account, however, I&amp;rsquo;ve had a bit of an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#001: A Fresh Start, Old Computers, and a New Coat Of Paint</title>
      <link>/post/0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0001/</guid>
      <description>Intro Hey, y&amp;rsquo;all. As you&amp;rsquo;ve most likely noticed, 2022 was&amp;hellip;.well, not a good year for social media. Twitter&amp;rsquo;s on fire, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s been under federal scrutiny for years now, and seeing as I don&amp;rsquo;t have a face for anything but radio, I&amp;rsquo;ve never bothered with Tiktok.
So, now that I&amp;rsquo;ve finally updated my website again, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to just go back to basics and start a little blog here instead. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been more long-winded than most social media sites want me to be as it is, and this kind of format gives me more of an opportunity to write a bit about things I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t normally get the chance to talk about otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Sarah. I&amp;rsquo;m an underground cartoonist, professional illustrator, and wandering ne&amp;rsquo;er-do-well. I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling stories and creating work for what is basically my entire adult life, and this is where I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to place my thoughts on doing so, as well as ramblings about life in general.
This blog is mainly where I write about things that hold my interest, and is also where I put notes on books, records, and other such things that I&amp;rsquo;m working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/post/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/faq/</guid>
      <description>Note: This FAQ page is a constant work in progress, as is most of the site. As I get new questions, think of things I might want to make sure my readers know, and invent new answers and/or questions for those answers, I&amp;rsquo;ll be adding them here. If you can&amp;rsquo;t find an answer to whatever it is that you&amp;rsquo;re curious about, send me an email and I might just add it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/post/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/links/</guid>
      <description>The following are links to websites of folks I think are cool.
Note that I said websites, not accounts. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to use this page to promote social media networks, and the vast majority of folks (specifically, other cartoonists/DJs) who I know all have social media accounts in place of a website, so this list shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be considered an exhaustive compendium of folks I think are neat.
f you&amp;rsquo;re not on this list but think you should be, I probably can&amp;rsquo;t find your website or I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten around to adding you yet because I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with other obligations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellany</title>
      <link>/post/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc/</guid>
      <description>The following is a series of links to random accoutrements that I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out a way to shoehorn into a post, but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to build a whole new website for. So, I&amp;rsquo;m putting them all under a lil&amp;rsquo; umbrella here for those of you who would be interested in these types of things.
Note: This list is VERY incomplete at the moment&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;m in the middle of a bunch of things and need time to code a bunch of the things I plan on including here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ongoing Project Update Threads</title>
      <link>/post/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/updates/</guid>
      <description>The following is a series of progress threads for pieces that are announced, that I have permission to share the creation process of, and that I want to share with you. These all used to be up solely on social media, but in the interest of both wanting to have everything in one place and insisting upon utilizing Indieweb principles to make sure my work isn&amp;rsquo;t lost to the ages for the umpteenth time thanks to the whim of some techno-jackanape, I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting them here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Update Thread: Our Lady Maven</title>
      <link>/post/update_barren/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/update_barren/</guid>
      <description>Here, you can find a chronological &amp;ldquo;thread&amp;rdquo; of sorts of posts about Barren. You can also click on over to the Barren tag to see all these posts individually, as well as a good amount of other things I&amp;rsquo;ve written that mention the series.
This page gets updated all the time, so check back frequently!
 Photo Roll 02 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 1 May 1, 2023 Original post here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Update Thread: Our Lady Maven</title>
      <link>/post/update_olm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/update_olm/</guid>
      <description>Here, you can find a chronological &amp;ldquo;thread&amp;rdquo; of sorts of posts about Our Lady Maven. You can also click on over to the Our Lady Maven tag to see all these posts individually, as well as a good amount of other things I&amp;rsquo;ve written that mention the series.
This page gets updated all the time, so check back frequently!
 Photo Roll 05 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 2, Part 1 September 9, 2023 Original post here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Update Thread: Our Lady Maven</title>
      <link>/post/update_snakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/update_snakes/</guid>
      <description>Here, you can find a chronological &amp;ldquo;thread&amp;rdquo; of sorts of posts about Our Lady Maven. You can also click on over to the Our Lady Maven tag to see all these posts individually, as well as a good amount of other things I&amp;rsquo;ve written that mention the series.
This page gets updated all the time, so check back frequently!
 Photo Roll 02 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 1 May 1, 2023 Original post here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Update Thread: The Garden</title>
      <link>/post/update_garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/update_garden/</guid>
      <description>Here, you can find a chronological &amp;ldquo;thread&amp;rdquo; of sorts of posts about Our Lady Maven. You can also click on over to the [&amp;quot;The Garden&amp;quot;] tag](/tags/the_garden/) to see all these posts individually, as well as a good amount of other things I&amp;rsquo;ve written that mention the series.
This page gets updated all the time, so check back frequently!
 Photo Roll 04 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 2 September 8, 2023 Original post here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarahallenreed.com Site Update History</title>
      <link>/post/misc_mainsiteupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc_mainsiteupdate/</guid>
      <description>2023 November 11, 2023  Added and changed the featured images on the Full Color Samples and Black And White Samples pages. Added an actually recent photo to the About page and cleaned up the design. Cleaned up the formatting on all text pages.  To Do  Add alt text to everywhere it&amp;rsquo;s not already implemented. I want to make this site as screen-reader friendly as possible. Implement Gitea to self-host my Git repos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Listening List</title>
      <link>/post/misc_listen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc_listen/</guid>
      <description>What Is The Listening List? In June of 2023, I started making a tiny thread on Mastodon about albums I was listening to in the gym and in the studio. While I tend to listen to music via Newpipe in the gym, I use mocp in the studio. It eventually hit me that I could just keep everything I listen to on MOCP saved in a folder of monthly playlists, and edit them down and put them up here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truckstop.Coffee Site Patch Notes</title>
      <link>/post/misc_truckstopupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc_truckstopupdate/</guid>
      <description>2023  July 3, 2023  Added this update log! Formally added a bunch of features, including the Miscellany section, the Project Update Threads, and more. Added Listening List entries from when I started keeping track in mid-June, up through July 1st. Finished the first entry in How To Cook Shit Started in on two additional entries Minor CSS updates, including different colors when hovering over the menu  July 4, 2023  Added post 14, the Jazz Program schedule for July.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/post/misc_sixthrees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc_sixthrees/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 00 - Selfies, Self-Portraits, And Portraits Of The Soul</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll00/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll00/</guid>
      <description>For whatever reason, a lot of folks seem to be fascinated with knowing what folks who create things look like. I&amp;rsquo;ve never understood it&amp;ndash;partially because I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly the type of artist known for going out of her way to look remotely presentable&amp;ndash;but for those of you curious, here&amp;rsquo;s a tiny little selection of self-portraits and press photos I&amp;rsquo;ve had taken over the years.
 
 Self-portrait from the pages of Tabula Rosetta.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>