<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>miscellany on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/miscellany/</link>
    <description>Recent content in miscellany on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Sarah Allen Reed.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/miscellany/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarahallenreed.com Site Update History</title>
      <link>/post/misc_mainsiteupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc_mainsiteupdate/</guid>
      <description>2023 November 11, 2023  Added and changed the featured images on the Full Color Samples and Black And White Samples pages. Added an actually recent photo to the About page and cleaned up the design. Cleaned up the formatting on all text pages.  To Do  Add alt text to everywhere it&amp;rsquo;s not already implemented. I want to make this site as screen-reader friendly as possible. Implement Gitea to self-host my Git repos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Listening List</title>
      <link>/post/misc_listen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc_listen/</guid>
      <description>What Is The Listening List? 2023  June 2023 Moe - Tin Cans and Car Tires
Drive Like Jehu - Yank Crime
Gorguts - Pleiades&amp;rsquo; Dust
De-Phazz - Black White Mono
Beck - The Information
Bugge Wesseltoft&amp;rsquo;s New Conception Of Jazz - Sharing
Elbow - The Taking Off And Landing Of Everything
Johnny Paycheck - 11 Months And 29 Days
Johnny Paycheck - Slide Off Your Satin Sheets
The Grateful Dead - Radio Luxembourg, May 16, 1972</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truckstop.Coffee Site Patch Notes</title>
      <link>/post/misc_truckstopupdate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/misc_truckstopupdate/</guid>
      <description>2023  July 3, 2023  Added this update log! Formally added a bunch of features, including the Miscellany section, the Project Update Threads, and more. Added Listening List entries from when I started keeping track in mid-June, up through July 1st. Finished the first entry in How To Cook Shit Started in on two additional entries Minor CSS updates, including different colors when hovering over the menu  July 4, 2023  Added post 14, the Jazz Program schedule for July.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>