<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>about on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in about on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Sarah Allen Reed.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 1969 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;floatcenter caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/photo/000/06.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/photo/000/06.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Sarah. I&amp;rsquo;m an underground cartoonist, professional illustrator, and wandering ne&amp;rsquo;er-do-well. I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling stories and creating work for what is basically my entire adult life, and this is where I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to place my thoughts on doing so, as well as ramblings about &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IAu2X4BExfk&#34;&gt;life in general&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is mainly where I write about things that hold my interest, and is also where I put notes on books, records, and other such things that I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I&amp;rsquo;d shy away of viewing this as an extention of my professional work as an illustrator&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, but I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consider it out of the question to view this as a suppliment to my work as a storyteller. I do illustration and contract work to pay the bills, sure, but the vast majority of my ouvure is decidedly more introspective, and you could view this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2020/09/03/1007716/digital-gardens-let-you-cultivate-your-own-little-bit-of-the-internet/&#34;&gt;digital garden&lt;/a&gt; as one would view &lt;a href=&#34;https://emvi.com/blog/luhmanns-zettelkasten-a-productivity-tool-that-works-like-your-brain-N9Gd2G4aPv&#34;&gt;Luhmann&amp;rsquo;s zettelkasten&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bl.uk/collection-items/the-notebook-of-william-blake&#34;&gt;William Blake&amp;rsquo;s sketchbooks&lt;/a&gt;, albeit written by an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/incongruous&#34;&gt;incongurious&lt;/a&gt; professional &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/dolt&#34;&gt;dolt&lt;/a&gt; rather than a man of letters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occasionally you&amp;rsquo;ll see posts about where I&amp;rsquo;ll be and what I&amp;rsquo;ll be up to, if those happen to be things you can tune into or come say hi to me at. The most frequent of those posts are the &lt;a href=&#34;/tags/the-jazz-program/&#34;&gt;schedules&lt;/a&gt; to my weekly three-hour radio block on &lt;a href=&#34;https://datafruits.fm&#34;&gt;datafruits.fm&lt;/a&gt;, but in the few instances that see me doing interviews or showing up in &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/meatspace&#34;&gt;meatspace&lt;/a&gt; they&amp;rsquo;ll be on here as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also curate a &lt;a href=&#34;/tags/photo-roll/&#34;&gt;photo roll&lt;/a&gt; with things in my world I find important. I am not a fan of social media for a good many reasons, but &lt;a href=&#34;/post/0005&#34;&gt;having my Instagram account nearly banned for reasons I still don&amp;rsquo;t understand&lt;/a&gt; has kind of taught me the lesson that, if I care about the few memories I bother to share with the world, I probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be hostin&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;em on the walled garden. You can also see &lt;a href=&#34;/post/photoroll00/&#34;&gt;drawings and photos of me on here&lt;/a&gt; if you want to do that for whatever reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I keep a &lt;a href=&#34;/post/links/&#34;&gt;list of links&lt;/a&gt; on here of sites by folks I respect, folks whose work I enjoy, or folks I consider friends. I adamantly refuse to link to social media if I can at all avoid it, so all of the links listed are websites away from the confines of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://indieweb.org/silo&#34;&gt;silos&lt;/a&gt; and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be consider a comprehensive list of &amp;ldquo;good folks&amp;rdquo; due to the fact that not everyone has their own website. If we&amp;rsquo;re buds and you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, consider making a website!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If that doesn&amp;rsquo;t answer all your questions, feel free to check out the &lt;a href=&#34;/post/faq&#34;&gt;(in)frequently asked questions&lt;/a&gt;, head over to &lt;a href=&#34;https://sarahallenreed/resume/bio&#34;&gt;the slightly more professional-sounding bio on my portfolio website&lt;/a&gt;, or just &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sarah@sarahallenreed.com&#34;&gt;drop me an email&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/bio/&#34;&gt;write me a letter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not. Stay safe out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It should go without saying that the nonsense I prattle on about is not a reflection of those who employ me or enlist my services, but because bad faith is the rule on the modern Internet I&amp;rsquo;m putting that disclaimer here. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do keep a zettlekasten of my own in a cigar box, and at some point&amp;ndash;probably when I start putting pieces of my next book together&amp;ndash;intend on porting it to Tiddlywiki and posting it here, in case folks wish to follow the proverbial bouncing ball. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

