<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>studio notes on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/studio-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in studio notes on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Sarah Allen Reed.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/studio-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#011: The Finer Things, April And May 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0011/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;floatcenter&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/01.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/02.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HahaahaAHAAHAA &lt;em&gt;fuck this is late&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy. As much as I&amp;rsquo;d like to, I&amp;rsquo;ve not had much time to pen a long column about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to in my spare time, much less had much spare time to spend. Snakes, Barren, and a couple other upcoming projects have kind of monopolized most of my attention, and I&amp;rsquo;m a bit late on having a second to sit down and write about fun stuff. Hell, &lt;a href=&#34;https://truckstop.coffee/post/0003/&#34;&gt;we&amp;rsquo;re skipping an entire month here&lt;/a&gt; cuz I don&amp;rsquo;t even remember what I did in March at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, I have listened to a whole lot of new records and watched a bunch of new shows and movies this month&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, and very much would like to share &amp;lsquo;em all with you. So, without further ado&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-listening-to&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN LISTENING TO&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;d be a long, long list if I were to type out every sonic novelty that&amp;rsquo;s held my interest over the past three months, but here&amp;rsquo;s a short list of records I&amp;rsquo;ve had blasting on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jonsafari/mocp&#34;&gt;mocp&lt;/a&gt; over the past bit, sorted by the two main places I listen to records&amp;ndash;during my workouts, and in the studio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(I&amp;rsquo;ll be skipping doing Recommended Tracks for the &amp;ldquo;Workout Jamz&amp;rdquo; section, primarily because I was listening to each record/mix the whole way through while pumping iron or doing cardio and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much time to pick out individual tracks for you to check out. Still recommend you check out each record in their entirety, though, regardless of which list they&amp;rsquo;re on.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;workout-jamz&#34;&gt;WORKOUT JAMZ&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/music_01.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/music_01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Freetube logo.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Literally the only thing I&#39;ve found to make Youtube consistently usable on desktop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that the roads aren&amp;rsquo;t (consistently)&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; prohibitively snowy, I&amp;rsquo;ve been finally able to hit the gym with some sort of actual consistency again. And, as a direct result, I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to a lot of longer mixes, re-visiting some old favorites, and generally putting on two hours worth of either mixes or variations upon a theme of podcasts while I do fifteen reps of my body weight on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=sus+machine&#34;&gt;sus machine&lt;/a&gt; and try to avoid cute muscle boys catching me checking them out so I don&amp;rsquo;t get the fuck kicked out of me in the locker room. &lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of this list are gonna be accompanied by Youtube links&amp;ndash;the sets don&amp;rsquo;t seem to be available anywhere else that I could find, although I refuse to use Spotify &lt;a href=&#34;https://jacobin.com/2020/12/spotify-streaming-model-exploitation-class-conflict&#34;&gt;for obvious reasons&lt;/a&gt; so they may be on there. I should point out that, when on the move ,I either use &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=sus+machine&#34;&gt;Newpipe&lt;/a&gt; via &lt;a href=&#34;https://f-droid.org/en/&#34;&gt;F-Droid&lt;/a&gt; if I have my spare Android device with me or &lt;a href=&#34;https://sxmo.org/&#34;&gt;sxmo&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; implementation of &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ytdl-org/youtube-dl&#34;&gt;youtube-dl&lt;/a&gt; if I have my Pinephone to snag them. In the studio, I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://freetubeapp.io/&#34;&gt;Freetube&lt;/a&gt;, which has the added boon of allowing you to pipe through &lt;a href=&#34;https://invidious.io/&#34;&gt;Invidious&lt;/a&gt; rather than going through the Friendly Panopticon&amp;rsquo;s servers directly. Privacy is important and so is making local archive copies of things you love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;mala---boiler-room-london&#34;&gt;MALA - BOILER ROOM LONDON&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hkgik4edDpY&#34;&gt;This set&lt;/a&gt; is legendary for a reason, and not just because it&amp;rsquo;s one of the only times Mala has appeared on video during a live mix, much less had his mixing wizardry recorded at all. Ample &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/cuepoint/wheel-it-up-history-of-the-rewind-21fdcff243d9&#34;&gt;rewinds&lt;/a&gt;, an insane track list, and a level of bass that almost necessitates a full stack, if not an entire sound system proper&amp;ndash;this set has it all, and Mala spins the entire thing dancing along with the audience. Fantastic stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/music_02.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/music_02.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Peter Cullen posing with Optimus Prime.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; When you get this guy to voice the intro to your D&amp;B album, you know you&#39;ve made it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;dieselboy---the-dungeonmasters-guide&#34;&gt;DIESELBOY - THE DUNGEONMASTER&amp;rsquo;S GUIDE&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t listened to this in almost a decade, and put it on basically on a whim. Unsurprisingly, it still rips. A masterpiece of aggressive drum-and-bass paired with a fantastic selection of samples (including Red Queen&amp;rsquo;s monologue from the Resident Evil movie on the track &amp;lsquo;Infection (E-Sassin&amp;rsquo; mix)&#39;) as well as an introduction from Optimus Prime himself (Peter Cullen), this whole record is a treasure trove for the specific type of dork that spins records back because she &lt;em&gt;knows&lt;/em&gt; she heard that sample somewhere else before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s me. I am that specific type of dork.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/music_01.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/music_01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Soul Cowboy cover art&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; IIIIIINDAaaaAASTREEETS! HIT-ME-IN-DA- STREEEEEEETZ!!!11 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;skinny-puppy---the-greater-wrong-of-the-right&#34;&gt;SKINNY PUPPY - THE GREATER WRONG OF THE RIGHT&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At some point, and again mostly on a whim, I decided to search out an old music video I watched back when I was younger. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZwhK9nfFhMU&#34;&gt;It still holds up as one of the greatest music videos I think I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:4&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:4&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, the tune slapped as well, and I put it on the Jazz Program as bump music for a bit. Looked it up while in the gym for a bit, and it turns out the rest of the album slaps as well. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it described as their &amp;ldquo;most accessible&amp;rdquo;, and seeing as I tend to turn off most industrial records halfway through, I&amp;rsquo;m kind of glad for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;amorphis---queen-of-time&#34;&gt;AMORPHIS - QUEEN OF TIME&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you gotta get back to your roots, man. I&amp;rsquo;ve been finding it weirdly difficult to listen to black metal since Ophelia Drowning went kaput and The Forest At Night left Radio Dark Tunnel&amp;rsquo;s lineup. Something about it just doesn&amp;rsquo;t give me the good brain chemicals it used to, and if anything hearing genres I used to try (and repeatedly fail) to be a part of the community of kind of just makes me depressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, Amorphis hits nowhere near that mark, especially their later stuff. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;d get endless amounts of flack for this were I to put this comment in some kind of metal forum or what-have-you, but &amp;ldquo;Queen Of Time&amp;rdquo; specifically hits a lot of the same notes for me as the post-hardcore and melodic metalcore I listened to growing up. Combine that with some heavy-hitting lyrics about love, loss, and overcoming obstacles on one&amp;rsquo;s journey, and yeah. This is something I can bench to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/music_03.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/music_03.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Hybrid Minds.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Soulful D&amp;B&#39;s greatest. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hybrid-minds---bbc-radio-1-essential-mix&#34;&gt;HYBRID MINDS - BBC RADIO 1 ESSENTIAL MIX&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hybrid Minds are gods. If you consider yourself to be among the throngs of little faith, &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/GpyMU6xrcDA&#34;&gt;go check out this set&lt;/a&gt; and  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/m000m0j8&#34;&gt;peep the tracklist.&lt;/a&gt; You cannot find a more energizing, enrapturing, and borderline spiritual set of soulful tunes and smooth, divine track transitions without just heading back ten years to the age of classics like Oakenfold&amp;rsquo;s Goa mix. Perfect for doing kettlebell work, in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;soft-machine---third&#34;&gt;SOFT MACHINE - THIRD&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look, we all have days when we&amp;rsquo;re in &lt;em&gt;weird&lt;/em&gt; moods. My weird mood days just happen to have me staring off into the æther while I &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VFk3RzndUEc&#34;&gt;leg press&lt;/a&gt; twice my body weight as &amp;lsquo;Slightly All The Time&amp;rsquo; wails into my ears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not telling you this is a bad album. It&amp;rsquo;s a certifiable classic. I&amp;rsquo;m also not going to sit here and get oddly &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dictionary.com/browse/braggadocious&#34;&gt;braggadocious&lt;/a&gt; about how &amp;ldquo;lol i&amp;rsquo;m so edgy&amp;rdquo; for listening to avant-garde tripe in inappropriate places, because I made enough of those in my mid-twenties when I was dumb enough to think I was cool. I&amp;rsquo;m just autistic as all hell, and sometimes I have Bad Brain Days and need the Weird Noises to accompany me on my bold journey to having a thicker ass than half the cisgendered cardio bunnies in this here Planny Fitty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;studio-jamz&#34;&gt;STUDIO JAMZ&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one&amp;rsquo;s a bit of a weird one, because half the time in the studio I&amp;rsquo;m putting on the same exact records I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to for most of my career, especially if I need to get my brain into &amp;ldquo;work mode&amp;rdquo;.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:5&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:5&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; With that stated, once I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;em&gt;in&lt;/em&gt; work mode, I&amp;rsquo;ll put on a variety of records&amp;ndash;either stuff I plan on featuring on the radio, records I&amp;rsquo;ve heard about or heard tracks from on other radio shows that I&amp;rsquo;d like to check out&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:6&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:6&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, or old records I love that I just want to hear again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;rsquo;t list the last one here&amp;ndash;my &amp;ldquo;comfort food&amp;rdquo; in the studio could take up seven or more installments worth of five thousand word columns&amp;ndash;but here&amp;rsquo;s a few interesting samples and selections from the first two categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/music_04.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/music_04.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cover art to The Glow, Pt. 2.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; This lil&#39; elephant here knows how to tug at my heartstrings. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-microphones---the-glow-pt-2&#34;&gt;THE MICROPHONES - THE GLOW, PT. 2&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At some point in the past few months, I jokingly told an old friend of mine about a great new black metal record I thought they should check out. That record was &amp;ldquo;The Glow, Pt. 2&amp;rdquo;, and I was only half being a jackass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Microphones hit a lot of the notes that got me into DSBM and post-black metal in the first place, both emotionally and sonically, and I&amp;rsquo;d unironically rank it up there with (and in borderline the same category as) Agalloch&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Mantle&amp;rdquo; or Lifelover&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Pulver&amp;rdquo; as far as records go. This entire record is a beautiful and devastating emotional rollercoaster, and I highly recommend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended Tracks: All of &amp;lsquo;em. The piece doesn&amp;rsquo;t really work if you don&amp;rsquo;t listen to the whole thing cover to cover.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/music_05.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/music_05.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cover art to Fire Of Unknown Origin.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Plus, this record features cover art by Rolling Stone&#39;s own &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.discogs.com/artist/2235781-Greg-Scott-8&#34;&gt;Greg Scott.&lt;/a&gt; What&#39;s not to love? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;blue-öyster-cult---fire-of-unknown-origin&#34;&gt;BLUE ÖYSTER CULT - FIRE OF UNKNOWN ORIGIN&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah. Yeah, I know. No, I&amp;rsquo;ve never sat down and listened to &amp;ldquo;Fire Of Unknown Origin&amp;rdquo; until this month. Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m just as surprised as you are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I can say about this one that hasn&amp;rsquo;t already been said. It&amp;rsquo;s either up there with or takes the top spot of BOC&amp;rsquo;s best records, depending on who you ask, and the whole thing is a nerdy, energizing, and generally wonderful record. If I had never &amp;ldquo;gotten&amp;rdquo; BOC before now, this would be the record that would have made their style click, and seeing as the record that made them click for me was &amp;ldquo;Agents Of Fortune&amp;rdquo;, this is just more of what I liked from that album, cranked up a notch or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended Tracks: Burnin&amp;rsquo; For You, Fire Of Unknown Origin&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/music_06.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/music_06.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cover art to Stretch Music.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Stretchiest trumpet in the world, right here. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;chief-xian-atunde-adjuah-christian-scott---stretch-music&#34;&gt;CHIEF XIAN ATUNDE ADJUAH (CHRISTIAN SCOTT) - STRETCH MUSIC&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hooooly fuck. I heard &amp;lsquo;Perspectives&amp;rsquo; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://kuvo.org&#34;&gt;KUVO&lt;/a&gt; this month, and I &lt;em&gt;had&lt;/em&gt; to track this record down. I have been trying for what seems like my entire life to find more records that scratch at or near the itch that listening to early The Mars Volta records at a formative age have just kind of left there, and&amp;hellip;yeah. Did not expect that void to be filled by a trumpeter from NOLA, but here we are. I&amp;rsquo;ll most likely be spending a good amount of time with the good Chief&amp;rsquo;s music over the next month or so, because the rest of the work I&amp;rsquo;ve heard from him is equally as fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended Tracks: Perspectives, Sunrise in Beijing (feat. Elena Pinderhughes), Tantric&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/music_07.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/music_07.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cover art to Saturday Night Special.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; I don&#39;t know who did cover art duties for this one, but whoever &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt;, did a helluva job. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-lyman-woodard-organization---saturday-night-specialdont-stop-the-groove&#34;&gt;THE LYMAN WOODARD ORGANIZATION - SATURDAY NIGHT SPECIAL/DON&amp;rsquo;T STOP THE GROOVE&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHEN IN DESPAIR&lt;br&gt;
DON&amp;rsquo;T TAKE TO THE AIR&lt;br&gt;
SIT DOWN AND FEEL&lt;br&gt;
WHAT YOU KNOW IS REEEEEAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CREAAAATIVE MUUUUUUSICIANS&lt;br&gt;
KEEP ON ROLLIN&amp;rsquo; RIGHT ALONG&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BpwLwzngFtc&#34;&gt;YEEEAAAH, YEAH, YEAAH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;.that&amp;rsquo;s it, that&amp;rsquo;s all I got here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seriously though, lyric quotes aside, go listen to Lyman Woodard. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how one can listen to his records and &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; feel the urge to dance and create.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended Tracks: Creative Musicians, Don&amp;rsquo;t Stop The Groove, Theme In Search Of A Sportspectacular&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-playing&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN PLAYING&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not much, honestly. Since, again, I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much time to sit down and faff about, I&amp;rsquo;ve been sticking to either games that I can turn my brain off to or games that I absolutely need a walkthrough of some manner for because I&amp;rsquo;m too stupid to figure out the inner workings of the game designer&amp;rsquo;s mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I contain multitudes, dammit. Multitudes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/game_01.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/game_01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot from The Case Of The Golden Idol.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; oh dear me yes it seems the Old Time Troubles are here in our humble village yet again &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-case-of-the-golden-idol&#34;&gt;THE CASE OF THE GOLDEN IDOL&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3SmxX_nazCs&#34;&gt;Supergreatfriend&lt;/a&gt; tried this one out for an hour a while back, and after sitting there screaming the puzzle solutions at the screen I decided to give it a shot to see if I&amp;rsquo;d have any better luck than he did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, for the first few puzzles, yes. Yes I did. The issues comes later, where the designers force the clues to compound between cases and require you to remember who&amp;rsquo;s who and which face goes with which person&amp;hellip;which would be fine if &lt;em&gt;how the characters are drawn was consistent between chapters,&lt;/em&gt; which is hit and miss at best. It&amp;rsquo;s a minor detail, but very much something that can be hair-rippingly frustrating at times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;conquests-of-the-longbow&#34;&gt;CONQUESTS OF THE LONGBOW&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/game_02.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/game_02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot from Conquests Of The Longbow.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; This scene, specifically, stuck with me. And not just because &#34;dancing in an enchanted forest in a gorgeous nightgown to an audience of my one true love and the creatures of the forest&#34; is what you could politely call my transition goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This game is &lt;em&gt;gorgeous&lt;/em&gt;. One of the first Sierra games to feature in full VGA color, &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Sierra_Entertainment_video_games&#34;&gt;if not &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; first depending on how you calculate it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;ndash;the previous in-house game was Quest For Glory II, which featured EGA graphics and a text parser&amp;ndash;and somehow they managed to &lt;em&gt;nail&lt;/em&gt; it right out of the fuckin&amp;rsquo; gate. The art is painterly yet restrained, the character portraits are beautiful and portray emotions remarkably well given the limitations present in both hardware and experience, and there are entire scenes that are just &lt;em&gt;moving&lt;/em&gt; in their beauty. Old-school Sierra were always masters of romanticism and fairy-tale universes, but it&amp;rsquo;s fascinating to see how a simple color-palette upgrade takes it all to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How&amp;rsquo;s the gameplay? Well&amp;hellip;it&amp;rsquo;s a Sierra point and click. Does it still include its fair share of Sierra bullshit? Absolutely. But if you can look past the moon logic, figure out how to work the strange mouse navigation from screen to screen, and if you remembered to track down a copy of the manual&amp;ndash;also beautifully illustrated, because of course it is, but as is tradition &lt;em&gt;your ass is not getting past the copy protection without it&lt;/em&gt;&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s a remarkably enjoyable point-and-click with some of the most memorable graphics I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen from this era.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;peglin&#34;&gt;PEGLIN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/game_02.gif&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/game_02.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Peglin sprite from the game Peglin.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; IT ME FR FR  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look, I&amp;rsquo;m a simple dipshit, aaight? I see a game about goblins throwing rocks, and my &lt;a href=&#34;https://sarahallenreed.com&#34;&gt;status as the undisputed Queen of Goblins&lt;/a&gt; legally requires me to play it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I blame &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLTvwKQHVid4YRvZnyLfCoNQ6lFtahFNrr&#34;&gt;Kikoskia&lt;/a&gt; for this one. I have his VODs and Let&amp;rsquo;s Plays going fairly often for background noise while I&amp;rsquo;m in the studio, and he picked up this game at some point in the past month. I saw it, picked it up, and haven&amp;rsquo;t really put it down since.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s still in Early Access, unfortunately, so there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of little bits and bobs either missing or outright broken. Hell, there&amp;rsquo;s a couple treasures you can pick up whose text outright doesn&amp;rsquo;t display for me on the version I have. With that stated, the art&amp;rsquo;s charming, the concept is simple and has an addicting gameplay loop, and the sound design (especially the final boss theme) is immaculate. Highly recommend snagging it if you enjoy simple arcade romps, plinky pachinko boards, or deck-builders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-watching&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WATCHING&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tee-vee&#34;&gt;TEE VEE&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;x-files-season-1&#34;&gt;X-FILES (SEASON 1)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gonna be real with you here. I don&amp;rsquo;t see it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/tv_01.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/tv_01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot from Conquests Of The Longbow.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; It&#39;s Always Sunny In The J. Edgar Hoover Building: The Gang Finds Mulder&#39;s Porno &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sacrilege, I know, but I genuinely can&amp;rsquo;t get the appeal. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I didn&amp;rsquo;t watch it in its heyday, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I expected to be able to take it seriously than I clearly was able to, and maybe it gets good after Season 1. But on god, half these episodes are god-awful (notable examples&amp;ndash;which I will not be calling by their actual names&amp;ndash;include S1E5 &amp;ldquo;Mulder Has A Cavewoman Fetish&amp;rdquo;, S1E8 &amp;ldquo;Hey Skully, You Ever Seen &amp;lsquo;The Thing&amp;rsquo;? No? Well This&amp;rsquo;ll All Be New To You Then&amp;rdquo;, and S1E9 &amp;ldquo;Oh No, There&amp;rsquo;s A Spoopy Face On The Moon, Time For A Second Challenger Disaster&amp;rdquo;) and the other half are only vaguely interesting (S1E3 &amp;ldquo;OH GOD ITS IN THE WALLS ITS IN THE WALLS ITSINTHEFUCKINWALLS&amp;rdquo;, S1E2 &amp;ldquo;It Turns Out That If Your Dumbass Partner Breaks Into A Top Secret Black Site You Can Just Point A Gun At The Cops To Get Him Back, Trust Me Bruh, They Won&amp;rsquo;t Shoot You, It&amp;rsquo;s Chill&amp;rdquo;, and S1E6 &amp;ldquo;The Case Of The Haunted Desk Plaquard With A Ben Franklin Quote&amp;rdquo; being the most &lt;em&gt;meh&lt;/em&gt; examples).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I &lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; schlock pulp teevee, dammit. I&amp;rsquo;ve watched the TV adaptation of La Femme Nikita, I have the complete run of the 2001 Witchblade show on my hard drive, and I have both Total Recall and Eraser in my VHS library. Hell, I almost prefer the trash &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0130416/&#34;&gt;1990s Mike Hammer reboot&lt;/a&gt; over &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0086760/episodes?season=1&#34;&gt;the &amp;rsquo;80s run&lt;/a&gt;, and that&amp;rsquo;s nearly explicitly because I think the idea of &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s No Way She&amp;rsquo;s Not A Body Snatcher Because No One Stays Lookin&amp;rsquo; That Young That Long&amp;rdquo; Velda and &amp;ldquo;Young Troubled Boy We Brought Onto The Show Because It&amp;rsquo;s The Nineties, Maaaan&amp;rdquo; Nick trying to teach &amp;ldquo;Definitely Not A Body Snatcher Because Holy Shit He&amp;rsquo;s Aged Fifty Years Since We Saw Him In The Eighties&amp;rdquo; Old Man Stacy Keach how to use the computer is funny as shit. The schlock ain&amp;rsquo;t the issue here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/tv_02.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/tv_02.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot from The X-Files.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Man, I didn&#39;t even cherry pick this one. This is &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Space_(The_X-Files)&#34;&gt;straight up off the Wikipedia page for the ninth episode from this season.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rather, the root of the issue seems to be that the writers &lt;em&gt;clearly&lt;/em&gt; want me to take it far more seriously than I&amp;rsquo;m even remotely able to, and at the same time it doesn&amp;rsquo;t play what tongue-in-cheek humor it &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; have evenly enough for it to work. I basically clocked out right at S1E11 after skipping half of the previous few episodes midway through because I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it, and seeing as S1E14 is literally called &amp;ldquo;Gender Bender&amp;rdquo; and I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine they&amp;rsquo;re gonna play &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; hand with any subtlety or compassion&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:7&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:7&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, my trans ass is almost &lt;em&gt;glad&lt;/em&gt; I skipped out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So yeah, despite on paper being the target demographic for it, I just cannot seem to grok S1 of X-Files. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll start in on Season 2 at some point and it&amp;rsquo;ll be more tolerable. Hell, if anyone has any advice on exactly when in S1 it starts getting tolerable, &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sarah@sarahallenreed.com&#34;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt; and let me know. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll give it another college try at some point. But right now&amp;hellip;nah man, I&amp;rsquo;m good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and speaking of Mike Hammer&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;mike-hammer-1990s-season-1&#34;&gt;MIKE HAMMER (1990s) (SEASON 1)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/tv_03.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/tv_03.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot from Mike Hammer: Private Eye.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; It&#39;s Always Sunny In New York: The Gang Watches Internet Porno. Yes, I know I just made that gag, but that&#39;s unironically what the third episode is about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;guess what I&amp;rsquo;ve been making Autumn ████████ watch during Studio Movie Night?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 90s run of Mike Hammer, as I briefly touched up above in my rant about Scully and Mulder&amp;rsquo;s Sexual Tension Adventures, is &lt;em&gt;balls to the wall 90&amp;rsquo;s as fuck.&lt;/em&gt; Like a good amount of reboots in the nineties (&amp;ldquo;Escape From LA&amp;rdquo; immediately comes to mind, and not just because &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0116225/fullcredits&#34;&gt;Stacy Keach also plays Commander Malloy in that one&lt;/a&gt;), the 90&amp;rsquo;s run of Spillaine&amp;rsquo;s signature big ugly bastard plops the best actor to have ever played the role out of the gritty &amp;rsquo;80s of his previous appearance and directly into the Brave New World of cable news, Internet porn, and b-ball. I&amp;rsquo;m not just pulling those tropes from a hat with the words &amp;ldquo;things the 90s had lying around&amp;rdquo; written on it, by the way&amp;ndash;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0130416/episodes?season=1&#34;&gt;those are literally the Big Bads of episodes 2-4 of Season 1, respectively.&lt;/a&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s campy-ass nonsense complete with requisite gruff pulp monologue narration from Keach himself, and while the topics retain the same level of grit as you would expect from a Spillaine-inspired romp&amp;ndash;the Internet porn episode&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;final boss&amp;rdquo; is a snuff film ring&amp;ndash;it does not for a second expect you to take it with any gravitas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;harvey-birdman-seasons-1-3&#34;&gt;HARVEY BIRDMAN (SEASONS 1-3)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/tv_04.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/tv_04.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Harvey Birdman and Steven Colbert&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Would it surprise you to learn these two are the same person? ...No? Yeah me neither anyways moving on&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve been tuning in early to my three-hour block on Tuesday nights over on [datafruits.fm], you probably know that I tend to test my connection to the radio server by doing a small segment loosely called &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;until then, here&amp;rsquo;s this.&amp;rdquo; I usually have a few minutes before Talkie Time and between Talkie Time and The Jazz Program each week, and I tend to fill said minutes with random tracks interspersed with stupid TV and movie quotes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You probably also might have noticed me sampling Harvey Birdman a lot. If so, that&amp;rsquo;s because Autumn&amp;rsquo;s retaliation for me making her watch Mike Hammer learn what cable is was to make me watch Steven Colbert play a washed-up superhero-turned-lawyer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s definitely a few episodes that get uncomfortable in that &amp;ldquo;early Adult Swim&amp;rdquo; kind of way&amp;ndash;S3E9 &amp;ldquo;The Return Of Birdgirl&amp;rdquo; is a notable one, as the writers stumble their way through attempting to comment on legalizing gay marriage and somehow manage to fuck up so badly that it almost seems like they&amp;rsquo;re equating gay marriage to incest&amp;ndash;but all in all, the series holds up as well as shit like Sealab 2021, Space Ghost Coast To Coast, and other early AS romps, while using its 13-and-a-half-ish minute time limit to not overstay its welcome in each episode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;autumn-and-sarahs-big-dumb-movie-night&#34;&gt;AUTUMN AND SARAH&amp;rsquo;S BIG DUMB MOVIE NIGHT&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Autumn ████████&#39;s schedule and my constantly being vaguely busy, our little studio/found family doesn&amp;rsquo;t have much time to sit down and do much together that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve working on shit these days. We do, however, try and find time to have some kinda movie night every so often, and we tend to strike a happy medium between her preference for off-the-wall nonsense and my firm love for shite action garbage. Note that a good portion of these selections should not be taken as reflections of our taste&amp;ndash;the two of us have a tendency to just pick shit that will actively annoy the other.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:8&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:8&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;ve had on over the past bit. I&amp;rsquo;m leaving out some of the ones we watched, as well as a bunch of the movies I watched in the gym during cardio, because&amp;hellip;well, I&amp;rsquo;m running out of space here. Most of the ones I&amp;rsquo;m leaving out were movies I watch every so often because I love &amp;lsquo;em, so they&amp;rsquo;ll come back at some point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;punisher-warzone&#34;&gt;PUNISHER: WARZONE&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I honestly expected this to be bad. I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect it to be &lt;em&gt;boring&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/movie_01.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/movie_01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot from Punisher: War Zone.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; FUCK THIS GUY IN PARTICULAR &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Autumn sold me on this&amp;rsquo;n by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xop8yqgDMo4&#34;&gt;describing a scene in which Frank Castle straight up lights up a drugged up dude doing parkour with what looks like a surface-to-air missle&lt;/a&gt;, and that hit &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; many Bullshit Action Movie Points for me that, in my hubris, I demanded we fill at least one movie night slot with this tripe. I &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; it would be complete trash going in. Combine the mid-2000s tendency to make action flicks in general &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/yujF8AumiQo?t=26&#34;&gt;overly edgy for no good reason&lt;/a&gt; with it being an early superhero film&amp;ndash;one that features Frank Fuckin&amp;rsquo; Castle, to boot, the king of Edgy McEdgelordbait&amp;ndash;and I was expecting &lt;em&gt;garbage&lt;/em&gt;, sure, but &lt;em&gt;entertaining&lt;/em&gt; garbage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nah, man. This flick&amp;rsquo;s just &lt;em&gt;fuckin&amp;rsquo; dull.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hell, even the action scenes constantly find themselves batting in the low .100s when they&amp;rsquo;re not fouling out or swinging into embarrassing strikes. The closest thing this film had going for it was the obvious queer-coded (and, I&amp;rsquo;d argue, borderline reclaimable as trans-coded&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:9&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:9&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;) duo of Jigsaw and Loony Bin Jim, and the most hilarious part of that is that not only does the movie fail to even manage to make the &amp;ldquo;villian&amp;rdquo; part of &amp;ldquo;queer coded villain&amp;rdquo; trope stick&amp;ndash;the scene where Frank Castle tosses the mobster into a glass crusher and fucks up his face bad enough to turn him into Jigsaw is so unreasonably brutal and fucked up that you honestly kind of empathize with the guy for wanting to fuck up Angry Cop Mans&amp;ndash;but it &lt;em&gt;makes them more interesting than the title character himself&lt;/em&gt;. Frank Castle is &lt;em&gt;boring&lt;/em&gt;, and spends half the film being an self-hating little whinebag when he&amp;rsquo;s not busy getting his ass handed to him or somehow manage to bumble his way into slaughtering rooms full of what I assume we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to take as &amp;ldquo;bad guys&amp;rdquo; by the virtue of the writers blatantly ignoring how modern arms work in favor of The Rule Of Cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/movie_02.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/movie_02.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot from Shoot &#39;Em Up.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Screenshot from Punisher: War Zo....oh wait no this is from a much better movie nvm &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hell, even The Rule Of Cool doesn&amp;rsquo;t save this film here&amp;ndash;while writing this, I actually completely confused one of the action scenes in this movie &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KkA1aPN9C0A&#34;&gt;with the staircase scene from Shoot &amp;lsquo;Em Up.&lt;/a&gt;, and got halfway through writing about a &amp;ldquo;staircase scene&amp;rdquo; before realizing I was confusing one edgy hyperviolent movie about an angry maladjusted white guy shooting his way through multiple cartoonishly evil villans and entire mobs worth of gangsters in order to protect a woman and child with another, slightly better movie with a nearly identical premise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seriously, if you wanna watch a movie about a maladjusted angry guy shooting people he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like, just watch Shoot &amp;lsquo;Em Up. It&amp;rsquo;s not good either, but at least it&amp;rsquo;s at least &lt;em&gt;somewhat&lt;/em&gt; fun, and you won&amp;rsquo;t get bullied by people who think it&amp;rsquo;s funny that they tricked you into watching a Punisher movie. &lt;em&gt;Looking at you, Autumn.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-matrix&#34;&gt;THE MATRIX&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, I had never seen The Matrix until this year when Autumn pulled it up for movie night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was okay. I guess I get a lot of pop culture references now. The fight scenes were great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t remember most of it, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&amp;hellip;boy howdy between this and my opinion of the x-files i&amp;rsquo;m gonna get some aaaaangry emails aren&amp;rsquo;t i&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;john-wick-1-2--3-parabellum&#34;&gt;JOHN WICK 1, 2, &amp;amp; 3: PARABELLUM&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatcenter caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/movie_03.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/movie_03.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;John Wick skin from Fortnite.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; jon wik forkknife vee bucx &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Wick 4 hit theaters relatively recently, and while both of us wanted to go see it, Autumn had only seen 1 and 3 and I had only seen 2. So, we decided to just sit down one night and watch all three before booking tickets to 4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve already burned way too many words on Being Angry At Frank Castle&amp;rsquo;s Big Gay NYC Adventure, so in order to prevent me from &lt;a href=&#34;https://i.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/newsfeed/001/044/247/297.png&#34;&gt;screaming at clouds&lt;/a&gt; once we get deep enough into this, I&amp;rsquo;m just gonna sum these up in one paragraph each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;john-wick-1&#34;&gt;JOHN WICK 1&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not the best action film of its era, but pretty high up there. Wick 1 suffers from some pacing issues, especially in the first half, but they&amp;rsquo;re the kind of pacing issues you&amp;rsquo;d expect from a movie that knows full well that it only gets two hours or so of runtime, and while it speedruns through most of Wick&amp;rsquo;s motivations it does in fact let you see where they take him in violent, bloody fights with fantastic choreography and a choice selection of obscenely beautiful shots. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard the Wick series called &amp;ldquo;Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s answer to John Woo&amp;rdquo;, and it does its best to set the stage for that here, especially in its fantastic final fight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;john-wick-2&#34;&gt;JOHN WICK 2&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the one I&amp;rsquo;ve seen, and the best of the three as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned. The homage to kung-fu cinema is even more blatant here&amp;ndash;the use of what looks like a green screen close-up with heavy color grading and heavy vignetting just before the subway fight scene with Cassian &lt;em&gt;screams&lt;/em&gt; Hong Kong cinema to me&amp;ndash;and key concepts such as the Continental are introduced here, which both flesh out the blood-covered world Wick inhabits and makes it incredibly fascinating. This is also where a lot of cracks in the armor start to show as well, unfortunately&amp;ndash;the complete lack of music or other audio during the Cassian fight, while atmospheric, makes the fight drag on just a little too long, which is something the third movie &lt;em&gt;drags into the ground&lt;/em&gt;&amp;ndash;but all and all this is the best Wick film in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;john-wick-3-parabellum&#34;&gt;JOHN WICK 3: PARABELLUM&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, I lied. I can&amp;rsquo;t keep this to one paragraph. I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;em&gt;mad&lt;/em&gt; at this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/movie_04.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/movie_04.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;John Wick skin from Fortnite.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;HI YES I&#39;M ADDY JUDICATER FROM HR AND I BET YOUR WONDERING WHY I CALLED YOU ALL TO THIS ZOOM CALL TODAY&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Autumn jokingly described this one as &amp;ldquo;the movie where they deal with the consequences of the first two&amp;rdquo;, and she&amp;rsquo;s right. The issue is that the consequences are introduced way too quickly and often end up on express trains to Nowhere Land before derailing and crashing just before shit could have gotten even remotely interesting, and then it spends half the film dealing with the assassin&amp;rsquo;s equivalent of an insurance claims agent bitching at everyone to pay up because god forbid your liability policy covers &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film tosses a lot of interesting (Sofia, Berrada), not-so-interesting (John Wick Fanboy Guy Whose Name I Forgot), and, occasionally, insufferable (The Adjudicator) characters at you, and then barely does anything with the good ones and drags the insufferable ones (&lt;em&gt;LIKE THE ADJUDICATOR&lt;/em&gt;) across your face like a teabag by a greasy frat boy who&amp;rsquo;s been training to hold a squat as long as possible for the explicit reason that he enjoys teabagging people (&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HAVE I IMPLIED HARD ENOUGH THAT I FUCKIN HATE THE ADJUDICATOR YET&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And speaking of The Adjudicator, the universe&amp;ndash;especially the enigmatic High Table&amp;ndash;is fleshed out rapid-fire, and the film teaches you that the High Table it fleshes out both sucks and is mired in weird bullshit that also sucks. It introduces this tiny shaven goth lady called The Adjudicator as The High Table&amp;rsquo;s token representative for the movie, and it spends &lt;em&gt;half the film&lt;/em&gt; making you watch every single person the previous two films built up as &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;literal gods in a world of hired killers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; pissing themselves at the prospect of having to deal with what appears to be nothing more than one hundred and ten pounds of cranky art school dropout turned HR Auditor. It also teaches you that John Wick&amp;ndash;you know, the guy the first two movies set up as basically the second coming of Assassin Jesus? The Baba Yaga? Fortnite Battle Royale Numbah One?&amp;ndash;is a little bitch when faced with even the &lt;em&gt;prospect&lt;/em&gt; of dealing with the High Table, a writing choice which, again, is complete bullshit, weird as hell, and really sucks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fight scenes are mostly great, but every second one seems to take the &amp;ldquo;no music&amp;rdquo; thing that pushed the Cassian fight in the second film just &lt;em&gt;barely&lt;/em&gt; into insufferable territory, then tosses the engine into first gear and drags its fuckin&amp;rsquo; cargo up a steep grade at an unbearably slow pace. Any concept of shot consistency is more or less gone. A particularly egregious example is the upstairs fight scene with John Wick Fanboy, which is just the mirror fight from 2 but way too fuckin&amp;rsquo; long, no actual continuity, almost no music, and the opposing player to Wick being basically Banderas&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=howhfMAoEt0&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;I Wanna Be Number One&amp;rdquo; character gimmick from &amp;ldquo;Assassins&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt; but simultaneously without the off-the-rails insanity that made Banderas&amp;rsquo;s character work and borderline Jokerfied in his fanboyism. Fact is, when your fights are topping ten minutes plus at the high end of their runtime,  often lack music entirely, make it impossible for the audience to follow what&amp;rsquo;s going on, re-use gimmicks from previous films with barely any actual iteration on the themes, and feature dull, unlikable characters, &lt;em&gt;that just doesn&amp;rsquo;t add up to what I expect from a franchise like John Wick.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/movie_05.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/movie_05.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;John Wick skin from Fortnite.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;I&#39;d tell you this was about when I started screaming but I&#39;m gonna be real, I just paused it and stared at the screen for like ten seconds.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And to be completely frank, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;all of this almost redeems itself at the end&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. The Continental fight is one of the best in the series. Winston putting Vivaldi on the loudspeakers is an immaculate brushstroke, the fight fleshes out Charon and Winston quite a bit&amp;ndash;which is great! they&amp;rsquo;re two of the most interesting characters in this universe!&amp;ndash;and despite making you suffer through the aforementioned mirror fight at some point during all this, the whole shebang ends with The Adjudicator throwing in the towel and coming to the table to negotiate. All would be fine if the living embodiment of &amp;ldquo;Do You Know Who My Daddy Boss Is&amp;rdquo; got her comeuppance at the end of the film, and we come real fuckin&amp;rsquo; close to that happening and this film closing out with a satisfying ending. Hell, maybe toss her off the roof to send a message to The High Table. That&amp;rsquo;d be fun. But, despite a huge shootout to defend The Continental against her bullshit, our boys Winston and Charon just acquiesce to her and &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;toss John off the roof instead out of almost nowhere and for basically no previously broadcast reason&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, giving John WIck 3 the most anticlimactic bullshit ending this side of Lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, I vetoed watching John Wick 4 in theaters after 3. We&amp;rsquo;re waiting &amp;lsquo;till it leaves theaters and watching it in the studio. Lord knows we do not need to get kicked out of &lt;em&gt;another&lt;/em&gt; theater due to me screaming at the screen, and seeing as the end of the third film sees My Least Favorite Character getting her way and The Continental tossing Keanu out on his ass and into Ya Boy Morpheus&amp;rsquo;s sewers, I don&amp;rsquo;t even think focusing on Lawrence &amp;amp; Keanu&amp;rsquo;s Excellent Adventures will make me think dropping thirty bucks on tickets and a tenner on popcorn will be worth it if Assassin HR Lawyer Team Girl is back for a second round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So yeah, we&amp;rsquo;ll come back to this in six months or however long it takes for this thing to get out of theaters and onto my smaller screen. And yeah, you bet your &lt;em&gt;ass&lt;/em&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m probably gonna have Opinions on that one as well. Stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-rock&#34;&gt;THE ROCK&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a fan theory going around that states that Sean Connery&amp;rsquo;s character in Michael Bay&amp;rsquo;s The Rock, James Mason, isn&amp;rsquo;t who he says he is. In fact, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9FdnevXjqdc&#34;&gt;there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of evidence that&amp;ndash;while not official in any capacity&amp;ndash;points to Mason actually being Connery&amp;rsquo;s last role as James Bond.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bet you can imagine why I demanded this be a movie night selection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/movie_06.gif&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/movie_06.gif&#34; alt=&#34;John Wick skin from Fortnite.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;thank you sean connery, very cool&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Issue this film has is the exact same one that Punisher: War Zone had, but in reverse&amp;ndash;the only two things this film has going for it is Connery in the role of Mason and Nick Cage in a lead role as bomb disposal expert Dr. Stanley Goodspeed. The villians suck, the supporting cast is mid, and the plot is nonsense. Every single thing this film has going for it is driven by these two powerhouses, and nearly every quotable or memorable scene is either because they&amp;rsquo;re both damn good at their jobs or because Michael Bay&amp;ndash;even this early in his career&amp;ndash;is laughably and demonstrably shit at his.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, in fairness, this is signs of peak Bay. Let&amp;rsquo;s be real here: you don&amp;rsquo;t watch a Michael Bay film because you expect it to be good. You don&amp;rsquo;t watch it because you expect a full cast of interesting and well-developed characters. No, you watch Explosions McBullshit Mans Brand Films to see one or two insane but entertaining dorks bumbling their way through  awkward interactions with what few women are in the film, inane and often ham-fisted plot twists, unreasonably high stakes driven by certifiable and irredeemable villains who get way more screen time and backstory than they really deserve, and explosions. Lots of explosions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In that, The Rock delivers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-reading&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN READING&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I promised you all some insights on my reading list last time, and never let anyone say I don&amp;rsquo;t deliver, even if it takes me a bit longer than anticipated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/book_01.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/book_01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;John Wick skin from Fortnite.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;Jack Reachers In Screenshot May Be Larger Than They Appear&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;lee-child---killing-floor&#34;&gt;LEE CHILD - KILLING FLOOR&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack Reacher is a man after my own heart. His interests include diners, blues, old cars, sex, and blowing off the heads of the local rich goon&amp;rsquo;s lackeys with stolen Ithicas. Add into that the fact that he&amp;rsquo;s six-foot-five and is built like a brick shithouse (and ignore the fact that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what commitment is) and he&amp;rsquo;d be the type of man that I&amp;rsquo;d have trouble keeping &lt;em&gt;out&lt;/em&gt; of my heart as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, &lt;a href=&#34;https://i.redd.it/7bl5i42gd02b1.png&#34;&gt;I have a type.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Killing Floor is the first released full book in the series, and it established the character as a force to be reckoned with in the modern noir canon for a reason. The book starts strong, with honestly one of the best opening lines in recent memory (&amp;ldquo;I was arrested in Eno&amp;rsquo;s diner&amp;rdquo;) and doesn&amp;rsquo;t let up from there. Lee Child paints a fantastically in-depth portrait of a man who both never really gave up the war and never really gave up on his freedom, either, and the supporting cast is fantastic and painted as boldly as any strokes from the masters like Spillane would be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of The Man Himself&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/book_02.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/book_02.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;John Wick skin from Fortnite.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;Hey look, it&#39;s that guy from Escape From LA! ...no wait hold on&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mickey-spillane---i-the-jury&#34;&gt;MICKEY SPILLANE - I, THE JURY&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;I also spent some time revisiting his masterstrokes. Managed to snag a copy of The Complete Mike Hammer, and &amp;ldquo;I, The Jury&amp;rdquo; was Selection Numero Uno. It&amp;rsquo;s a strong start. All the notes one would expect from the biggest, ugliest leading beast in dime store crime are hit&amp;ndash;dead friends, colorful allies, dangerous goons, and seditious, murderous dames are all present. The climax of the book is honestly one of the best in Spillane&amp;rsquo;s catalogue as well, as a country club full of a rogues gallery that would intimidate even Poirot turns into a bloody routing of the murderer and the finale of the who-dunnit as all the remaining suspects lay dead and the final culprit turns out to be the one closest to the heart. It&amp;rsquo;s a knockout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;john-lecarre---the-spy-who-came-in-from-the-cold&#34;&gt;JOHN LECARRE - THE SPY WHO CAME IN FROM THE COLD&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I re-read this every year, and every year I turn up something new. John LeCarre is a romantic in the purest form, which makes his subject&amp;ndash;the ins and outs of global espionage&amp;ndash;all the more intruiging in how he paints it. &amp;ldquo;The Spy Who Came In From The Cold&amp;rdquo; is a prime example of his unique touch, as the damned Leamas finds himself falling out of love with his country and in love with a Party member. She saves him from himself, he saves her from the hands of the bloodiest man in communist Berlin, and in the end none of it matters in a climax that still takes its place as one of the bleakest in spy fiction. If you ever wonder why everything I write is a love story at its core no matter the subject&amp;hellip;here&amp;rsquo;s where I get it from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tom-clancy---patriot-games-the-hunt-for-red-october&#34;&gt;TOM CLANCY - PATRIOT GAMES, THE HUNT FOR RED OCTOBER&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/book_03.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/book_03.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;John Wick skin from Fortnite.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;thank u tom clancy, very cool&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Patriot Games&amp;rdquo; is something I had a copy of when I was a kid (for reasons I will never understand) but &amp;ldquo;The Hunt For Red October&amp;rdquo; is one I never sat down and read, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0099810/&#34;&gt;despite its film adaptation being hands-down my third favorite movie of all time.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:10&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:10&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; This re-read&amp;ndash;especially now that I&amp;rsquo;m a bit older and have had more than my share of Troubles with over-degreed and well-pedigreed fucks over the past few years&amp;ndash;hits a bit different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A large part of why Patriot Games hit home so much for me as a kid is because of one line that always stuck with me. There&amp;rsquo;s a scene early on in the book where Jack Ryan&amp;ndash;at this point in the timeline just a lowly ex-Marine who teaches history at Quantico and occasionally does some work for &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/q6TNe4FlirA?t=519&#34;&gt;Relno The Story-keeper&amp;rsquo;s favorite recurring villain&lt;/a&gt; that he Just Can&amp;rsquo;t Talk About&amp;ndash;finds himself a fish out of water at a dinner with the Royal Family. Sporting a busted arm and an overwhelming sense of anxiety and dread, he&amp;rsquo;s put at ease by the Queen herself stating gently, &amp;ldquo;Jack, the reason everyone here is fond of you is because of who and what you are. Try and keep that in mind.&amp;rdquo; Keeping that line in mind, especially as someone with my own battles with social anxiety, has carried me through quite a few shitty imposter-syndrome-laden dinners of my own, and for the most part Patriot Games keeps that anxiety at the core of the book. Jack being way out of his depth is a plot point that humanizes the man, and in the film adaptation of &amp;ldquo;The Hunt For Red October&amp;rdquo;&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:11&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:11&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; it&amp;rsquo;s the crux of his character. And it &lt;em&gt;works&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0011/book_04.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0011/book_04.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;John Wick skin from Fortnite.&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;If you think I&#39;m fucking with you about it getting infinitely dumber as the series goes on, I&#39;d like to point out that this is the canonical reason Jack Ryan eventually becomes president at the end of &#34;Debt Of Honor&#34;.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Issue with the novel is that &lt;em&gt;he&amp;rsquo;s not that&lt;/em&gt;. He&amp;rsquo;s a man whose background has a lot of weird amounts of prestige added to it, and the entire book is filled with folks who seem to belong to the Patting Themselves On The Back Club, Skull And Bones Chapter. Literally the only relatable character in the book is Captain Marko Ramius himself. Everyone else seems to have stumbled their way upwards through either generational wealth, generational status, Good Old Fashioned American Exceptionalism&lt;sup&gt;TM&lt;/sup&gt; that just seems to be written in the same way that the people that glorify fail-upwards-morons like Daddy Elon seem to write their characters, or a little of Columns A, B, and C. This is a problem that would persist in every subsequent Clancy novel from there on out&amp;ndash;albeit to much more enjoyable Action Movie Bullshit levels&amp;ndash;and it is a problem in Patriot Games as well. Hell, there&amp;rsquo;s a scene in Patriot Games where Clancy insists upon showing you that Jack Ryan has a superhuman sense for making Good Stock Trades, which is undermined juuust a little bit if you overlook the fact that what he&amp;rsquo;s doing is acting on privileged information he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have and could, if he were any less rich, fall under the lines of &amp;ldquo;prosecutable insider trading&amp;rdquo;&amp;ndash;a point which Clancy touches on, then utterly ignores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whole thing, annoyingly enough, feels tone deaf now that I&amp;rsquo;m not an impressionable youngster and will never be a Harvard grad. Still recommend the movie tho, and Patriot Games still has a slammingly good climax and some fantastic writing to it&amp;ndash;assuming you can overlook the whole America Gud Third Wurld Not Gud parts, that is. Older I get, the more I have trouble doing so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-smoking&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN SMOKING&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re seeing a pattern in the headings in this section here, that&amp;rsquo;s because there is one. Pipes And Cigars had a blowout sale on Peterson tins, and seeing as I thought I&amp;rsquo;d be out of Denver by now I went ahead and stocked up so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to pick up more tobacco once we get into the new place if I ran out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out, most of these aren&amp;rsquo;t to my liking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;petersons-de-luxe-navy-rolls&#34;&gt;PETERSON&amp;rsquo;S DE LUXE NAVY ROLLS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First time trying a coin cut, and at first I didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly know what to make of it. I smoked through the entire tin in six days, though, so clearly I enjoyed it. Then again, I tend to enjoy VaPer blends, so there is that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The room note is a bit strong, even by my standards, but it does smell pairs well with fresh-brewed coffee. And seeing as I nearly always have a pot going, that&amp;rsquo;s not a bad thing in the slightest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;peterson-early-morning-pipepeterson-nightcap&#34;&gt;PETERSON EARLY MORNING PIPE/PETERSON NIGHTCAP&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A fairly iconic duo that I suppose I expected more from. To be honest, Early Morning is a bit more to my liking than Nightcap was, but then again that would check out anyways, seeing as I tend to enjoy Virginias over Latakias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;peterson-irish-flake&#34;&gt;PETERSON IRISH FLAKE&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I jotted this one down when I originally penned the table-of-contents for this column, but despite making a point to do so at the time, I don&amp;rsquo;t even remember smoking this one. Usually, the Irish and I tend to see eye-to-eye on a good many things&amp;ndash;we share the same sentiments on whisky, beer, tea, and (I would imagine) pipe tobacco. So you would assume I&amp;rsquo;d remember smoking this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Somehow, I don&amp;rsquo;t. I have to imagine it wasn&amp;rsquo;t &lt;em&gt;awful&lt;/em&gt;, or I&amp;rsquo;d have at least remembered &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt;. But I don&amp;rsquo;t remember if it was &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt;, either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welp. Not much of a review, but still. If I ever pick up another tin of this, I&amp;rsquo;ll let y&amp;rsquo;all know what&amp;rsquo;s up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;assuming I remember to, of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;petersons-perfect-plug-3ps&#34;&gt;PETERSON&amp;rsquo;S PERFECT PLUG (3P&amp;rsquo;S)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just finished smoking a pipeful of this now as I&amp;rsquo;m writing this, actually. I will say that it&amp;rsquo;s much, &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; more compact than any other plug tobacco I&amp;rsquo;ve smoked&amp;ndash;you&amp;rsquo;re going to need a knife for this one. With that stated, I like it. It burns well, has a heady yet tolerable hit (I do love my heavies) and sports a lovely, woody room note. As long as you have a decently sharp blade on hand&amp;ndash;my &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.opinel-usa.com/collections/opinel-pocket-knives&#34;&gt;Opinel carbon steel&lt;/a&gt; works lovely&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s well worth a try.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;WHAT&amp;rsquo;S NEXT&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I expect to be doing a LOT of reading over the next few months, although it&amp;rsquo;s not the kind of reading I&amp;rsquo;m going to be doing for pleasure. &amp;ldquo;Snakes&amp;rdquo; is proving to be far more of an undertaking than I&amp;rsquo;d imagine, and I&amp;rsquo;m going to have a shelf stacked full of case law, queer history, and current events articles for me to slog through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do, however, also expect to have a few more movies and teevee shows to gripe about, seeing as I just loaded my Android device back up with more big dumb action movies. So look forward to that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all I got for now. I&amp;rsquo;m jumping right from penning this to quickly hammering out this month&amp;rsquo;s Jazz Program and Talkie Time schedule, so you should be able to peep that right after you peep this as they&amp;rsquo;ll probably find themselves out on the same day. I&amp;rsquo;ve also got a new column that I hope you folks will enjoy hitting this site soon, so stay tuned for that as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless, thanks as always for reading. You&amp;rsquo;re all amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not. Talk soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;SARAH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;Oh, and before I forget: fuck The Adjudicator. Lame-ass character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Footnotes&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the perks of being in the gym five out of seven days of the week to manage my ADHD is that I have a weird amount of time to camp on the treadmill and watch movies, as well as listen to new stuff either for The Jazz Program or for myself. See also the section on &amp;ldquo;Workout Jamz&amp;rdquo;. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I genuinely don&amp;rsquo;t know how, but we&amp;rsquo;ve had snow in April here. This place sucks. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still have to use the men&amp;rsquo;s locker room&amp;ndash;being naturally bald kind of prevents me from even remotely passing enough to change in the women&amp;rsquo;s, and there isn&amp;rsquo;t a gender neutral option. Even if that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the case, this is just kind of reality for most trans/gay folk, unfortunately. A lot of the survival skills I learned when I was openly gay in the Missourian backwoods still have to be applied over a decade later in a relatively blue city. Some things never change, unfortunately. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:4&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Top spot will always to to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X2LTL8KgKv8&#34;&gt;whatever the hell Corey Hart was on about here.&lt;/a&gt; I have to imagine the brainstorming session for this consisted of A&amp;amp;R asking our boy Corey if he had any ideas, and the man responding by snorting a line of cocaine off his television, pushing over a stack of straight-to-VHS pulp releases from the era, and screaming &amp;ldquo;ALL OF IT&amp;rdquo; at the top of his lungs. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:4&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:5&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re curious, my preferred &amp;ldquo;get into work mode&amp;rdquo; comfort playlist is Interpol&amp;rsquo;s LP discography in chronological order, with &amp;ldquo;Antics&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Turn On The Bright Lights&amp;rdquo; switched. When I used to drive semis, &amp;lsquo;Next Exit&amp;rsquo; (track one on &amp;ldquo;Antics&amp;rdquo;) was my alarm clock, and I&amp;rsquo;d spend my first few hours listening through their discography (with TOTBL following Antics, because how are you gonna skip TOTBL) while getting the engine warmed up and my brain woken up. I&amp;rsquo;ll also occasionally put on listen to Cake&amp;rsquo;s discography in chronological order for the same reasons, especially if I&amp;rsquo;m doing some writing instead of drawing that day. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:5&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:6&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I find most of my &amp;ldquo;jesus fuck this is fantastic I gotta find this album&amp;rdquo; tracks on either &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kuvo.org/&#34;&gt;KUVO&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://kdhx.org/&#34;&gt;KDHX&lt;/a&gt;, and (of course) &lt;a href=&#34;https:/soma.fm&#34;&gt;Soma.fm&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:6&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:7&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if you&amp;rsquo;re wondering &amp;ldquo;is the big bad something gender/queerness related?&amp;quot;&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m not watchin&amp;rsquo; the fuckin&amp;rsquo; thing, but &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0751129/&#34;&gt;according to IMDB&lt;/a&gt;, probably, yeah. Hell, Googling the name of the episode gives the description &amp;ldquo;A series of sexually-oriented murders that are identical, except that the killer appears to be both male and female, draws Scully and Mulder to an Amish-type community of people who may be alien in origin&amp;rdquo;, which is somehow &lt;em&gt;worse&lt;/em&gt; of a descriptor than IMDB gave. I&amp;rsquo;m good, bruh. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:7&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:8&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re curious as to which of the listed movie selections were me starting shit with her and which was Autumn starting shit with me&amp;hellip;Punisher Warzone was her pick, and The Rock was mine. Although, in fairness (as I kinda go into in the section about it) I was told The Rock would at least be interesting. So yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s my bad. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:8&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:9&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one&amp;rsquo;s probably a bit inside-baseball for the cis sections of my audience, but the scene where &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/cCbgjrb75fg?t=209&#34;&gt;Loony Bin Jim shatters every single mirror so that Jigsaw never has to look at his reflection again&lt;/a&gt; borderline &lt;em&gt;screams&lt;/em&gt; T4T romance to me in how it shows one person caring for another by doing their best to mitigate dysphoria through any means necessary, including by physically destroying mirrors with their own body. Although the tiiiny little detail where they&amp;rsquo;re, you know, &lt;em&gt;blood relation brothers&lt;/em&gt; makes that a bit weird&amp;hellip; &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:9&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:10&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0112401/&#34;&gt;Assassins&lt;/a&gt;, second is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0083658/&#34;&gt;Blade Runner&lt;/a&gt;. In the current runnings, at least. As with everything else, this list is subject to change. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:10&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:11&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s for this reason that Alec Baldwin will always be The Man to play Jack Ryan as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned. His portrayal in The Hunt For Red October hits exactly the parts of Ryan&amp;rsquo;s character that nail him down as a relatable protagonist before the later books spiral out of control and have him stumbling upwards to the Presidency through some capital-letter Utter Bullshit Writing in &lt;a href=&#34;https://jackryan.fandom.com/wiki/Debt_of_Honor&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Debt of Honor&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;. See also the attached screenshot above if you think I&amp;rsquo;m fuckin&amp;rsquo; with you. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:11&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#008: Studio News: March &amp; April 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0008/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bit of a longer segment this month, so I&amp;rsquo;m breaking my &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo; into two segments; &amp;ldquo;Studio News&amp;rdquo;, where I talk about the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to and what I&amp;rsquo;ve got in the pipeline, and &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo;, where I talk a bit about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to, watching, reading, playing, and smoking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also got a bit of a long, introspective topic to talk about, but that&amp;rsquo;s getting lopped into its own post as well; it&amp;rsquo;s heavy enough for one of my books, which means that I&amp;rsquo;d rather put it in its own little column instead of putting it in with the lighter things I usually talk about on this blog. I&amp;rsquo;ll have a bit more on that at the end of this post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So without further ado, here&amp;rsquo;s the studio notes for the past couple months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-working-on&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WORKING ON&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0008/01.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0008/01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Signing copies of Our Lady Maven to send out to backers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-lady-maven&#34;&gt;OUR LADY MAVEN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Lady Maven Issue 1 is finally done, promo art and all, and it&amp;rsquo;s more or less all out the door. I&amp;rsquo;ve signed and sent back my portion of the signed copies we did for the crowdfunding campaign, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be packing up the original art the fine folks who picked them up for the crowdfunding campaign and writing letters to go with them soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I cannot underscore how stoked I am to finally have this book out into the world, and both Em and I are very grateful for all of your support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t checked out the book yet, you can check out &lt;a href=&#34;/post/photoroll02&#34;&gt;this photo roll&lt;/a&gt; where I go into detail on the process of working through the issue itself, and you can also check it out &lt;a href=&#34;https://globalcomix.com/c/our-lady-maven/chapters/en/1/&#34;&gt;on GlobalComix&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ourladymaven.com/shop/&#34;&gt;purchase a physical copy here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cigarettes-demo&#34;&gt;CIGARETTES DEMO&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0008/02.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0008/02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Mapping out the...er, map.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also been intermittently working on the &lt;a href=&#34;/post/0003/#what-ive-been-working-on&#34;&gt;adventure game you all saw last time&lt;/a&gt;, albeit with a bit of a twist&amp;ndash;in order to flesh out the actual systems of the game in a slightly more low-stakes setting, Autumn ████████ and I have been crafting a tiny demo. Her and I have been collaborating for about a year and a half on developing a small TTRPG setting that we want to eventually expand upon, and I figured telling a story in that setting in a tiny demo of the ADV-style adventure game engine I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on developing in Renpy would be a fantastic way to make sure everything ticks just the way we want it to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have much to show on it currently&amp;ndash;and probably won&amp;rsquo;t for a bit, seeing as I&amp;rsquo;m about to start in on OLM Issue 2, as well as one other project I can&amp;rsquo;t talk about just yet and other comics that I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about later in this post. This will mostly be a little thing to hack on in the mornings when I&amp;rsquo;m still waking up and need something to get my mind rolling. Still, it is coming along decently nicely, and I&amp;rsquo;ve already got the map for the demo mostly plotted out, as you can see here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of hacking on things&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pinephones-porting-themes-and-other-open-source-fuckery&#34;&gt;PINEPHONES, PORTING THEMES, AND OTHER OPEN SOURCE FUCKERY&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As some of you know, I own a Pinephone, and I love the little bastard. I&amp;rsquo;ve used the thing in place of a commonplace book, as a portable SSH terminal, as a ScummVM box that fits in my purse, and as a general fun-time hacky thingy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0008/03.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0008/03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Rose Pine theme, ported to qt5. I&#39;m running &lt;a href=&#34;https://audacious-media-player.org/&#34;&gt;Audacious&lt;/a&gt; here for my music player.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also been working on making sure that I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one who gets to benefit from my tinkering (and occasional suffering). I had to manually port the &lt;a href=&#34;https://rosepinetheme.com/&#34;&gt;Rosé Pine theme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; to qt5ct (you can see it in the screenshot to your left there, running the QT version of Audacious), and ended up porting it to Xresources as well before being informed that they already had a theme going for it. &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rose-pine/xresources&#34;&gt;Thankfully the fine folks needed screenshots anyways, so I at least got to make one decent contribution.&lt;/a&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ll probably be sending them a qt5 theme as well, once I&amp;rsquo;ve finished up with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thing is, I had a helluva time even getting qt5ct running on PostmarketOS (among other things, including bluetooth&amp;ndash;which involved multiple wipes-and-OS-reinstalls) and while she&amp;rsquo;s all set up now I&amp;rsquo;ll probably be putting together a little blog post so you all don&amp;rsquo;t make the same mistakes I did. That&amp;rsquo;ll probably be a thing for next month, however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve finally got the ol&amp;rsquo; girl fairly close to a unixporn-worthy setup, though. She&amp;rsquo;s comin&amp;rsquo; along just fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;new-comics-maybe&#34;&gt;NEW COMICS? MAYBE?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;img class=&#34;floatleft&#34; src=&#34;/heavysm.png&#34;/&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fair warning: the following segment talks about an in-progress book of mine that covers a particularly heavy topic&amp;ndash;namely, the ongoing mistreatment and attempted genocide of the transgender population by certain far-right subsects of the American government.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I know not everyone has the spoons to read about that right now, or even read about an in-progress book about it&amp;ndash;lord knows I barely have the spoons to write about it&amp;ndash;so if you&amp;rsquo;re not in a good place or just would prefer to skip ahead to the next section, go on ahead.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, as some of you have noticed on &lt;a href=&#34;https://defcon.social/@sarahallenreed&#34;&gt;Mastodon&lt;/a&gt;, I&amp;rsquo;ve been angry-typing my way through a new script, &amp;ldquo;Snakes: A Brief And Personal History Of The Inner Workings Of Trans Genocide&amp;rdquo;, in response to my home state of Missouri officially criminalizing trans healthcare in the name of &amp;ldquo;consumer protections&amp;rdquo;; a hilariously dishonest one, seeing as half the billboards you see when entering our state advertise that you should buy your smokes here, because we have the lowest cigarette tax in the contiguous 48. Hell, we have multiple establishments in our fine state that are a combination smoke shop, gas station, and &lt;em&gt;fireworks emporium.&lt;/em&gt; I say this as a habitual cigar smoker and recovering alcoholic&amp;ndash;if Missouri gives a shit about public health, I&amp;rsquo;m the second coming of Anne Fuckin&amp;rsquo; Rice and I have a bridge to sell you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The issue with this obvious slam dunk of graphic journalism can be fairly clearly illustrated the fact that I&amp;rsquo;m probably the only one stupid enough to write it. I&amp;rsquo;m going to be honest, I have zero expectation of this doing anything but getting me doxxed, harassed, and possibly shot, regardless of how much effort I put into it. I don&amp;rsquo;t see this getting picked up by any publisher or any magazine or periodical, a statement I say with some experience. I actually pitched this book last year to a couple graphic journalism outlets, and one of my friends even gave me a direct referral to her publisher. Not a single publisher took me up on it, and that was well over a year ago at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0008/04.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0008/04.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; An early draft of Snakes, with its original working title.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thing with writing about trans issues is that most of the populace doesn&amp;rsquo;t give a shit about trans people dying, especially if the ones who die aren&amp;rsquo;t useful to the cis narrative, and there&amp;rsquo;s a certain segment of the population that would rather us straight up commit suicide than bother them with our existence at all.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Even the folks that &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; care about trans lives often will straight up not support work by trans folk that aren&amp;rsquo;t woefully capitulatory to the &amp;ldquo;generosity&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;acceptance&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;compassion&amp;rdquo; of the cis people around us, three things that a large section of the trans population rarely, if ever, get shown. In fact, unless you&amp;rsquo;re white, cis-passing, come from wealth or some kind of generational privilege, didn&amp;rsquo;t come out publicly until you&amp;rsquo;ve already done some kind of public-appeal work the cis folk liked, and don&amp;rsquo;t have an inordinately tragic backstory that involves you getting disowned, repeatedly sacked, and dragged through the mud and thrust into a state of depression and isolation that is nearly guaranteed to eventually kill you, you&amp;rsquo;re often doomed to not even be allowed near the microphones at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am exactly one of those things&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, and I&amp;rsquo;m also not writing about a fun part of the trans experience. I&amp;rsquo;m writing a series of arguments for the fact that the current persecution and violent treatment of trans folks in the United States is a direct&amp;ndash;and intentional&amp;ndash;mirror of the ten steps of genocide, as well as outlining my own personal history being raised in an abusive religious foster family, my experiences with a church (the one I was raised in, for the record) that directly funded the AIDS crisis and subsequent genocide of the gay community in the &amp;rsquo;80s and &amp;rsquo;90s, and the parallels between that event in American history and the one going on today in my own home state being pushed by ultra-Christian white supremacists who own copious amounts of guns and are more than happy to broadcast the fact that they&amp;rsquo;re willing to shoot minorities with them. This is not something anyone is going to pick up. This is not even remotely publishable. If anything, this is a death wish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0008/04_1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0008/04_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Its current state, as of me typing out this blog. To say this has come together quickly is a bit of an understatement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thing is, that&amp;rsquo;s not remotely new to me. Hell, at the moment, I&amp;rsquo;m also working on BARREN, another book that I genuinely don&amp;rsquo;t think is going to get picked up by any publisher due to its violent content, fucked-up and complicated storyline, and its unflinchingly bleak ending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This kind of leaves me with exactly one option if I want to get these books out into the world, and that&amp;rsquo;s to publish them myself. I&amp;rsquo;ve done this before&amp;ndash;Tabula Rosetta was my answer to the fact that no one wanted to publish my comics, and it ran for nine issues over nearly three years. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to re-boot Tabula Rosetta; as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned, it ran its course, and seeing as the first three chapters of the original draft of BARREN were published in the original run of TR, I think it&amp;rsquo;d be kind of weird having the tenth issue start up by telling a more refined version of the first chapter of a book that was already published in issue 7.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also don&amp;rsquo;t want to go back to a regular release schedule. Tabula Rosetta&amp;rsquo;s bimonthly release schedule&amp;ndash;which was kept to even when I was living in a van and homeless on the east coast&amp;ndash;was more or less what stopped me from continuing it. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to risk burning myself out by forcing myself into slamming through a regular release schedule, especially since I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with burnout for years anyways and haven&amp;rsquo;t released a full-length solo work in nearly four years at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What this leaves us with is either:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A.  I&amp;rsquo;ll end up putting these comics online, on their own website, as I finish each chapter, or;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;B.  I&amp;rsquo;ll end up putting these out, chapter by chapter, in their own magazine, which won&amp;rsquo;t be released until each issue is done to my satisfaction and ready to roll. &lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:4&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:4&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current plan is to do both at once. I have a title picked out for the magazine in option B, and I&amp;rsquo;ll probably secure the domain name for option A as well just in case. Lord knows my agoraphobia has kept me from getting to the post office in a timely manner more than once in my career; option A is probably the safest to ensure that I&amp;rsquo;m actually able to get these out there to all of you without you having to wait until my head&amp;rsquo;s in a good enough state to leave the house and deal with the post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-up-to&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN UP TO&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;coming-to-terms-with-having-to-root-for-the-cubs&#34;&gt;COMING TO TERMS WITH HAVING TO ROOT FOR THE CUBS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0008/05.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0008/05.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; hahahahahaha yeah about that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I&amp;rsquo;ve got good news and bad news. The good news is, Autumn ████████ and I are finally getting the hell out of Colorado. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to leave this shithole since nearly the minute I got here, and after multiple years of having setback after setback, it&amp;rsquo;s finally just about time for us to get out of Dodge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bad news is that we&amp;rsquo;re moving this red-blooded dyed-in-the-wood Ozzie-Smith-loving Cardinals girl to Illinois, just outside of Chicago. You know, the home of the Chicago Cubs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sacrilege&lt;/em&gt;, I tell ya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0008/06.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0008/06.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Packin&#39; boxes. If you wanna judge my book collection, now&#39;s the time; I&#39;m not sure when I&#39;m gonna be able to unpack it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fun part about being a household made up of a found family consisting of two trans folk and a toothy barking fuzzball is that there&amp;rsquo;s not many places you can move where you won&amp;rsquo;t be risking getting shot at. We obviously can&amp;rsquo;t go back to my home state of Missouri, and Autumn&amp;rsquo;s from even further south in DeSantis Land so we&amp;rsquo;re definitely not moving to her neck of the woods. Thankfully, Illinois not only has trans protections but is also a true-blue trade union state, something that has been very clearly lacking in the state that has been desperately trying to live up to Senator Armstrong&amp;rsquo;s libertarian ideals since well before the release of Revengeance.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:5&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:5&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m honestly looking forward to being back in the Midwest again, if for no other reason than the fact that the elevation here makes my skin flake up, the lack of humidity kills both of us and I miss my fuckin&amp;rsquo; rivers. Had we the cash, I&amp;rsquo;d have preferred to move back to Maine&amp;ndash;I lived there for about a year, and I honestly kind of grew to love it. Still miss Portland to this day. Maybe at some point we&amp;rsquo;ll have the money to end up back there, but for now, it&amp;rsquo;s back to the lower rents and muddy waters of the Mississippi River, where my accent won&amp;rsquo;t be out of place, my beater car won&amp;rsquo;t get rammed by idiots driving Teslas who are really angry that I don&amp;rsquo;t know who their father is, and the fact that I don&amp;rsquo;t regularly get high enough to think Joe Rogan is onto something is a social faux pax in and of itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Seriously, though, don&amp;rsquo;t expect me to root for the fuckin&amp;rsquo; Cubs. I ain&amp;rsquo;t doin&amp;rsquo; it. You can&amp;rsquo;t make me.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sobriety-and-recovery&#34;&gt;SOBRIETY AND RECOVERY&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next month, I&amp;rsquo;ll have hit a major milestone&amp;ndash;six months sober. I&amp;rsquo;ve also finally weighed in for the first time in a while, and I&amp;rsquo;m finally down to 155lbs&amp;ndash;last year in January, I weighed in at 215 after two years of relapsing on my eating disorder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The past three years have been particularly rough, and to be frank I&amp;rsquo;m surprised I survived them. Finally getting sober and getting my eating disorder back under control is something that took an absurd amount of effort. I want to keep this post at least relatively light, so I won&amp;rsquo;t be going into it here, but I did write a bit about the past few years and trying to get a handle back on my life. &lt;a href=&#34;/post/0009/&#34;&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re in a place where you can handle some heavier narratives, you can check it out here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s about all I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to in the studio for the past month. Tomorrow I&amp;rsquo;ll have the radio schedule up for The Jazz Program and Talkie Time for the month of May, and probably shortly thereafter I&amp;rsquo;ll post a new installment of The Finer Things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you all, as always, for reading. You&amp;rsquo;re all amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not. See you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;SARAH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;Footnotes...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used to use &lt;a href=&#34;https://draculatheme.com/&#34;&gt;Dracula&lt;/a&gt; across most of my devices, but I honestly like the pastels of Rose Pine a lot better. If you saw older screenshots of my setups over the past year, though, I was probably using Dracula. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know, I almost cut this line, thinking it was too confrontational even for my radical ass, and then &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.advocate.com/politics/montana-seekins-crowe-daughter-suicide&#34;&gt;this story hit the news the same day I was editing this.&lt;/a&gt; If you wanted proof, here you go. Trust me, I don&amp;rsquo;t like it anymore than you do. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you somehow couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out which of the list applies here&amp;hellip;it&amp;rsquo;s the first one, honey. I&amp;rsquo;m paler than mayonnaise. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:4&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is also a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/tertiary&#34;&gt;tertiary&lt;/a&gt; option and failure state C, where I just don&amp;rsquo;t release any of these books in any form, realize what&amp;rsquo;s good for me, stop drawing forever and take up a career as an underwater nuclear welder, bomb disposal expert, or something equally less hazardous to my health than being the weird fusion of gonzo journalist, underground cartoonist, and certifiable lunatic that I am. I don&amp;rsquo;t see that happening though. If I were smart enough to know what was good for me I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have survived this long. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:4&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:5&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten, or just never played MGS:R, Senator Armstrong is the state senator from Colorado. He also used the line &amp;ldquo;Make America Great Again&amp;rdquo; well before Orange Manbad ever made a bid for the US Presidency, and his nonsense is honestly a pretty on-the-nose reflection of the political beliefs and personal philosophies of most Colorado residents I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:5&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#003: Studio Notes/The Finer Things, January &amp; February 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0003/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0003/01.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; The corkracks, sometime in the middle of production of Our Lady Maven. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I’ve just finished up the final touches on Issue 1 of Our Lady Maven at long last, and I’ve finally got time for a bit of a breather to write a bit about what I’ve been working on, what I’ve been reading when I have a second to sit down and read, what I’ve been listening to in the studio, what I’ve been playing in my wee small hours of the morning before I pass out for the day, and (for those few of you who are curious for reasons other than wondering “what the fuck is wrong with her”) what I’ve been smoking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if this will be a regular column, but I fully intend to make it one if I can. I started doing this blog thing to talk about things that aren’t exactly “marketable” “content” to begin with and to give a bit of context as to my thought process as I go through my craft, so I can’t think of a better idea for a regular feature. I tend to align with the school of thought that holds that “death of the author” is most often misused as a cop-out by milquetoast moderates who don’t want to interrogate or even bother thinking about the moral implications of continuing to uphold the &amp;ldquo;merits&amp;rdquo; of middling fiction written by maladapted &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/mooncalf&#34;&gt;mooncalves&lt;/a&gt; (looking at you, Harry Potter fans), much less the lives and contexts of somewhat more morally ambiguous (and usually queer, non-white, or other marginalized) creators who spend their lives crafting much more complex or fucked-up narratives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m also of the school of thought that holds that the spirit of a creative work is inseparable from the context it resides in, which very much includes the thoughts, times and places the creator was working through at the time. Quite frankly, on a personal level I’ve found that the things I’ve been up to outside of putting pen to paper drastically influence my thoughts and way of being while I’m working on any given piece, and while a good portion of those things tend towards the negative a good bit of what I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading, listening to, playing through, and observing works its way in as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re still here, and are cool with kickin&amp;rsquo; back for a bit and listen to me ramble about shit I find cool&amp;hellip;you&amp;rsquo;re in luck, &amp;lsquo;cuz this is what this column&amp;rsquo;s gonna be. Oh, and if you read through this and have some records, games, books, or movies for me to check out, &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sarah@sarahallenreed.com&#34;&gt;email me at sarah (at) sarahallenreed (dot) com&lt;/a&gt; and hit me with those recs. I always love hearing from all of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0003/02.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Game in progress&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I&#39;d tell you what&#39;s going on here, but I&#39;d have to resort to things that could be considered violent or cruel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-working-on&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WORKING ON&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Lady Maven has occupied the majority (if not the entirety) of my mindshare for the past few months, and at some point I fully intend to do a full write-up on it. It&amp;rsquo;s been a labor of love from myself and &lt;a href=&#34;http://hexadecim8.com&#34;&gt;Em&lt;/a&gt; that&amp;rsquo;s been multiple years in the making, and now that it&amp;rsquo;s finally out the door I can honestly say I&amp;rsquo;m more than content with the end result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Oh, and if you wanna pick up a copy, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ourladymaven.com/shop/&#34;&gt;head on over to the webstore Em put together and go snag one&lt;/a&gt;, and if you haven&amp;rsquo;t read the series yet but would like to, &lt;a href=&#34;/comics/samplestory4&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve got a little teaser right here on the site&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also finally been sitting down to finish up the re-drafting and re-working of my graphic novel BARREN, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/p/CjVaV5LO-PW/&#34;&gt;which I received a grant for thanks to the magnificent Annie Koyama last year.&lt;/a&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit of a slog, to be honest. The best thing about re-working a script you wrote years ago is that you realize that younger you had a lot of great ideas but fucked a lot of shit up. From the looks like I have some reading to do to get some shit right, grounded, and believable before sitting down to rework the script. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;ll be worth the wait. I&amp;rsquo;m damn good at what I do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, there&amp;rsquo;s been at least one thing I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on in between bouts of inks and moments of rest and recovery that has been a unique challenge. If you &lt;a href=&#34;http://github.com/sarahallenreed&#34;&gt;follow me on Github&lt;/a&gt;, you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t noticed much in the way of new things updated, but you&amp;rsquo;ve most likely seen the little green code commit thingy get the occasional ping. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a secret project that Autumn ████████ and I have been working on, and it&amp;rsquo;s in a format of storytelling that I&amp;rsquo;ve toyed around with but never made a dedicated effort to do anything with. It&amp;rsquo;ll be a good minute before I have anything to show for my labors here, but for now I&amp;rsquo;ll let the screenshot to the left here speak for itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-listening-to&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN LISTENING TO&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there&amp;rsquo;s one little section here on this column you&amp;rsquo;ll always see, it&amp;rsquo;s this one. I literally don&amp;rsquo;t stop listening to music. I have a flip phone and don&amp;rsquo;t bother with social media these days save having &lt;a href=&#34;https://instagram.com/sarahallenreed&#34;&gt;Instagram for work&lt;/a&gt;, but I keep my old smartphone around with a pair of wireless Audio Technica noise-cancelling over-the-ears every time I leave the house so I can keep the jams going, and given the fact that I work from home through the night and sleep during the day I&amp;rsquo;m shocked my neighbors don&amp;rsquo;t complain nearly as much as they have the right to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;d be a long, long list if I were to type out everything that&amp;rsquo;s held my interest over the past couple months, but here&amp;rsquo;s a short list of records I&amp;rsquo;ve had blasting on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jonsafari/mocp&#34;&gt;mocp&lt;/a&gt; over the past bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;dean-martin---like-never-before&#34;&gt;DEAN MARTIN - LIKE NEVER BEFORE&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there is one travesty in this world, it is that it is nearly impossible to legally (or illegally, for that matter) track down Dino&amp;rsquo;s back catalogue in DRM-free form. I don&amp;rsquo;t have Spotify or any streaming services, and I adamantly refuse to pay for anything of the sort aside from the occasional Bandcamp purchase. With those restrictions in play, the only place I&amp;rsquo;ve found to track down the Rat Pack&amp;rsquo;s most quintessentially Italian member is what I have to assume is his estate&amp;rsquo;s official Youtube channel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Records one through four in this little list. One of these things is not like the other, one of these things just doesn&#39;t belong...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And thank god for that, because for as much of a Sinatra fangirl as I am Ol&amp;rsquo; Blue Eyes is in a perpetual dead fuckin&amp;rsquo; heat for &amp;ldquo;favorite Rat Pack member&amp;rdquo; with Dino. I absolutely love his old records, and highly recommend this one, &amp;ldquo;Amore&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;My Woman, My Woman, My Wife&amp;rdquo; if you need more crooners in your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended tracks: I Ran All The Way Home, &amp;lsquo;Til I Find You&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;arovane---atol-scrap&#34;&gt;AROVANE - ATOL SCRAP&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do love me some IDM. I often credit the genre for being the reason I got into making music in the first place, and this album&amp;ndash;originally released all the way back in 2000&amp;ndash;was absolutely on the list of &amp;ldquo;reasons I started&amp;rdquo;. Between this record, Plaid&amp;rsquo;s Not For Threes and a few select Aphex Twin and Outlier Recordings pics, there&amp;rsquo;s definitely a playlist worth of records I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to for the past ten years plus that I put on whenever I really need comfort food to buckle down and focus to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended tracks: Just listen to the whole thing all the way through. It&amp;rsquo;s an atmospheric IDM album, that&amp;rsquo;s what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to do.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;combichrist---what-the-fuck-is-wrong-with-you-people&#34;&gt;COMBICHRIST - WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG WITH YOU PEOPLE?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I know this one&amp;rsquo;s a bit out of place on this graphic next to Dino and Bill Evans. I also contain multitudes, so you&amp;rsquo;re going to have to roll with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I first heard this record thanks to some goth kids I went to high school with before I got kicked out, and I&amp;rsquo;ve very occasionally used it in the same way investment bankers use amphetamines; i.e., if I need a kick in the ass and a wakeup call, downing an energy drink and blasting Andy LaPlegua screaming about how you&amp;rsquo;re a piece of shit and he&amp;rsquo;s going to kick your ass definitely helps, but it&amp;rsquo;s not something I&amp;rsquo;d turn to unless I absolutely fuckin&amp;rsquo; have to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll be the first to admit a good bit of the lyrics didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly age well at best or are morally abhorrent at worst (see also the weirdly fascist-allusions-for-the-sake-of-muh-edge on &amp;ldquo;Fuck That Shit&amp;rdquo;, a track I always end up skipping), but then again 99% of industrial-adjacent acts from the 2000s and early 2010s find themselves in the same boat. (Looking at you, Mindless Self Indulgence.) I&amp;rsquo;d recommend a skip if that&amp;rsquo;s not something you&amp;rsquo;re willing to tolerate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended tracks: Get Your Body Beat, Deathbed, Electrohead&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;bill-evans-trio---portrait-in-jazz&#34;&gt;BILL EVANS TRIO - PORTRAIT IN JAZZ&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bill Evans at his finest. Back before The Jazz Program was structured in the &amp;ldquo;listening party&amp;rdquo; format it is now, I used to have a monthly feature I called the &amp;ldquo;Artist Spotlight&amp;rdquo;, which basically was the current show format on the first Tuesday of every month. (The remaining shows were mixes of whatever I wanted to throw on that week, with no real theme to them). For the last few months of 2022, I decided to just embrace the sadness I always feel during the holidays and took up the October, November, and December slots with the records I always listen to when I&amp;rsquo;m miserable and need to sob it out. Bill Evans was the second choice of the three&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and if memory serves, Portrait In Jazz was the first record on the docket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bill&amp;rsquo;s catalogue isn&amp;rsquo;t just a depression listen for me, however&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s chock full of the finest piano jazz records ever produced in the Western hemisphere. (Japan definitely gives us multiple runs for our money, but we&amp;rsquo;ll get to that when I get around to gushing about Ryo Fukui.) This album&amp;rsquo;s version of &amp;ldquo;What Is This Thing Called Love?&amp;rdquo; is one of my favorite versions of the standard by a country mile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended tracks: What Is This Thing Called Love?, Blue In Green&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;https://datafruits.fm/chat&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/03_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; Records five through eight in this little list. I want to point out that I put this graphic together at about thirty minutes past my usual bedtime and I did not notice the awkward placement going on in the...er, bottom there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;editors---an-end-has-a-start&#34;&gt;EDITORS - AN END HAS A START&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got introduced to Editors in two less-than-stellar ways. First, through enjoying the first half of their 2018 record Violence and then being utterly underwhelmed with the second half, and second, through being gobsmacked at the news of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.stereogum.com/2184148/editors-blanck-mass-member-heart-attack/music/&#34;&gt;permanent edition of experimental noise/electronic musician Blanck Mass to their lineup&lt;/a&gt; with the release of 2022&amp;rsquo;s album EBM. I still haven&amp;rsquo;t checked that record out and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I want to. The idea of noisier, edgier screamy joints mixed in with sad-boy post-punk offshoots doesn&amp;rsquo;t resonate as well with those of us who remember Myspace. I still have occasional moments where I vaguely remember Breathe Carolina exists&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and I throw up a little in my mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless of whatever they&amp;rsquo;re on these days, I&amp;rsquo;ve finally gotten around to listening to their first three records during the past few months in the studio, and to be quite frank I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve heard a record that&amp;rsquo;s hit a nerve quite like this one in a while. &amp;ldquo;The Weight Of The World&amp;rdquo; had the dubious honor of being one of the very few pieces of media that has made me tear up, and the rest of the album is as cacophonously cathartic as that track. When I wrote &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sleepingvillagereviews.com/olde-reviews/let-the-waves-have-their-way-on-interpol-and-black-metal-a-retrospective-by-sarah-allen-reed&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Let The Waves Have Their Way&amp;rdquo; for online metal mag Sleeping Village&lt;/a&gt; about Interpol&amp;rsquo;s relation to the closure and comfort present in both black and post-black metal&amp;rsquo;s most violently soothing moments and the work of New York&amp;rsquo;s bleakest foursome, I honestly could have written about this record in a different universe where I shoplifted this record instead of Our Love To Admire. Turn it up and let it wash over you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended tracks: The Weight Of The World, When Anger Shows, Smokers Outside The Hospital Doors&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;massive-attack--mezzanine&#34;&gt;MASSIVE ATTACK : MEZZANINE&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need me to give this record an introduction, you either are so young that you missed an entire generation&amp;rsquo;s worth of influences or you&amp;rsquo;ve never gotten into trip-hop for reasons that are far beyond my understanding. Let me put it this way&amp;ndash;there is a very good reason an extended cut of the first track is the menu music for cult classic Vampire The Masquerade: Bloodlines. The record &lt;em&gt;reeks&lt;/em&gt; of smoked-out clubs, sinister motives, and the sensation of wrestling with your most sickening inner thoughts and losing miserably.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;d say more, but experiencing this record will hasten your understanding of it far more than any words or clever writing I could give you. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never heard it, do yourself a favor&amp;ndash;find a copy, plug it into your stereo, and go take a night drive at one in the morning. It&amp;rsquo;ll click for you. Given the fact that I&amp;rsquo;m a nocturnal neurotic who wakes up at four in the afternoon and don&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until six in the morning, this night beat record fits perfectly in my standard rotation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended tracks: Angel, Inertia Creeps, Risingson&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;placebo---sleeping-with-ghosts&#34;&gt;PLACEBO - SLEEPING WITH GHOSTS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll admit it&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;ve bounced off of this band for most of my life. Multiple important people in my life have sworn by this English twosome (looking at you, Penpen and Autumn) but I&amp;rsquo;ve never really found a decent entry point into their discography that meshes with my taste. That changed this past month, as I started diving back into snowboarding-arcade romp SSX 3 for the first time since I was a kid (we&amp;rsquo;ll get to that in the video games section) and found &amp;ldquo;The Bitter End&amp;rdquo; on the impeccibly curated soundtrack next. My collection contains more than a few discographies I&amp;rsquo;ve acquired for people I care for, so it didn&amp;rsquo;t take long for me to locate the record that track is found on and the whole thing became an immediate repeated spin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve actually been listening to this as I write this up. The whole thing careens past at a speed just over &amp;ldquo;out of control&amp;rdquo; when it&amp;rsquo;s not cozying up to your ear on tracks like &amp;ldquo;Something Rotten&amp;rdquo; and seductively slinking around with wa-wa pedals and barely whispered vocals that sound something out of the previously mentioned Massive Attack&amp;rsquo;s sonic vocabulary. There&amp;rsquo;s also more than a couple heartfelt tracks like &amp;ldquo;Special Needs&amp;rdquo; that honestly makes a teenage me&amp;ndash;a fucked up kid that got lost in the system who ended up getting stuck with an IEP and a smorgasbord of psych meds I didn&amp;rsquo;t need instead of recieving any kind of help or being given any real chance for success&amp;ndash;feel seen. Once you put the entire package together, it makes me wish it was summer again so I could go skateboarding and get lost in the music and the flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended tracks: The Bitter End, Ashtray Girl, Something Rotten, Special Needs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-mars-volta---amputecture&#34;&gt;THE MARS VOLTA - AMPUTECTURE&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s always going to be some consistent themes in my listening habits, and &amp;ldquo;something something Omar Rodruigez-Lopez&amp;rdquo; is one of them. Best part about that is, I&amp;rsquo;m never going to run out of side projects of his to gush over. The man has never made a single bad record in his life, and I&amp;rsquo;m counting my personal least favorite of his (Bosnian Rainbows) in that. Even my least favorite project of his has its only studio album scoring at least a 7 out of 10 to me.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0003/04.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/04.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;One of the many joys of breaking hardware--custom boot screens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, Amputecture was particularly formative to me as a musician and songwriter, and aside from two of his self-produced efforts (Xenophanes and Solar Gambling) and one other TMV record (Frances The Mute) this is probably the record I return most frequently to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recommended tracks: Asilos Magdalena, Tetragrammaton&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-playing&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN PLAYING&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly a big gamer, and a lot of that is due to life circumstance&amp;ndash;most of my twenties was spent either without a consistent place to crash or living out of vehicles for months at a time, and it&amp;rsquo;s a bit hard to plug in a Playstation in a Corolla. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even own my first seventh-generation console until I bought an Xbox 360 at a Goodwill in late 2019 for half of what it was probably worth.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:4&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:4&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t allowed game consoles that were even remotely modern as a kid either, and so a lot of games that were formative storytelling experiences for a lot of my peers were things I never got to experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, working for a brief time at the electronics arbitrage desk at a recycling center during the pandemic &lt;a href=&#34;/comics/samplestory3/&#34;&gt;(an experience that insipred &amp;ldquo;I Am Starting To Empathize With Bukowski&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/a&gt; enabled me to get a couple decently-powered (if ten years old at the time I bought them) machines at cost. One of those was a Dell all-in-one which I promptly slapped on top of an old box radio that I had gutted, installed a low-end Logitech speaker system into the box, and turned it into what I usually refer to as &amp;ldquo;The Jukebox&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s not what you&amp;rsquo;d called a beast, but as of late I&amp;rsquo;ve figured out how to get the poor thing to run a few decent emulators. I also somehow scraped together the cash in 2021 to snag myself a used 2DS XL, which I of course immediately rooted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, for a good year or so now, I&amp;rsquo;ve been making a point to try and re-visit a bunch of gaming stories that I never got to experience outside of Let&amp;rsquo;s Plays for the first time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a few of the ones I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing over the past couple months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;jake-hunter-ghost-of-the-dusk-3ds&#34;&gt;JAKE HUNTER: GHOST OF THE DUSK (3DS)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love me some visual novels for the same reason I love me some detective fiction. I love a good noir-tinged romp, I adore a good mystery, and to be frank I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of a sucker for shite tropes. Snatcher is one of my favorite games of all time and is one of the reasons &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/p/CoMUs_ROWng/&#34;&gt;why I have an &amp;ldquo;Outer Heaven&amp;rdquo; flag on my wall.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:5&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:5&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0003/06_1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/06_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;They say if you look real hard at Jake Hunter&#39;s alcohol-beaten liver you&#39;ll find the codec number for the maître d&#39; of a certain nightclub in downtown Neo Kobe that sells buffalo meat. Or whale meat. Y&#39;know, whichever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, I&amp;rsquo;ve been a huge fan of the Jake Hunter series ever since I discovered the first localization on the original DS, and was absolutely stoked when I found a copy of this volume of stories for the 3DS. Dripping with charm, interesting (and at times unbearably tropy) characters, and a bunch of relatively well-put together puzzles&amp;ndash;with a few notable exceptions, including an infuriating &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.haggardhawks.com/post/moon-logic&#34;&gt;moon-logic&lt;/a&gt; puzzle in the morgue in a later chapter of the first story in the collection), Ghost Of The Dusk is as much of a favorite waiting-room holdover as any old paperback I could stuff in my purse. Plus, the whole thing is chock full of references and allusions to other thriller/detective tropes, including the obligatory genre name-drops of works of Marlowe and other golden-era crime novelists and a few more obscure and occasionally region-specific ones. My personal favorite is what I have to assume is a direct allusion to the aforementioned SNATCHER, with Jake Hunter ordering a glass of &amp;ldquo;Napoleon&amp;rdquo; within the first few lines of Chapter One&amp;ndash;a bottle of which is a key item in a specific puzzle in Kojima&amp;rsquo;s classic take on the detective adventure genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a few amusing bumps in translation&amp;ndash;including the strange &amp;ldquo;localization&amp;rdquo; choice to repaint all of the &lt;em&gt;very clearly&lt;/em&gt; Yakuza members as Italian mobsters and somehow forgetting to change both their character models and the backgrounds of the environments you find them in, which are obviously textbook Yakuza regional offices to anyone who&amp;rsquo;s bothered playing the Sega series of the same name&amp;ndash;but they honestly only add to the charm. That&amp;rsquo;s a good thing, seeing as tropey charm is this game&amp;rsquo;s bread and butter. Hell, the button you press to get a hint from the player character as to what to do or where to go next is literally the &amp;ldquo;smoke&amp;rdquo; button. You read that correctly. Press the L button (which is mapped to a literal graphic of a pack of smokes in the GUI) and Jake lights up a smoke (or doesn&amp;rsquo;t, if you&amp;rsquo;re in somewhere he deems he&amp;rsquo;d get in trouble for doing so) and tells you what to do next. Absolutely fantasic. 10/10. No notes. Every game should have this button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ssx-3-gamecube&#34;&gt;SSX 3 (GAMECUBE)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I fuckin&amp;rsquo; love extreme sports games. I can barely battle my way through a stairset on a skate deck (something that, for some reason, has never made me lose my love for longboarding) but I adore the freedom and arcade-iness of anything that puts a board or bike under you and lets you tear your way through a city with fun sound effects whenever you land a trick. &lt;a href=&#34;http://thugpro.com/&#34;&gt;THUGPRO&lt;/a&gt; has been an old favorite of mine since the days when I lived in my van, and I&amp;rsquo;d log on wherever I could track down a public Wifi network and skate a few hours away. I&amp;rsquo;ve played through nearly all of the rest of the Tony Hawk franchise as well and even (mostly successfully) stumbled my way through SKATE on the 360. With that in mind, it should be no surprise that I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of SSX3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very few sports games of this time period bothered with this kind of expansive world&amp;ndash;hell, Tony Hawk&amp;rsquo;s Underground released literally seven days after this one&amp;ndash;but SSX3 takes the interesting tracks and fun designs of Tricky and slams them all into three interconnected peaks. There&amp;rsquo;s no loading zones whatsoever&amp;ndash;if you&amp;rsquo;ve unlocked all three peaks, you can literally snowboard from the top of Peak 3 at the very pinnacle of the mountain all the way to the bottom of Peak 1 at the base. Unlocking all three peaks, however, takes a good bit of progression. Thankfully, it&amp;rsquo;s (mostly) very fun progression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0003/07.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/07.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;CUZ IT&#39;S EASYYYYY ONCE YA KNOW HOW IT&#39;S DONE YA CAN&#39;T STOP NOW IT&#39;S ALREADY BEGUUUN IT&#39;S THE FEEELIIIIIN RUNNIN THROUGH YOUR BOOOOONES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the controls can feel barely on rails at best and completely out of your control at worst, the game&amp;rsquo;s speed, intensity, and expansiveness leads to a very fun fuck-offable experience. A good portion of the controls are questionable at best (I had to remap the &amp;ldquo;reset&amp;rdquo; button, designed to put you back on the track if you fell off, away from the Y button on my controller and onto the Select button because I kept hitting the thing in the middle of races and screwing up my runs&amp;ndash;something that&amp;rsquo;s mapped in that exact way on the PS2 controller that actually &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; a Select button for a very good reason) and the AI the computer controlled players have for race modes cheats like hell, but the entire experience is absolutely a blast. If that wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough, the game comes packed with one of the most entertaining soundtracks this side of the Burnout franchise. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLZrecTLpg7CG1ICEXiEZf0JCyBTr0xYW7&#34;&gt;Placebo, Dan The Automator, Yellowcard, The Faint, Thrice, Chemical Brothers&amp;hellip;.the entire thing just blasts&lt;/a&gt;, and I have found myself staying up well past the sunrise just jamming along with The Bitter End or Jerk It Out while busting out tricks that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be physically possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes all you need is &lt;em&gt;vibes&lt;/em&gt;, man. And this game has &amp;lsquo;em in spades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;resident-evil-4-gamecubeps2&#34;&gt;RESIDENT EVIL 4 (GAMECUBE/PS2)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be honest, I bounced right the fuck off this one. &lt;a href=&#34;playlist?list=PLaSPgE4K0SB1MyNFxDny3igpCwMRdPOIO&#34;&gt;Supergreatfriend&amp;rsquo;s recent Lets Play of the Oculus port&lt;/a&gt; was one of my favorite fall-asleep-to Youtube playlists of the past year, and while I&amp;rsquo;ve tried various early titles from the series in the past I could not get past the clunkiness of the tank controls and my own blatant incompetence at handling them. So, when I figured out that Gamecube emulation worked on the Jukebox (albeit at a crawl for certain titles), I figured I&amp;rsquo;d give this one a shot. Turns out, the Gamecube emulator somehow figured out how to lag on, of all things, cutscenes. Reeeally need to get a better computer for the Jukebox.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Either way, the PS2 port ran fine, and&amp;hellip;.well, to be honest, as someone used to modern twin-stick controls, I could not get past the initial opening segment. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard that the PC port coupled with a couple mods allows for a bit more of a modern control setup, and I may try that, but as for now I&amp;rsquo;m still stuck on remembering that the right stick doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly control where the camera points in any manner that&amp;rsquo;s remotely permanent&amp;hellip;and that the knife controls like the gun in first person, which means moving the stick upwards aims the knife upwards for some reason&amp;hellip;and that you can&amp;rsquo;t move while using the knife&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0003/05.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/05.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Tea party time with the besties, might ascend to heaven and save the world later idk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to get back to you on this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fantasy-life-3ds&#34;&gt;FANTASY LIFE (3DS)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one surprised me. Best way I can describe it is &amp;ldquo;Animal Crossing meets an MMO without the online connection&amp;rdquo;, and while normally that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be up my alley whatsoever this particular little &amp;ldquo;casual romp&amp;rdquo; has slowly been taking over my life for the past few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The premise is simple&amp;ndash;you have twelve sets of jobs&amp;ndash;cleverly called Lifes in game, complete with title-case L&amp;ndash;ranging from typical fare like &amp;ldquo;mercenary&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;hunter&amp;rdquo; to left-field choices like &amp;ldquo;seamstress&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;cook&amp;rdquo; (which I of course picked). That might sound like there&amp;rsquo;s a few that are less fun to play, but even the latter titles find ways to be challenging. The &amp;ldquo;cook&amp;rdquo; job has you working in a restaurant making everything from standard omelettes at lower levels to monster meat recipes that require you to straight up slay dragons, drag their meat back to the restaurant, and cook it up, bringing a whole new meaning to &amp;ldquo;farm-to-table&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Somehow, this game mixes a fairly light-hearted (and obscenely cleverly written) storyline with extremely nerve-hitting and far-reaching themes like grieving a lost parent, the meaning of family and belonging, and what it means to choose your own path in Life, be it with the title-case L in the context of the game or in reference to self-determination in life in general. I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly easily moved by media, but somehow this cute little game that lets you don a wok as a hat while you work in a restaurant with a cook named Alfredo and bonk monsters named things like &amp;ldquo;The Napdragon&amp;rdquo; upside the noggin with two princesses in tow somehow got to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus, like&amp;hellip;look at this screenshot. It&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;adorable&lt;/em&gt;. You could argue that I should have saved my Dosh (yes, that is the actual name for this game&amp;rsquo;s currency) for better weapons or something, but I had twenty grand and bought a cute lil&amp;rsquo; log cabin with flowers and shit. It&amp;rsquo;s great. I invited my girlies over for tea and we&amp;rsquo;re gonna go out and go fishing in an active volcano later so I can catch some Lava Prawns and make this game&amp;rsquo;s equivalent of Cajun gumbo. Those are things you can do. You can also&amp;hellip;like, do the story, I guess, save the world or whatever, but the beauty of this game is that it makes a point to remind you that there&amp;rsquo;s always time for tea, and I love that about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I suppose I&amp;rsquo;m enthralled with this game for the same reason that I decided to spend hours and devote server space to gushing about these records and obscure old games&amp;ndash; sometimes you want a break from penning inordinately personal horror narratives or illustrating extraordinarily deep historical tales and the best cure for all that heavy is to spend a few hours fucking off and grinding dinosaurs for culinary ingredients in a maid outfit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life needs balance, whether it&amp;rsquo;s spelled with a capital L or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-ive-been-smoking&#34;&gt;WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN SMOKING&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah, pipe tobacco. Since I quit drinking this is the only vice I have left that I can be pretentious as all shit about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;you know, I say that, but I drank bottom shelf bourbon straight or with no-cal sodie and I&amp;rsquo;ll be the first to admit that my taste in smokes is a bit lacking. Anyways, while I&amp;rsquo;m not going to even imply that I&amp;rsquo;m a connoisseur by any means, here&amp;rsquo;s my favorite three tins of the past couple months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatright caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0003/08.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/08.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;s m o n k&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gurkha-retribution&#34;&gt;GURKHA RETRIBUTION&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spectacular English blend. I got this in a tin sampler of the Gurkha line, and to be honest this is the only one that impressed me. Heavy on the Turkish Orientals and Latakia, the blend has a fantastic woody room note and has a sizable heft to its hit without being overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cascadia-pipe-co-vertical-limit&#34;&gt;CASCADIA PIPE CO. VERTICAL LIMIT&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got this one in yet another sampler over the holidays, with an additional Cascadia tin, a pipe, and a cute lil&amp;rsquo; tin campin&amp;rsquo; mug and folding pocketknife.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:6&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:6&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Out of the two, Vertical Limit is the one I remember most&amp;ndash;nice and easy burning, heavy on the Burleys, and with a good amount of smoked Kentucky you can absolutely taste. I don&amp;rsquo;t normally go for these types of brick cuts&amp;ndash;they literally included the knife in the sampler because you need &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt; to cut these heavily pressed leaves with&amp;ndash;but if I decide to pick a brick again over my usual preferred flake cuts I&amp;rsquo;ll probably go with this&amp;rsquo;n. Probably. There&amp;rsquo;s still three other offerings from Cascadia I have yet to try out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4th-generation-1931&#34;&gt;4TH GENERATION 1931&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not gonna lie, this is my new go-to. The flake here feels just &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; to rub out onto your pipe-packing surface, the flavor is spot the fuck on and pairs gorgeously with my usual hefty method of preparing French press coffee the way I like&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:7&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:7&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, and while this is mainly billed as a Burley blend you can absolutely taste and enjoy the Virginias in it and the subtle note of Cavendish just sends it into the stratosphere. I&amp;rsquo;ve already got more tins on order. With as much as is on my desk this year, Lord knows I&amp;rsquo;ll need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;floatleft caption&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= &#34;/blog/0003/09.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/blog/0003/09.png&#34; alt=&#34;Datafruits&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A masterwork by one of the patron saints of detective fiction, and Call Of Duty 69: Ghost Goes to The Optometrist&#39;s Office&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;WHAT&amp;rsquo;S NEXT&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not going to lie, I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much time to read as of late. Is this a good thing? Probably, given the fact that I&amp;rsquo;m about to be doing a whole shitton of reading when I start in on re-working the script for BARREN in between a few other projects and Our Lady Maven Issue 2. I mentioned this a bit in the start of this document, but as you can probably tell from the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/0003/1_02.png&#34;&gt;screenshot of my working file here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;hellip;yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be drowning in a LOT of dry shit for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that stated, I&amp;rsquo;ve always got a couple dime-store numbers kicking around, and I&amp;rsquo;m always on the hunt for both quality reprints of noir classics and modern thriller fiction in paperback as well as more and more ridiculous pulp nonsense. I&amp;rsquo;ve had one of each flavor nestled nicely inside my purse for the past month, and while I haven&amp;rsquo;t left the house for a long enough time to get to sit down somewhere and read them, I&amp;rsquo;m very much looking forward to finishing both Chandler&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Little Sister&amp;rdquo; and whatever godforsaken nonsense &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OMEGA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; is supposed to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That phrasing may sound like I&amp;rsquo;m hate-reading the latter, but seriously, I fuckin&amp;rsquo; love ridiculous bullshit like this. You&amp;rsquo;re talking to someone who will unironically argue that Escape From LA is better than Escape From New York if you get me drunk enough to be comfortable gushing about my passion for campy action flick dreck.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:8&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:8&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m genuinely looking forward to finding out whether or not &amp;ldquo;dollar-store Snake Pliskin brandishing a tacticool anti-materiel rifle with the stand still up and a fucking phoropter strapped to his face&amp;rdquo; is as ridiculous as whatever&amp;rsquo;s in this book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also got a hefty backlist as far as movies goes&amp;ndash;maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll get to a few of &amp;lsquo;em next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all I got for now. I still have to do that write-up about Talkie Time, and while I hoped to be a bit more punctual with that one it&amp;rsquo;s looking like by the time I finish writing it I&amp;rsquo;ll probably end up tacking on our schedule for The Jazz Program for the month of March to the end of it. Months tend to go by fairly quickly when you&amp;rsquo;ve got ADHD, but February especially always seems to sneak up on me when I least expect it. Regardless, thanks as always for reading. You&amp;rsquo;re all amazing and don&amp;rsquo;t let anyone tell you that you&amp;rsquo;re not. Talk soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;SARAH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;Footnotes...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I recall correctly, Astrud Gilberto was November&amp;rsquo;s pick and Frank Sinatra&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;suicide albums&amp;rdquo;&amp;ndash;namely, No One Cares, Only The Lonely, and Where Are You?&amp;ndash;were played in December. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While doing research for this post, I actually found out that Breathe Carolina hails from Denver&amp;hellip;which honestly kind of explains quite a bit as to why living in Denver sucked so much ass. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how you gentrify Southern hip-hop but if anyone was going to do it it was gonna be some Denver kids. I also found out doing said research that one of the founding members &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thedailybeast.com/insufferable-twitter-stock-trading-influencers-who-boasted-of-making-millions-are-indicted&#34;&gt;has spent his past few years being obnoxious on social media and getting arrested for securities fraud&lt;/a&gt;&amp;hellip;which, again, peak Denver. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will never acknowledge Nocturniquet&amp;rsquo;s existence and you can&amp;rsquo;t make me. That album NEVER HAPPENED, I tell you, and that fact has NOTHING TO DO with the fact that said nonexistant album is a two out of ten at best. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:4&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were selling it for fifteen dollars because it &amp;ldquo;didn&amp;rsquo;t have a hard drive&amp;rdquo;. It was also an Xbox 360 Slim model, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; an external hard drive, a fact which I did not bother enlightening the clerk on. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:4&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:5&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, I know the buffalo-meat-serving nightclub in Snatcher is entirely different than the island-of-misfit-militiamen in MGSV or the severely-incompetently-staffed secret base in the MSX original. I also happen to know that Metal Gear Mk. II in MGS3 is a direct reference to the Metal Gear Mk. II player companion in Snatcher, right down to the chassis design, so maybe we should remind ourselves from time to time that &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/IDUShHRJ9aw?t=70&#34;&gt;they&amp;rsquo;re just some games and we should really just relax&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:5&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:6&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;mma be real with you here, I mainly bought it for the knife. I never say no to free knives. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:6&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:7&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Put about a quarter cup of dark roast expresso beans, an eigth of a stick of cinnamon, and a half teaspoon of chicory into a grinder. Bring your kettle to a boil, toss in the bean and spice mix, put just enough water in to let the mix bloom, stir once counter-clockwise, and let rest for two minutes. Once those flavors have time to get to know each other, do a very slow pour clockwise against the glass of the French press, then let sit for five minutes. Stir three times counter-clockwise to remove a bit of the bite, let sit for five, and press down. Boom&amp;ndash;an immaculate cup of heavy-duty brew. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:7&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:8&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnote&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the record, Escape From New York is the better made film and I know it. I just happen to adore campy action trash and to me Escape From L.A. is infinitely more fun. It&amp;rsquo;s a shame I don&amp;rsquo;t drink anymore. You&amp;rsquo;d get a much better explanation from Drunk Sarah. &lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:8&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

