<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>studio notes on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/studio-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in studio notes on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Piper Bly .</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/studio-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#022: Studio News: Fall And Winter, 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0022/</guid>
      <description>Hey ya&amp;rsquo;ll! Sorry for the delay, again, but I&amp;rsquo;ve got a whole bunch of studio news, life updates, and the like for ya. This one&amp;rsquo;s a bit long, so settle in and get comfortable.
Also, some things on this list include some heavier topics; I&amp;rsquo;ve went ahead and put a content warning both on those posts and on the titles of the sections in the table of contents, so if you&amp;rsquo;re not in the headspace for some heavier topics you can go ahead and skip past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#017: Studio News: Summer 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0017/</guid>
      <description>Hey ya&amp;rsquo;ll! As you know, it&amp;rsquo;s been a good minute since I&amp;rsquo;ve had the time to sit down and write a full-on Studio Update. We&amp;rsquo;re finally settled in&amp;ndash;mostly&amp;ndash;in the new studio1, and I wanted to check in and let y&amp;rsquo;all know what&amp;rsquo;s coming down the pike, what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to, and where I&amp;rsquo;m planning on heading next.
WHAT I&amp;rsquo;VE BEEN WORKING ON OUR LADY MAVEN Issue 2 on the drawing board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#011: The Finer Things, April &amp; May 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0011/</guid>
      <description>HahaahaAHAAHAA fuck this is late
I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy. As much as I&amp;rsquo;d like to, I&amp;rsquo;ve not had much time to pen a long column about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to in my spare time, much less had much spare time to spend. Snakes, Barren, and a couple other upcoming projects have kind of monopolized most of my attention, and I&amp;rsquo;m a bit late on having a second to sit down and write about fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#008: Studio News: March &amp; April 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0008/</guid>
      <description>Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bit of a longer segment this month, so I&amp;rsquo;m breaking my &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo; into two segments; &amp;ldquo;Studio News&amp;rdquo;, where I talk about the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to and what I&amp;rsquo;ve got in the pipeline, and &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo;, where I talk a bit about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to, watching, reading, playing, and smoking.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also got a bit of a long, introspective topic to talk about, but that&amp;rsquo;s getting lopped into its own post as well; it&amp;rsquo;s heavy enough for one of my books, which means that I&amp;rsquo;d rather put it in its own little column instead of putting it in with the lighter things I usually talk about on this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#003: Studio Notes/The Finer Things, January &amp; February 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0003/</guid>
      <description>The corkracks, sometime in the middle of production of Our Lady Maven. Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I’ve just finished up the final touches on Issue 1 of Our Lady Maven at long last, and I’ve finally got time for a bit of a breather to write a bit about what I’ve been working on, what I’ve been reading when I have a second to sit down and read, what I’ve been listening to in the studio, what I’ve been playing in my wee small hours of the morning before I pass out for the day, and (for those few of you who are curious for reasons other than wondering “what the fuck is wrong with her”) what I’ve been smoking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
