<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pinephone on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/pinephone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pinephone on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Piper Bly .</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/pinephone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 10 - Meet Navi!</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll10/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s the baby! Shown here with Vim and Nerdtree, with a tin of Bengal Slices and one of my many pipes. Here&#39;s some screenshots of my original setup, starting with Vim with Startify. Dosbox with Frederick Pohl&#39;s Gateway. Liferea. Due to the Pinephone&#39;s smaller screen, this isn&#39;t the *best* solution for RSS feeds, but I&#39;ve yet to find a CLI one I like.
And, of course, everyone&#39;s favorite PySol Fan Club Edition, which of course runs flawlessly on the Pinephone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#008: Studio News: March &amp; April 2023</title>
      <link>/post/0008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/0008/</guid>
      <description>Hey y’all! It’s your favorite dork, back at it again. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bit of a longer segment this month, so I&amp;rsquo;m breaking my &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo; into two segments; &amp;ldquo;Studio News&amp;rdquo;, where I talk about the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to and what I&amp;rsquo;ve got in the pipeline, and &amp;ldquo;The Finer Things&amp;rdquo;, where I talk a bit about what I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to, watching, reading, playing, and smoking.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also got a bit of a long, introspective topic to talk about, but that&amp;rsquo;s getting lopped into its own post as well; it&amp;rsquo;s heavy enough for one of my books, which means that I&amp;rsquo;d rather put it in its own little column instead of putting it in with the lighter things I usually talk about on this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
