<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>illustration on Truck Stop Coffee</title>
    <link>/tags/illustration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in illustration on Truck Stop Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All work written by Piper Bly .</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/illustration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 14 - Went Out Shootin&#39;, December 24, 2023</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll14/</guid>
      <description>Autumn █████████ and I went out on Christmas Eve to get both of us out of our heads a bit and for me to go shooting. Here&#39;s a little sample of what Imogen and I shot today. All of these were edited with Darktable on Linux Mint.
Some pretty goosies. the gooses are on the looses! Keeping watch.
I took a few of the geese on the lake. This one&#39;s my favorite, to be honest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 13 - Scenes From The Studio - November 2023</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll13/</guid>
      <description>November 2 November 2nd is Prey Day, of course, so that narrows down today&#39;s background noise material. The task was to do as much as I could to update the blog. I didn&#39;t get as much done as I&#39;d like, but progress is progress. The drawing board covered in last month&#39;s completed pages. Also, today I tried to take a photo of Polly with Imogen. As you can see... ...it didn&#39;t go well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 12 - Mister Pliskin Presents New Rekkids Day, December 2023</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll12/</guid>
      <description>Mister Pliskin sez it&#39;s new rekkids day. What&#39;s in the baggie? Who can say! Let&#39;s take a gander, shall we? First up: my third favorite Yes record, 90125. I used to have this one (and Fragile, my second favorite Yes record) on cassette years back when i owned a shitty Toyota Corolla with a tape deck. I&#39;ve been looking for a replacement copy ever since, and while this isn&#39;t exactly a cassette I&#39;m glad to finally have it in the collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 11 - Jazzy Fuckin&#39; Holidays 2023 Poster Process</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll11/</guid>
      <description>Drafting, Pencilling, and Inking Starting in on pencils. The lettering and all that was done (as always) on graph paper and glued up as I went; for a more in-depth look at how I do that, check out this process thread. Here&#39;s the rest of the lettering, glued up and into place. Starting in on inks. Two passes later. I was originally going to black the entire poster&#39;s background out, but I decided to sketch in some variations in tone for the sky and trees as opposed to simply a blacked-out sky covered in snow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 09 - Scenes From The Studio - Datafruits World Expo Poster</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll09/</guid>
      <description>Initial pencils and lettering. Starting in on inking. First and second pass of inks down. I wanna point out here that the lil&#39; guy there in the witch&#39;s hand was designed by Datafruits&#39; own Zaxy. His name is Beamsprout, if you were curious. As with nearly everything else, I&#39;m doing the lettering by hand.
Inking the lettering... ...gluing it into place... ...and affixing it to the drawing. Yet another pass of inks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 05 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 2, Part 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll05/</guid>
      <description>Part one of a series of progress photo galleries of me working through Our Lady Maven, Issue 2.
Hand-lettering, as usual. It&#39;s how we do it here. Pencilling in a facsimile of the Chicago skyline. Roughing in the other two panels. Blocking in the kids with some more rough pencils. I&#39;m using a General&#39;s carpenter&#39;s pencil here to scratch in some shading to mark where I&#39;m going to put some thick swatches of black ink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 04 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 2</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll04/</guid>
      <description>Part two of two sets of progress photos of me working my way through the concept art for The Garden.
Initial pencils for the concept art for Kaia here. Pencilling in the adults.... ...and the other kiddos. Adding in some inks on the concept art of the adults. Inked kiddos. Karina, Penny, and Bobbie on the top, and a full sheet of Kaia on the bottom. Final scanned and digitized inks for the adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 03 - Scenes From The Studio - The Garden Concept Art, part 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll03/</guid>
      <description>Part one of two sets of progress photos of me working my way through the concept art for The Garden.
The initial pencils for the concept art image. I hid [Gnome Chompski](https://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Garden_Gnome) in there somewhere--see if you can find &#39;im! Starting in on inks, going section by section. Layer layer layer Most of the sections are filled in now; only a few more adjustments then it&#39;s digitization time. The final, digitized inks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Roll 02 - Scenes From The Studio - Our Lady Maven, Issue 1</title>
      <link>/post/photoroll02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/photoroll02/</guid>
      <description>Some in-progress photos of me working my way through Our Lady Maven Issue 1.
Inking panels from the comic. Full art for Page 8. Close up inks. You can see the ink smudges from the typewriter real well here. Probably my favorite panel. Sneaking in an overt homage to one of my favorite adventure game detectives Pages 12 and 13.
Corkracks full of pages in progress. Inking page 14 Even more corkracks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
